Chapter 104

Matt looked at his system screen, it had changed slightly after the fiasco that was that secret ground. He walked slowly through the large compound, there was far too much space here. He didn't know why people liked to live in such grand luxury, he still preferred smaller apartment-like spaces.

'They sure like to live it large... well not like my own clan is any different. Maybe I should make some budget cuts...'

He laughed to himself as he was now part of the dreaded ruling class, he was still new to this but the system was coming handy. The system showed him the all-around happiness of the people living in the city he was considered the lord of. He could see the crime rates, the death toll even how clean the area the people lived in was.

'But, this place is just terrible...'

There was color shading to signal the places in question, red indicated that it was dangerously low and not somewhere people should be living in. Then it went to orange after that was yellow and finally green. The colors also varied by how bright or dark they were.

'Spirit Spring City wasn't as bad as this...'

He gave out a sigh while walking, there were many people shuffling around this place searching for resources and hidden areas that the Cheng Clan was hiding. Matt didn't really bother with things like that, he left it to the juniors. He also sent Zhang Zhi in hot pursuit of the fleeing Cheng clansmen, he was still somewhat amused that he got them to wear those police uniforms. He hoped that his plan to change the way the people operated in those cities would go through.

He was still someone that grew up in the twenty-first century, he was used to things like plumbing and not having to see horse shit all over the road while walking. The sanitary situation in this world wasn't all that great, no one really minded doing their business in the bushes. People also did their deed in a bucket and then threw it outside the window or even on the street.

'Operation plumbing will have high priority in this city.'

He flew upwards on his sword, it looked a bit different than before as he reforged it himself. He was still thinking back how much of a drag it was to learn all those techniques again. He wasn't sure why the system changed but it looked like it removed the training wheels from itself after he was trashed by that demon dude. He started recalling what happened back then, he still felt that he should have died after that final battle.

He woke up back in Spirit Spring City, naked and submerged in some kind of water tank with healing liquid. This was some kind of special healing chamber used in times of need. He didn't look as malnourished as he was after the fight, having recovered most of his muscle thanks to the nourishing liquids in that healing tank. After his discharge from the watery healing facility, he received a report about what happened back then after he passed out.

The robotic voice congratulated them for passing the trials, the elders could even keep one secret book from the library when they left. This happened after he had that punching duel with the pride demon. All of them were awarded one book of their choosing, they could take it with them. This wasn't much of a prize for Zhang Dong, as he already had everything written down in his system library.

He decided to just offer the other cultivators his manual instead as he didn't need it. He even taught them rock-paper-scissors so they could decide who received the bonus manuscript. In the end, the old granny from the Feng clan beat all of them and took another wind cultivation technique for her and Feng Liena's clan. He still chuckled as he remembered how much Huo Qiang was pouting after his loss.

There was no reward for the junior members, soon after the stage ended the whole place started shaking and everyone began teleporting outside. Everyone expected to receive a good patdown by the Dark Palm sect when they got out, the heaven graded manuals that the elders received were in danger of being discovered and snatched.

They were teleported onto the same platforms that they used to get inside the training ground, but something was off. It looked deserted, they couldn't see any Dark Palm sect cultivators around at all. Everyone was startled, wondering if some powerful beast whacked those powerful cultivators, worrying if they were in danger or not.

Everyone gathered up together and headed out of the teleportation chamber, backtracking as they still remembered the way that they used to walk here. They arrived at the place that the large door was and finally found some people in that room. Those people were wearing the Dark Palm sect robes, but their cultivation was rather low. When they saw the Clans returning their eyes almost popped out of their sockets, or at least that was what the Zhang Clan members recalled.

Apparently the door started to suddenly open itself, probably because the trial was finished. The Dark Palm cultivators quickly reacted as they brought everyone above the foundation establishment early stage into this main room. Then something strange happened, the door slammed open and a giant suction force was directed towards the cultivators in that chamber. No one could resist it, not even the nascent soul elder that was with them.

Every sect member was sucked inside of it, the door quickly closing itself afterward and only the weaker members of the sect were left to guard it. The clans still had six core formation experts with them besides the injured Zhang Dong and even many foundation establishment members in the great circle.

The remaining sect members knew that they had the sect backing them, but it would be unwise to threaten these cultivators that could easily slaughter them while telling some lie about what really happened. The clans decided to leave the sect members alone, it would be better if they didn't have some kind of nascent soul uncle coming to their clan demanding to know what happened, the sect members could explain it themselves later, without bringing unnecessary risks.

But with this, they were able to keep all of their rewards and return safely. The weakened sect expedition party couldn't force them to stay there at most they could report it to their higherups and have the clans searched later, but they knew that they wouldn't find anything afterward. The important thing now was, to monitor the sacred ground and wait for their elder to return with good news. They would send some words to the main sect, but it would take a while to produce another large team like the one that was sucked inside the strange door.

Zhang Dong was the most injured of the group, the other clans could have used this opportunity to rob the Zhang Clan of their riches but they decided to aid them instead. They guarded the injured man, that was carried by his own clansmen Feng Liena and Huo Qiang sticking to him closely as they considered him a fellow comrade by now.

Afterward, everyone pulled out their transmission treasures and contacted their clans so they would escort them back. The friendly clans even helped the Zhang Clan to bring their Patriarch back to the city, afraid that some core formation cultivator might try their luck on the weakened Zhang Clan.

He ended up in his clan's version of the intense care unit, which was the strange tank filled with green liquid. He was in it for about three months before he woke up, even then he was feeling drained and it took him another month to make a full recovery. He had trouble walking and eating, but at least he had lots of time to check out his new system setting.

He didn't find it out till later, but he couldn't earn any more spirit points for slaying people or monsters. For some reason, this main feature was removed, but he could still absorb spirit stones and convert it to points, though the gains were worse than before. The cash shop was gone too, the icon vanished from the main window screen and was nowhere to be found.

He wondered why this happened, was it because he suffered a near-death experience or did his level up to a peak core formation expert had something to do with it. How would he even craft more weapons or items if he couldn't buy any more schematics he thought, this prompted him to check things out in his crafting abode.

His eyes went wide as the once small crafting space was several times bigger and looked more like a blacksmiths lair now. There were large cauldrons, various hammers and tongs lying about. Also, he spotted things that shouldn't be there, like a classical looking pill furnace. But this place was supposed to be for crafting weapons and armor, not pill making or so he thought.

The place had many more things, but also others were missing. The window to the crafting abode changed, the familiar graphical interface was gone replaced by something else. There was no way to bring up the previously implemented shop to buy resources or crafting schematics. But there was a research window on the side, when he brought it up he could see all the things that he made and all the crafting schematics that he previously bought.

There was also some kind of separate number there, it was at zero for now and had the letters 'CP' next to it. Soon he found out what that meant. The dancing game that he 'loved' so much was gone, this meant that he was supposed to craft the items the old fashioned way. Using the items that were scattered in this room along with the crafting techniques that were infused into his brain.

He still was the holder of the Dao of Smithing and Crafting, it turned out that it wasn't just for show. He tested things out, making the simplest of daggers. His hands just moved on their own as if he knew what he was doing, still, his movements were awkward and unpracticed so he ended up with a middle graded common weapon. He thought that the Dao's were only good for lowering prices, but they actually made him very proficient in anything related to them.

Thanks to this test, he noticed his 'CP' increasing. He later decided to call them crafting points, he would earn them each time he created something, was it a weapon, an armor piece or a magical treasure. He even received them for creating pills and elixirs, but he wasn't so good at that, the Dao of pill concocting was something separate to the crafting and forging one. But this was something that he could learn later, he had all the required manuals stashed away.

The crafting points could be spent on many things, like regular upgrades to the new crafting abode. Better hammers or better smelters, but the most useful things he could spend it on were upgrades for the schematics and for any crafting related skills that he possessed. For instance, if he had basic metallurgic skills, he could craft the required amount of daggers and then use the points to make that skill better, the knowledge would flow into his mind just like when he bought it through the store.

Previously he could have just bought himself the skills and techniques he required in that cash shop, but now he had to put in the work. He realized that there was a big difference in learning skills in this new way. He had to work his way through, learn the lesser skills before he could receive the better one at the end. This made him a lot more proficient in them, having built up a good foundation through the process.

Also, he received bonus points if he created something without requiring the system's schematics. He also could spend the points so that he would receive a bonus to the crafted item, it could be random or something precise depending on the number of points he spent. He also had the whole library of high-quality manuals in his system, it was still there and he could absorb the knowledge whenever he required. He held back on it though as he thought too much knowledge might fry his brain if he just tried absorbing everything at once.

Besides that, he could still upgrade his cultivation level like he could before the skill tree was showing him that golden nascent soul option that was next in line for taking. Though that would take a while as he had a whole hundred points and couldn't get easy ones by slaying monsters. There were a couple of ways that he could do it though.

First was just plain old capitalism, snatch as many spirit stones as he could get his hands on. He cold craft items, sell them or even obtain a lot of cash for the more harmless techniques that he could write down from his library.

The second one was playing with his clan window, he could earn passive points through improving the living conditions of his people. He would also win bonuses for things like their all-around strength, loyalty, happiness. This looked like a lucrative endeavor as gaining points without having to do nothing was always appreciated. The hundred points he had now were all gained through this method as he was out and recovering.

The third was his disciples, but he wasn't betting much on that one. It looked more like a side gig, the points that he received from them breaking through levels were rather low.

The fourth one was kind of similar to the first one, he could still absorb beast cores for points or any other spiritual artifacts of that sort. So he could still hunt, or go on treasure hunts.

Due to this, improving the living environment of his people started. He started creating things like schools, clinics, police stations to keep the order going. He was already at the hundred percent mark with this cultivation and he just needed to gather points for the next jump. For now, he could spend his time improving his skills, while the points slowly ticked up. If he managed to build up a good base of operations he should be able to rake in those points in the future.

A note from Kuropon

Join the Patreon for some more Chapters https://www.patreon.com/kuropon

Also, join the discord https://discord.gg/fWefdgn

Stay safe!

Chapter 105

Matt had spent the bulk of those two years relearning his crafting techniques. He had to actually do it manually but the gained knowledge opened up new ways and opportunities. There was one particular nifty perk of the new system, he could reverse engineer weapons and treasures that other people made. He had a chance of receiving crafting points through that but also the schematics for that item. It mostly depended on the ranking of the items and how the system rated his current skills.

For instance, while being a Novice Blacksmith, he couldn't really earn anything from items that were above the common grade. He gained those schematics by depositing the item in question into a special smelter, it would burn the item up and then signal him if he received something back. He could also use it to gain a percentage of resources that the item was made from in return, so it wasn't a total waste even if he failed.

So came the grudging task to work himself to a semi-reliable craftsman. There was a difference between having the knowledge in your brain and actually doing things with your hands. He fumbled around constantly, hammered items into unrecognizable lumps and atrocities pulling his hair out at night as he burned through the resources.

The system ranking was self-explanatory it started from the Novice rank, then went Apprentice, Adept, Expert, Master, and Grandmaster at the end. He thought that the ranking names would be more eastern styled but they were exactly like ones from a certain RPG game he used to spend countless hours on back in the day.

There were also separate occupations for each crafting classes like Blacksmith, Apothecary, Alchemist, Armorer. For instance, Alchemist was more geared towards making liquid elixirs while Apothecary was your usual pill maker, the former was more popular around this world than the later both had their good and bad parts.

The Alchemist's elixirs were harder to brew, even small deviations and mistakes would turn your elixir into black sludge but when you made it right you received something special. In response, pill making was more lenient you just ended up with a pill of a lower grading that had a certain level of toxicity to it. If you took too many of those toxic pills your cultivation would suffer later on and without some special cleansing pills, you might even remain stuck at a realm with no way of progressing in the future.

But time is what Matt had plenty, he couldn't reach the Nascent Soul level without gathering ten million points and regular cultivation would just take far too long. He also feard that he could blunder while breaking through such an important realm and suffer some consequences if he did it. The system only updated his cultivation method after he upgraded it, so he didn't have the nascent soul version of his method in his brain just yet.

He spent those two years on crafting, due to having many manuals geared towards healing and forging he was able to increase his knowledge in certain Daos. He couldn't tell if there was a bonus in the system to having multiple Daos anymore, he could see his progress in his status screen. It was always nice to have a tangible number attached, it showed him if he progressed or if he was stuck in a rut. After the two years, his Status window looked something like this.

Name : | Zhang Dong
Affiliation : | Zhang Clan
Spirit Points : | 8973267
Cultivation Base Qi : | Core Formation [Great Circle 100%] (Divine Golden Lightning Core)
Cultivation Base Body : | Core Formation [Great Circle 100 %] (Golden Body)
Techniques : | Divine Lightning Path Cultivation Art, Golden Body Arts, Thunderlight Sword, Thunder Movement Art...
Dao : | Dao of Heavenly Lightning, Dao of Smithing and Crafting...
Other : | Senior Aura, Impartation of Knowledge, Mentor's Eyes, Apprisal...

When he went into his Dao section you would see :

Name | Proficiency
Heavenly Lightning (Greater) | 100%
Smithing and Crafting (Greater) | 100%
Pill Making (Greater) | 20%
Alchemy (Greater) | 16%
Holy (Greater) | 50%
Water (Greater) | 25%

The interesting thing about the status screen was, that it only showed him the greater Daos, so, for instance, he could click the Water Dao section and it would show him all the lesser Daos that he learned. He was part of the Zhang Clan so in his free time he decided to learn some of their techniques. So you would see the Dao of Rainwater in that section, ice-related Daos would also be featured in there.

He earned the Holy element Dao knowledge thanks to his upgrade of the cultivation technique. His elemental affinities were also going upwards the more he immersed himself into the Daos, the only thing holding him back was the lack of time. Thanks to the various manuals of the heaven grade he could progress at a fast rate, but even then it wasn't that easy. He couldn't just absorb the knowledge from the manual and be a Grandmaster at it from the start.

Just like with his crafting skills, he had to make his body and soul experience the various spiritual energies from the Daos. Take his time to digest and contemplate before reaching an epiphany. But after grasping that essence of the Dao he was able to process and learn the skills from it at a rapid rate.

After immersing himself in the techniques he also noticed that there was a difference in rankings to them. The system gave him the bare-bones knowledge letting him move into the novice level without problems. There were various ways that people in this world rated the level of their proficiency in skills like minor success stage and greater success stage. Matt preferred the grading of the system gave him, the RPG like mechanics were much easier to digest.

It went the same as with the crafting ranks, starting from Novice all up to Grandmaster. Six stages of proficiency, if you got it all the way up to Grandmaster a lower graded technique could start competing with a higher graded one, even jumping one larger stage in power.

He could instantly bring his skills up into the Novice stage, it took some training to move it into the apprentice stage but it was still fairly easy. Adept was the staple stage you wanted to be in, it wasn't so hard to earn it but it let the practitioner wield his techniques with moderate competence. He set out to obtain all of his skills to this level at least, he even earned some system points for training and getting his proficiencies up.

For instance, the Supreme Thunder God's Penetrative Nirvana Finger attack. When he used it against the demonic being it was at most at the apprentice level, if he managed to push it up to the expert level he probably wouldn't have had to burn through his life force to win that battle.

Thanks to his Lightning Dao Mastery all lightning-based techniques came quite easy, still, he would have to train for quite a bit to take them all the way up to Grandmaster. For now, He aimed to bring his most used skills up to expert status. He was also a bit worried that he was spreading himself too thin. It always came down to time, at least the system was helping him upgrade the skills if he needed too which made them more powerful and easier to absorb.

Back in the present Matt nodded at some of his clan members that passed by him and gave him the usual 'Oh god it's the glorious Patriarch' Bow. He wondered if he could do something about this mindset, maybe in a hundred years the people could stop bowing to everyone they met, operation handshake would take a while.

He had some things to do as he went into a secluded room and jumped into his crafting abode.

'I'm glad that I have this thing with me now, otherwise, I would have to spend all of my free time in here slaving away.'

He patted a furnace looking contraption that was standing in one of the rooms of his new crafting castle. The area was a lot bigger than before and it had separate rooms for crafting and forging of other items. He was standing next to a very important item, it was something like a 3D printer.

This was quite the nifty little thing that he discovered while examining his new crafting base. After he manufactured an item it would be graded, there was the main grading and the advanced one. This here 3D printer was a time-saver, he could insert the created item into one part of it and the 3D printer would copy it down. It required resources to copy things, you could just put them into another slot. There was also a size limit, but he could upgrade it further to counteract that.

The product that came up would be of lower quality than the original though, but he could spend crafting points to upgrade this contraption. So by now it only dropped a couple of those advanced grades, in the beginning, it would even drop from a high grade all the way down to a low grade.

'Took quite a bit of crafting points to get this going, but now I don't have to produce all those police and military uniforms myself.'

The thought back to all those sleepless nights that he spent creating the police caps, the etching of the emblems was quite time-consuming as well.

'Xue finally reached the early stage of foundation establishment, I promised to gift her something if she managed to do it within the year. Damn kids progressing faster than their own master!'

Zhang Liu was close to reaching the middle stage now, he was slightly ahead of his younger sister but she was quickly catching up. The girly being the youngest foundation establishment cultivator that the clan had brought up. Their progress was slowing down though, it would probably take some time till they are ready to burst through to core formation.

Things were hectic at the start, so he couldn't really focus on his two cute disciples that much, he was more concerned about points at that time. Only later was he able to actually reevaluate his approach, he couldn't just give them random skills and techniques that he used. They both had different proficiencies and talents.

Xue was proficient in the Spear, while Liu was good with the Saber. He had already produced a perfect graded Saber for the youth not long ago, he remembered that he was really worried back then as he didn't fully grasp his crafting skill yet at that point. It was a bit of a drag that none of them were proficient in swords, he would have to train in those himself if he wanted to pass down any input that he had.

Luckily he wasn't required to do that, the kids were fine with receiving some manuals and the crafted weapons. Everyone in this world understood that people were different and your master wasn't required to give you everything. They needed to tread their own path in life, he was just supposed to partially guide them along.

"Well then, let me get this over with!"

He was already an expert blacksmith at this point and he used a technique that didn't require much hammering to produce strong weapons.

"Guess I'll make it a normal leaf-shaped blade and the tassel will have a sky blue color to signify the Zhang Clan."

He used some spiritual energy to move the required iron ingots to the desired spot in front of him. He learned a certain crafting skill thanks to the seventh level of that trial tower, it was a high grade technique that required the utmost concentration. He moved his fingers like a conductor his lightning energy flowing into the blocky piece of metal.

It was heated up and quickly turned into a red hot liquid while hovering up in the air. Then with a couple of flicks of his fingers, the lump started extending slowly taking the shape of that leaf-like blade tip. Soon a spear shaft flew in from the side, Matt was sitting in a lotus position eyes closed and his arms moving around slowly while concentrating.

The shaft was made from special wood, it was much more resistant than regular steel. The flaming tip and the spear shaft embedded themselves into each other as the process continued. The resistant hair of a formation establishment beast was used as the tassel, the weapon coming together nicely as the process was finished.

Matt whipped the sweat from his brow, this skill made things easier and faster but it was quite taxing on his cultivation. The harder the materials the more time he had to spend on them. But thanks to this, he saved copious amounts of time and he could train his Qi manipulation while crafting as well.

"There, that should do it... let me just put my emblem onto it... and done!"

A little lightning bolt was embedded into the blade, showing that it was something that he made. He still liked to mark things that he made himself, good marketing was key. People liked to buy up his custom made stuff like hotcakes and thanks to that he almost had that ten million points to reach the next level of power.

'Soon...'

A note from Kuropon

Join the Patreon for some more Chapters https://www.patreon.com/kuropon

Also, join the discord https://discord.gg/fWefdgn

Updated the Tiers a bit.

Chapter 106

These past two years had been more or less peaceful, but Matt knew that it wouldn't take much to break this illusion of peace. He didn't know what happened to the Dark Palm sect members back in the secret ground, they had some spies in the nearby cities to scout things out. But they weren't giving them any good reports, the area was still on lockdown. No way to know if those guys found that immortal technique back there that they were hoping for or not.

He had to stay vigilant, there was a small run-in with their force not long after they escaped that secret ground. But they were mostly just interested in the things that happened transpired at the secret ground. He wasn't sure what the other clan's said to them, but Matt thought that the Zhang Clan wasn't strong enough to go against that sect just yet. But that could change soon after he obtained those ten million points.

There was contradicting intel about how many nascent soul cultivators that sect had, but it shouldn't be that many. It wasn't one of the giant sects that had their headquarters in the most spiritual energy-rich locations on the continent but it wasn't the weakest either. One thing was clear, the only way he could hope to resist them was to reach the next level of power.

He was somewhat confident in fighting a nascent soul expert at the early stage. If he compared that monster to the elder that greeted him before they went into the secret ground, then the monster was stronger. The Sin of Pride was also a dual cultivator, those regenerative and defensive capabilities were only beaten thanks to his new holy attribute being the bane of demons and devils.

He had gotten a lot stronger since then, the condensation skills and his avatar form were all trained up to the expert levels which let him last in that empowered state for a lot longer now. But that wasn't the answer, at most he could hope to take out one nascent soul expert in a fair bout. But if there were two, or if they knew his weak point and stalled for time he would probably lose.

'Ah, if I didn't train my Tranquil Mind up to the Master level I'd probably be a shaking mess by now.'

The life of the glorious Patriarch wasn't that easy, he was constantly reminded that thousands, no millions of people's lives depended on him. Sure he could be like the other rich and powerful cultivators and not care about the general populace. But that just wasn't him, he couldn't just abandon everyone and flee when things got tough.

'Well, I guess I should check up on the others and see how they are doing with the next stage of the plan.'

He strode to one of the larger rooms of the old Cheng Clan compound, they had started setting up their base of operations here. His retainers were already waiting for him, ready to give their report.

"So, how are things proceeding Kuo?"

The man was holding a communication jade in his hand and then looked to the Patriarch, he was already reporting while preforming his perfect graded bow.

"Reporting to the Patriarch! Captain Zhi has apprehended the Cheng Clan Patriarch and is heading back here, we also managed to capture the rest of their clan members but a couple of them fled into the surrounding forest and are hiding."

Matt rubbed his chin while listening to the report.

"Oh? Weren't they fleeing in a flying ship, shouldn't it be easy to just capture them all on it?"

Zhang Kuo fixed his glasses slightly while a tiny bit of sweat formed on his forehead.

"Captain Zhi destroyed the ship and sliced it two halves before the rest of the pursuing team could give him support..."

Matt blinked and scratched his cheek slightly, thinking back to what he said to the man before he charged off to battle.

'Hm... guess I shouldn't have told him to bring them back at any cost... or the part with whacking them good if they resisted...'

Zhang Zhi was a powerful cultivator, already in the core formation stage and at a fairly young age. His only bad trait was, that he would take everything literally. He would follow up on any order with the utmost care, from Matt's point of view the man had kind of a Patriarch complex. The way he bowed and how his eyes shined whenever he ordered him to do something, was slowly giving him the creeps.

'I bet if I ordered him to wear a pink tutu, he would think its some powerful spiritual treasure that I'm gifting him to further his cultivation. Though it was surprising to hear that he was getting married that time, he even has a kid already.'

Matt wasn't in the tower defense section for too long, but a certain power couple was born from it. It was Zhang Zhi and Feng Daiyu, the woman was truly massive the word Amazon perfectly describing her, those chiseled abs were quite astonishing. Supposedly the two hit it off back in the training ground, he didn't know anything specific but whenever he asked about how Zhang Zhi met his wife he looked depressed.

Later on, it would be revealed that the woman sneaked into his bed chambers after one of the more hard-fought battles. She didn't take no for an answer and devoured the poor Zhang Zhi's chastity the man was still pure and innocent even at forty, his only purpose in life being cultivation. The child was born out of wedlock and they only found out after the woman's belly was already large. Zhi was quite an honorable man, so he decided to get engaged to the amazonian woman that became Zhang Daiyu and was back with their daughter in Spirit Spring City.

"That's troublesome, but he made this mess so he should clean it up. Tell him to form a search party and bring the other Cheng Clan members back, we need to show the people how we treat criminals like them."

Normally what happened in this kind of world would be a clan cleansing, every member of this clan would be captured and killed. Matt wanted to change that, he wanted to gather evidence and then put people up on a trial. The death sentence wouldn't be the only thing they could do, sentencing to hard labor was also an option. Making someone a criminal slave wasn't out of the question either, they would work with a slave collar slowly paying back their debt to society.

'Luckily we have spiritual treasures that can tell if you are telling the truth, this makes the whole thing a lot easier.'

Thanks to treasures like these he didn't really need to create occupations like lawyers. The process would be nice and smooth, but others could still temper with those treasures so they still had to watch out for swindlers. Thanks to his new gained crafting potential he could come up with various new treasures that could emulate things that he knew back from Earth.

One such item was making its way into the City Square, the common people were looking at the Zhang Clan that used to be the rulers here, quite interested in what they were doing. There was a chubby statue being removed that was a spitting image of the man Zhang Zhi whacked today. It was being torn down to make way for a large fountain, or at least that was what it looked like.

Thanks to spatial technology that was also improved by Matt's crafting knowledge, they could set up the new magical fountain.

The fountain was circular shape at the base, inside of it were four pillars with dragon heads coming out of them. On those pillars was a smaller cauldron, the water inside of this fountain was radiating blue light and even the regular people felt that this thing wasn't simple.

"What is that, a fountain?"

"Are they from the fabled Zhang Clan? Think their Patriarch is here, maybe he'll sign my manuscript?"

"Why would he do that?"

The area was abuzz while the Zhang Clan cultivators finished up, they inserted something shiny into a slot in one of the pillars which made the whole thing glow for a moment. The spectacle subsided soon after, the dragon heads spitting out water after the magical item got activated.

Suddenly something happened, the cauldron that was smaller in size than the whole fountain but still quite large began to light up. The water inside it gave off a deep blue coloring which soon lit up the whole place. The people gasped as a pillar of light shot up into the sky, everyone within the square could see the bright beam of light.

This wasn't over though, inside the beam of light they saw a person. It was a rather handsome man, due to the coloring of the water he was in a shade of blue. He was standing up straight, his hands behind his back making him look like a seasoned veteran cultivator. The commoners gulped as the man looked quite lifelike as if he was going to jump out and give them a throughout thrashing.

"Greetings people of Moonlight City, my name is Zhang Dong and I am the Patriarch of the Zhang Clan that you see before you."

To the people's surprise, the man in the fountain started to speak, it was even the widely talked about Zhang Clan Patriarch! Everyone moved closer, their ears perking up as they gathered, they felt truly blessed for having such an expert talk to them.

"Fear not, My Zhang Clan isn't like the previous Cheng Clan, we will treat you right."

He reached out with his hand, gesturing to the Zhang Clan members that were dressed in the new police uniforms.

"These members from my clan will keep order in the streets, they will be stationed in a separate building soon."

"Even while I'm speaking to you, they have rescued countless good people from slavers and hooligan's alike."

The man moved his hands behind his back and struck a valiant pose, the people not really knowing how to react to the whole spectacle as they didn't expect anything like this.

"I'll leave you with my Junior Sister, she will be the one delivering the news in the future. May you live long and prosper."

The so-called Zhang Clan Patriarch then moved to the side and bade his farewells to the masses, in his place appeared quite the lovely lady. She had quite the nice curvature, was wearing glasses and had a strange form-fitting robe. It was just an ordinary female business suit, with a miniskirt that Matt fashioned after the image of newscasters from his old world.

The woman bowed to the people, looking quite professional while doing it.

"Greetings this sister's name is Zhang Meifen, I'll be reporting the news in this city from now on."

The people of this world had no idea what was going on, the motion of daily or weekly news was something that they didn't know about. Most information was distributed by word of mouth and there were some information agencies doing it for a steep price.

"Following the capture of the Cheng Clan members, we will be conducting a trial..."

The woman started talking about the new trail system, about how slavery would be forbidden and anyone that took part in it would be sentenced to hard labor, you could even have your cultivation crippled. While the lady was doing her thing, Matt moved back to the side he knew that he needed to throw in some words there as the leading figure, he even thought he did a good job all things considered.

'Hm, think I'm getting less stressed from these public appearances, when I did this back at home it was scarier.'

This was something he came up in his free time, what was better than a television to bring your message across. He fumbled around in his crafting fort, trying to make something that would produce an image with sound and finally was able to produce this fountain-like hologram. This would be a great propaganda tool as well, he could slowly bring his clan's image up while diminishing the image of other powers if there was a need for it.

This was just a prototype that burned way too much spirit energy, but he was planning to set up more portable TV like items into the people's homes. Maybe he could make something like the internet in the future. They just needed to expand their infrastructure, he had two options. Either to supply the spiritual power with something like cables, or fashion them in such a way that the treasures would absorb the residual Qi in the surroundings.

He wanted to go with option two, but he would need to lower the energy requirement first and make the items more compact. For now, this would do. The Moonlight city restoration project had just taken off and it was going well for the Zhang Clan, but they still had some pesky mice to take care of.

A note from Kuropon

Join the Patreon for some more Chapters https://www.patreon.com/kuropon

Also, join the discord https://discord.gg/fWefdgn

Chapter 107

The people started whispering amongst each other, the fountain hologram had finally been turned off, the new ruling clan and their members had left the square. No one dared to utter a word or question them about anything, they were still afraid. The Zhang Clan used to rule this city before, but even then they weren't like this. They weren't as bad as the evil Cheng Clan, but they still upheld the status quo.

The woman in the picture explained a couple of things. That there would be something like the 'police' patrolling the city, this was easy to understand as they were just guardsmen in strange uniforms. The other things were a bit odd, the woman said that some of the taxes would go to something called 'health care' and you could sign up to a clinic and get yourself checked out by a physician without having to pay. The taxes would cover the expense instead.

"Are they testing us or something, this sounds too good to be true..."

Some of the people whispered after the threat of the powerful family was gone. They having left after doing their strange announcement.

This wasn't all, besides the police and free clinics for the masses there would also be a school. This wasn't just a martial arts school in which you could earn some low graded techniques, no. This would be something that youths from a young age could attend, learn how to read and write and even have some free standardized techniques and cultivation manuals to choose from. They even said that the promising students would have an option of being invited into the midst of the powerful Zhang Clan.

"Yes, why would they want us to join their family, wouldn't that just lower their prestige?"

"But what if it's true... It wouldn't be bad to have my little Wang'er to learn something from such a powerful clan..."

"Yes, if even one of my brats could join that clan I would be set for life!"

The people's reaction to the things that the Zhang Clan was offering was mixed. They wanted to believe in the families' goodwill, but they were also afraid that those places might have some shady dealings. It wouldn't be much of a stretch if they had their kids enroll in that 'free' school and then some Zhang Clan uncle would come demanding payment, their kids could even be captured and turned to slaves.

Most of these people were from the first up to the third level of Qi condensation, this was the realm the vast majority of regular people reached. The bottleneck past the third level was just too hard without having the backing of a clan and their knowledge. It was a risky move to attempt it on your own a lot of people crippled themselves while struggling to force their way through.

"Wonder what the other families think about this..."

"Not like they can go against the Zhang Clan, anything is better than those blasted Chens."

"Hope that Patriarch of theirs has a slow death... his bastard kids were always bullying everyone, how many young girls lives did the end?"

The people started rumbling about how the old clan was trash, their bravery kicking in at the moment the city was taken over by the new power.

The Cheng Clan wasn't the only family clan in the city though, it was only the strongest. This city was far too large to have only one big faction to run it, there were many smaller family clans around that were just controlled by the big overlord that was the Cheng Clan. This wasn't anything new, the same thing was also true back in Spirit Spring City. You could say that the Cheng Clan was the Dark Palm sect to these lower clans, but now it was replaced by the Zhangs.

In this city, there were three other powers. There was the Xing Clan they were mostly involved in the more shady businesses having stakes in the pleasure district and the gambling spots around it. Then there was the Kuan Clan they were responsible for the food supply and the farming areas around the city, they would go to the village areas and transport the rice and wheat while taxing the farmers. The last were the people from the Situ Clan, they had a monopoly on the medicine in the area most of the clinics and apothecaries belonged to them.

The three factions kept themselves at bay, but if they ever worked together then they could have been able to compete with the Cheng Clan. That clan in question was focused on strength, so they didn't really need to spread themselves thin with many establishments. They collected taxes from the lower three clans and protected them in response, acting like the military of the city. So they were more like a mafia family that was collecting protection money while running some shady businesses on the side.

But now there was a new tiger in town, the old families used to work with the old Zhang Clan but that family didn't really exist anymore. The new Patriarch was making things clear after one of the businesses owned by the Xing Clan was raided. It was the place old fatty Mu was the owner of, they didn't even come to the Xing Clan to work things out before going into action.

In a certain secluded place, there were three men sitting around a round table. They were looking at the map of Moonlight City, some red marks drawn on it, one in the spot of the slave trader Old Fatty Mu.

"What are they thinking, are they trying to squeeze my Xing Clan for spirit stones?"

Xing Deng the Xing Clan Patriarch spoke up, his fist slamming onto the table while his brows quivered in anger. The people sitting at the table were the Kuan and Situ Clan Patriarchs, the three had called an emergency meeting after the leading family was taken down. They didn't like each other, but when their livelihood was being taken away they would work together.

"My people reported that they want to give free medicine to those useless commoners, preposterous!"

This was the Situ Clan Patriarch named Situ Rong who earned his living by overpricing all medicine that his businesses made, if some renegade pill maker popped up in the city he would be either recruited under this family or removed from the city.

"Damn Zhangs, they want to lower the taxes on the blasted farmers as well and they want to reexamine the quality of the food we produce!"

This was the Patriarch of the third family Kuan Yin, he was also angered. The taxes would be lowered and his family might even have to pay fines if the food didn't meet the Zhang Clan's standards.

"This is just blatant bullying!"

"We must make a decision brothers... do we lose face or do we strike back..."

Xing Deng asked while leaning back, in his mouth was a large cigar and he looked more like a mafia boss than a cultivator. He was the most ruthless from the bunch, he had no qualm in using people as slaves or selling them off for body parts.

"Brother Deng speaks wise words, but I don't think we can fight this clan openly... their Patriarch is just too powerful, he easily defeated Tsai Fang."

Situ Rong spoke up, the man looking like a middle-aged man with the top of his head balding but with some hair on the side.

"But we got word that he was injured after they returned from that secret ground, the state of his cultivation is unknown and he rarely leaves Spirit Spring City."

Kuan Yin chimed in, he was holding a fan covering part of his face he looked the oldest with an unhealthy skin complexion and sunspots. All of them were cultivators in the great circle of foundation establishment. None of them had a core formation expert in their family, but even those kinds of experts could be bought out.

"I say we wait it out, for now, no reason to stick our heads out just yet. Maybe the Zhang Clan will come around, it might be some scheme we don't know about."

Said Situ Rong while looking at the town map, hoping that he was right.

"If they still don't change their minds, then we could hire someone to take care of their Patriarch... I bet if we combine our resources we could hire a powerful expert, I think Brother Deng should have someone in mind?"

Kuan Yin asked while looking in Xin Deng's direction.

"Hm, you speak wise words. It's too soon to act and yes there was a strong expert making a name for himself, he even slew some beasts that were at the very top of the food chain. If I remember correctly... this expert goes by the name of... Lei Yinglo!"

"Oh, that esteemed Senior! I've heard of his tales, he has made a name for himself by slaughtering demonic cultivators and beasts alike... but he won't be cheap."

"Yes, we might have to empty our coffers out, but if there isn't any other possibility..."

"That Patriarch is just a little brat if he doesn't give us any face, then we don't have to give him any either!"

The three Clan Patriarch's chuckled while looking at each other, Xin Deng sticking a dagger in the place that the old Cheng Clan villa was situated and now belonged to the Zhangs. They chatted for a bit more, talking about business-related things while they sealed the deal on their pact. They would wait it out, for now, while gathering information on the new enemy. They weren't against a peaceful solution, but that depended on their bottom line and if the Zhang Clan crossed it or not.

While the three Patriarchs were being their villainous selves an old man was walking down the street. He looked to be in his sixties or seventies with a long white beard, his physique was a bit wide making him look like he worked out at the gym a lot but his baggy robe hid that fact quite well.

The man stopped at a new Apothecary shop that was also used as a clinic. He looked at the blue-robed men and women bringing in various items into the new shop, not even noticing the elderly man that was standing there. He coughed into his hand a bit to get their attention, one of the younger girls finally noticing him as she approached.

"Greetings, how can I help you, Sir?"

The girl asked while looking at the old fart, the man's face was all wrinkled up but he looked quite friendly.

"Ah yes, my name is Wei Hung. I think you should have been informed about me, little missus?"

The man smiled while moving his hands behind his back, hunching forward slightly. The female Zhang member thought for a second and then a lightbulb appeared above her head.

"Ah yes Senior, come come, we have been waiting for you!"

She quickly run into the shop and clapped her hands together so that everyone would turn their heads towards the elder and her, then she spoke out.

"Everyone, this is elder Wei Hung, he will be working as the physician in this shop from now!"

This man had been hired to be the main physician and pill maker of this new free clinic. He would take care of the hard cases that the normal pills or elixirs couldn't cure. From what the younger Zhang members knew, this man was an experienced doctor that was recruited for this job by the Zhang Elders, but in reality, he was their Patriarch in disguise!

Matt knew that being too well known wasn't such a good thing, if he tried walking through the streets of cities or land that he owned he would receive the dogeza treatment. People would line up and clear a path, their faces squished into the ground fearing his wrath. This was also the reason that he used the holograms wanting to appear friendly and approachable.

Still, he knew that he couldn't just go out and do his thing anymore, he had a certain status to uphold. This is where his disguise technique would come into play. He had improved upon it quite a bit, it now being able to mask his aura as well. He wouldn't be recognized by anyone below the nascent soul level, even those would have problems in seeing through it in certain situations.

Why would he disguise himself you might ask. Well, he wanted to improve the happiness of the people in the cities that he owned, but he couldn't just do that as himself. It would seem strange if the Zhang Clan Patriarch just appeared out of nowhere and started teaching people basic skills or healing them with his pills and healing arts.

The situation of this city was tragic, he was even losing points from the way this city was run now. He just bought a diseased animal and was supposed to heal it while parasites still festered in it. They might have gotten rid of the main culprit which was the Cheng Clan, but there were still more people fashioned from the same cloth.

He wanted to pretend to be a lower level cultivator, seaming to be at the foundation establishment middle level. No one would suspect that an old doctor was the Zhang Patriarch in disguise. He could slowly scope out the area and gain some knowledge while also helping the sick and poor out in the process.

A note from Kuropon

Join the Patreon for some more Chapters https://www.patreon.com/kuropon

Also, join the discord https://discord.gg/fWefdgn

Chapter 108

Matt moved into the building, it was quite large and had more than one level. There was enough space to bring in multiple patients if the need arose. The shop had a bit of a different look than the other establishments around the area, sticking out due to the large glass door that slid apart when someone stood at the entrance.

This was something Matt made in his free time, wasn't all that hard just required a pressure plate and some technical knowledge that he now had. The electricity for things like that could easily be replaced by spiritual energy and it didn't really take much out from a lower graded spirit stone to run those doors for multiple months on end.

After you went through the sliding door and heard a chime you could see a large reception area, a cute lady was sitting there also hired by the Zhang Clan as they didn't really have many family cultivators to spare for tasks like these. There were a couple of junior members in here though and guards but no one really strong.

They didn't really think anyone would attack their shop in here, Zhang Zhi would be stationed in this city for now acting as the de facto governor. His lovely buff wife and their child would be joining them soon, the man was a bit apprehensive about this mostly due to not wanting to be separated from his man crush that was the Patriarch.

Next to the reception area was the waiting area, there were a couple of long benches next to the walls for people to sit in but also a wider area with some tables where they could enjoy some tea while they waited for their order.

There was a little window in which some apothecary workers were inside, they would be responsible for selling pills and elixirs. There wasn't anything like a need for prescriptions in this world, anyone could just say which pills they wanted and if they had the money for it they would buy it. But, physicians still gave them out to people that didn't know what they needed as a service.

The way things worked in her were similar to modern times. People would go take a plaque with a number on it and then the lady at the desk would call it out, signaling that they were next in line. This was also why the small tea area existed so people could nicely spend their waiting time. Matt would like to have a digital counter and something that just automatically printed your spot in the line, but for now, this would have to do.

There were some stairs to the side, they leading up to the second level of the building and into the physician corner of the clinic. There were more waiting areas there, beds all around and some lovely ladies dressed in white Chinese styled robes and nurse hats on their heads, also forced upon them by the Patriarch's peculiar tastes.

He would be stationed on this level, he had his own room with a bed to the side where he could treat patients one by one. There was also an open area with many beds outside, making it look like one of those military hospitals with just some drapes separating the patients.

"Yaaawwwnnn..."

Matt was sitting in his chair, slumping forward a bit. A crooked posture was one of his special abilities, this he managed to bring over from his old gaming days. So he was sure that no one would see through his elderly man disguise.

'Sure is quiet around here, no one showed up. Did that news lady deliver the message correctly?'

Matt expected the sick people to claw their way in, demanding free healthcare as they did back in his earthly days. The waiting lines in his home country were always so damn long and you had to wait for hours to receive your checkup. But here, there was no one there. Everyone was just lazing around now, all the items and resources were already moved inside.

'Maybe the news needs to spread further, or we need to send someone to advertise in the streets.'

He rubbed his beard, thanks to the disguise art he could grow it out quite nicely. He even had a nice fu manchu mustache to go with his beard.

'Well, I guess I'll go make some pills if I don't have anything to do now.'

There was another reason for making this shop, his pill concocting was lagging behind his crafting skills quite a bit. He only needed some items to and he could create a heaven grade item, that he could absorb to push his body into the nascent soul. He had worked his actual crafting skills to the very top of core formation he just lacked the necessary resources to go further.

'Yeah, those sect bastards really double down on anything related to heaven grade materials.'

It was ill-advised to create items in the nascent soul stage, whenever a practitioner fashioned an item of that level a peculiar aura would be produced. This aura could be felt by the nearby cultivators by miles upon miles, you would have sect uncles knocking on your door demanding you to cough the item up for some chump change in no time.

'Those sects sure are scared about their position aren't they?'

The same thing would happen if a person reached the nascent soul stage and was discovered. The only option for someone like that was either to run from the leading sect in the area or have enough backing to fight them off. If you were a renegade cultivator or came from a weak family, you would be chased down. Either killed by the sect uncles or recruited by them and closely watched, have some slave-like contracts forced upon you while they slowly brought you over to their side, one way or the other.

He was somehow able to make lower graded earth pills at the moment, but even this feat was something that would make him into a master pill maker in this world. Anything that reached to the earth realm would be considered a treasure, the families would fight each other to get their hands on a pill of that grading.

There was a logical explanation as to why, a low-grade earth pill was able to help someone reach the core formation early stage. This was enough for a weaker clan to be able to duke it out with the big boys, the Cheng Clan was in that category having spent quite a fortune for a pill like that which allowed their Patriarch to finally reach the core formation-level before the other three families in the area.

This was also how Zhang Zhi managed to burst through his bottleneck. Matt managed to create a pill that pushed him into the core formation stage and that didn't have that many side effects. But this caused the already nutty junior of his, to worship him even more.

Wei Hung smiled at the bowing clinic workers as he headed out from his office, he looked around the empty rooms no patients coming in at all. But he wasn't that surprised, he knew that people were naturally suspicious and untrusting in this world. Even more in this kind of town where you might be robbed in broad daylight. He already knew that his small police force was having trouble in keeping up with the reports, there was just too much shady stuff happening around here.

There was a cellar into which he headed, this was a designated brewing room for him. No one would bother him here even if someone was on death's door as cultivators were really serious about their pill making. They were quite afraid to anger a pill making master during his or her work.

'Well... let me get to work...'

He looked at the items spread out here and smirked, he wouldn't actually be using these second-hand goods for his work. He had his crafting fortress for that and a designated brewing and pill forging area in there. This crafting abode had somehow integrated itself into his system, he could upgrade it even without having to buy the next version at the cash shop like before.

He closed the door behind him and put up the sign that he shouldn't be disturbed. He then closed his eyes, his body began to glow slightly and then vanished from the spot he was standing in. Matt appeared in the center of his crafting abode, the air around here was surprisingly refreshing. He had a similar copying device for his pills, but it wasn't as upgraded as the one that he used for weapon crafting. Each crafting related profession required a different one which really pained him when he had to spread his crafting points out.

'Hope it won't blow up in my face like last time...'

Crafting pills required a pill furnace, they came in various shapes and sizes. The one that he had in this room was a green jade-looking one. It was standing on three legs and had an oval shape. It had the yin and yang symbol on it from four sides and a lid with which you could close it. If you wanted to make elixirs, you needed a cauldron instead. He had one of similar quality in another part of this room, it was quite large and golden.

"What should I practice on today... think the people would really love more of those Core establishing pills."

He had made a Water Core Founding Pill for Zhang Zhi, but he went through quite a bit of exploding furnaces. The things liked to burst open and hit his face whenever the temperature was off. It was even harder to fashion this pill as it had the greater Dao of Water truths inside of it, it would be a lot easier to make one that gave a cultivator a lesser Dao core instead.

'Good that it worked, but it was probably more due to the superior cultivation manual...'

He had upgraded Zhang Zhi's cultivation method, thanks to the library from that secret ground Matt could combine the heaven graded manuals with the ones that his clan members used and derive better cultivation methods. This was also another feature of the new system, well more of this crafting abode that had a library section a certain magical item with which you could combine texts.

It didn't look like much, it looked like a desk with many smaller drawers in it. You put the text in there and then a popup window would appear in front of the contraption. You could spend points to combine the two techniques, add more so that the grade would improve. The costs were decreased if you put in a lower graded item and a higher graded item to receive a middle graded one from the combination.

For instance, if you grabbed a mortal grade Zhang Clan staple technique and popped a heaven graded one into the drawer. The system would show you if the techniques were compatible, and if they were you could cheaply receive an earth graded manual from it. You even could play around with the settings, letting the system improve the attacking potential or defensive potential of the skill. The inserted books would be lost in the process, but for Matt, that wasn't a problem as he could write them all down again anyway.

'Come to think of it, that feels a bit like cheating... but not my fault that they left so many techniques back there.'

This worked only to a certain point, it depended on how good the best technique that he had for combining was and if it vibed well with the other technique manuals in the mix. From what Matt understood the system checked if there were faults in the techniques in reference to the other ones used in the process. So if he threw in hundreds of similar technique manuals, the system should work out some kinks and he would receive an improved version. But there was also a margin of error and he could receive an utterly trashy technique, that would kill you the moment you tried cultivating in it.

Matt was now sitting opposite his pill furnace, some herbs already in it as he heated up the crafting utensil with his Qi. The purer your spiritual energy was, the better your crafted pills came out and Matt had one of the best Qi purities around. The various herbs and spices circled around the pill furnace, jumping into it while the cultivator focused. He was past the stage in which he had to insert items by hand, his mind doing all the work while he focused.

'Keep the temperature stead... now comes the chilling star mushroom... d-damn added it too soon... need to add the inferno spirit grass to counter its effects now...'

You could see the sweat running down his forehead, one of his hands touching the furnace while the other was pointing at the circling herbs above the furnace. Soon it started rumbling which made the young pill maker's brows quiver, he inserted more Qi into the furnace trying to slow down the explosive chemical reaction that was taking place but to no avail. The lid suddenly popped upwards and black goo shot out in all directions, Matt's face all black and his clothes ruined and stinky.

"God damn it!"

He looked at the mess in this room, he would have to either clean it by hand or spend his crafting points on it. This new system was truly without mercy for its current owner.

'Should I make some low graded elixirs to gain some crafting points... or clean it myself...'

While the elderly man was focusing on scrubbing the stinky black residue from his pill furnace, someone burst through the sliding doors of the clinic. Some time had passed since it was opened and it was now closing hour, but the screeching woman rushed in while holding a little boy in her hands.

"Please save my child, I have nowhere else to go!"

A note from Kuropon

Join the Patreon for some more Chapters https://www.patreon.com/kuropon

Also, join the discord https://discord.gg/fWefdgn

Chapter 109

It was close to closing hours and the elder that was responsible for the clinic was still down in the basement concocting pills, or so the workers that were working thought. The people that were gathered here were mostly hired help or regular cultivators, they didn't develop a more lenient mindset just yet.

Zhang Dong had ordered to help the people of this city and offer them service, but these two looked like beggars. The Patriarch didn't realize that he worded his order in the wrong way. The workers thought that 'People of this city' was about the actual citizens that paid taxes, if they saw a beggar they would shoo them away.

"Please, this is a clinic, right? Is there a doctor around?"

The woman wasn't someone that the news about the Zhang Clan had reached, she just noticed the extravagant health clinic sign outside. All the apothecary shops and other establishments for healing that were owned by the Situ Clan had already turned her down. They would never aid someone that wouldn't be able to pay those exorbitant prices that they charged.

"I beg you, save my little Zhu'er."

The people looked at each other and then to the mother, she was holding a 10 or 11-year-old child in her hands, the youth looked like he was trashed by someone. This wasn't rare around these parts, if you bumped into some people without begging for their forgiveness it wasn't strange to be beaten up to the brink of your life.

"We are sorry the doctor is busy now, come back tomorrow..."

One of the male workers replied while looking to the side, his gaze to the stairs going down to the basement where Wei Hung headed too. He was afraid that the old man might beat them up if they bothered him with two beggars like this. He really didn't want to earn a caning by some old grandpa, he had gotten enough beatings by his own elders so he was adamant about reporting this to the man in charge. Those pill makers were a strange bunch, their furnaces would explode and they would blame it on the workers being too loud which broke their concentration.

'No way I'm dragging that old grandpa up here, he looked ferocious.'

In Matt's mind he was playing the role of a sympathetic old grandpa, but in reality, whenever he smiled his face would contort in strange ways making the people feel uncomfortable around him. They wouldn't say a thing though, everyone knew at least one grumpy old elder in their life and knew well how to evade their wrath.

"Yes, yes the old master is busy making pills, please leave if you can't pay for healing pills or elixirs..."

The woman only had a couple of copper coins on her, the rest were the torn up clothes. The child that she was holding was the only family that she had, her husband having been sold off as a slave after he gambled their money away in the casinos of Moonlight City. She was too old to be a working lady and had trouble finding a job only doing odd jobs.

Times were tough though and the people were cruel, even when she cleaned and cooked for them they would only leave scraps and underpay her tremendously. Sometimes they would even throw her out without anything after her slaving away for a whole day, cooking and cleaning. Her boy was a little troublemaker too, always getting in trouble and making his poor mom worry.

Due to the mother working all day the youth went unsupervised. One thing led to another and he joined the local street urchins that moved around the city stealing food and small change. Most of the time they managed to get away, the young kids far too agile and used to the backstreets to get apprehended. This time they weren't so lucky, one of the older kids tried his pickpocketing skills on the wrong person that noticed it. Little Zhu was there keeping the pickpocketing target busy, but when the urchins tried running they got caught and were taught a tough lesson.

The youth managed to drag his beaten body in front of the shack he and his mother were living, the woman shocked when she returned after a hard day of work. She had nowhere to go, her head down on the ground in front of the workers. There was no one in this blasted city that would do anything for free, it was always money. Her eyes were tearing up, she didn't want to lose her only son that was the only thing that she had left in this world.

"Please I implore you..."

"Shoo, This clinic belongs to the great Zhang Clan, they don't do business with moochers like you, now shoo!"

In the worker's minds, they were doing the right thing. They couldn't let other people see some beggars and vagabonds in this new clinic, they were far too afraid of the Zhang Clan elders coming and reprimanding them for it. While the man in front was thinking that the woman started getting frantic, grabbing his leg and pulling on his pants.

"Hey, get off me!"

He was about to kick the woman away, his foot moving backward for the windup but as his foot was flying forward someone grabbed it. He started seeing things upside down as the person that was grasping him by the ankle lifted him up into the air. He soon could see the lower areas of the robe that Wei Hung was wearing, the grandpa having caught his kick mid-strike.

"What are you fools doing?"

The man looked at the worker that he was holding with a raised brow, he had come out of his basement-dwelling, disgruntled after having to clean up the mess that he made. He then heard some screaming and noticed the crying woman on the floor grasping one of the hired helpers. What were these people doing, weren't they supposed to help the injured people instead of injuring them themselves?

"Ahh... s-sir... these beggars just showed up, but don't worry we will remove them from this esteemed clinic in a moment."

Wei Hung's face started deforming the moment he heard them call the people beggars and that they were going to kick them out. He even noticed the beaten-up child, bruises and cuts all over his body the weeping woman just there not knowing what to do.

"You damn buffon, who told you to remove them, huh? You are supposed to help everyone and I mean EVERYONE!"

The worker was flung against the wall after the enraged elderly man chucked him to the side, not caring if he was okay or not. He then looked at the nursing staff that had conflicting expressions on their faces, not really sure what was going on.

"You and you, bring the boy up to the second level and wash his body with the cleansed spirit water, I will be there in the moment!... Well, DON'T JUST STAND THERE WITH YOUR MOUTHS WIDE OPEN, MOVE!"

The elder's scream made everyone flinch and scatter to work, the boy was snatched and carried off to the second level the mother quickly following after the workers while bowing at the older man that just showed up.

'Damn savages...'

Matt cursed inwardly, not knowing that even the people from his clan and the workers they hired would be this cruel. It was even a woman with a beaten-up child, how could people show so little compassion. He just couldn't understand it, his brows were furrowed and his teeth clenching up he would have to investigate this later, for now, the boy was more important.

Matt slapped his cheeks and went upstairs, blaming himself for the transgression that transpired here. The mother was to the side as the Nurses carried him to one of the empty beds in the larger rooms and started cleaning his body from the blood, grime, and sweat. The special water that they were using was something the Zhang Clan was known for, it had some weak healing and regenerative abilities and was good at disinfecting wounds to boot.

The mother looked at the old looking man, he looked to be the doctor. He was a bit scary but was apparently willing to help her child, she wasn't sure if there was an ulterior motive behind this, but she would give her life for her son if she had too.

"Please sir, help my little boy."

She pleaded, the man just looked at her while going over. He placed his palm on the woman's shoulder, the woman experiencing a peculiar feeling when he did that. She could feel warm energy flowing into her body making her worries fly away as she felt really calm. She wobbled to the side where she was guided to the bench by one of the nurses, the man moved over to the boy that was on the table with only his groin area covered by a white cloth.

Wei Hung took out a bunch of needles that were used for acupuncture, they were pure gold and looked quite costly. The nursing staff's eyes went wide after seeing them, quickly being able to distinguish the item's price. The man opened up his palm the needles started hovering up in the air which made everyone's eyes bulge out even more as they had never seen a physician work in such a fashion before.

'This Wei Hung isn't simple... he must be a master!'

They thought to themselves while gasping, the metallic items hovered around the boy's body as they homed in on the desired acupuncture points. They were slowly lowered into his body, the man just waving his finger around while his other hand was held behind his back as he performed the strange procedure.

The people then saw the golden needles radiating golden light, the spiritual energy filling out the room and making everyone gasp some more. This was the holy element type spiritual Qi that Matt was now proficient in, the energy was slowly infused into the boy's body his complexion quickly getting better and better as you could see his many wounds closing at a rapid pace.

The people couldn't believe it, what was this strange technique that this elder was showing them. The young boy was getting healed at a rapid pace as if he drunk some kind of high-quality healing elixir. They looked at this elder that was concentrating, not knowing how he ended up in this small clinic his skills were better off getting used by some kind of great sect.

The needles soon hovered away from the boy's body, the procedure ending rather quickly after the divine healing energies were distributed throughout the youth's body. Matt could use a couple of healing techniques by now, but this one was the best one as he could directly insert the healing energies into the patient's body through the acupuncture needles. This increased the speed of the process and was a lot better for people with internal injuries, this technique could even heal up some plugged up meridians.

"He will be fine now."

The old man stroked his beard while turning to the bewildered people that were staring at him as if he was some rare creature.

"Also, all of you lot report to my office, I must have a word with you..."

The nurses snapped out of their trance and looked at the man, his face was contorted and he was clearly mad. They knew that they were in for a beating or at least an earful.

"Don't forget to drag that one fool over too, slap him awake if he is still passed out, hmph!"

He was going to give those idiots a good lecture, maybe even cut their pay for the week for this transgression. He wanted to show the goodwill of his Zhang Clan, show them how different they were from the other clans, but this was the result. Crying mothers and beaten children getting refused treatment.

"Well...get moving, you buffoons, or I'll dock your pay for the entire month!"

"Oh no sir, show mercy!"

The poor workers shuffled down and dragged the passed out man, dumping water over his face and smacking his cheeks till he woke up. Then they quickly rushed to Wei Hung's office, they could take a beating, they could take getting called idiots and clowns, but they certainly couldn't take not being paid.

A note from Kuropon

Join the Patreon for some more Chapters https://www.patreon.com/kuropon

Also, join the discord https://discord.gg/fWefdgn

Chapter 110

Matt looked at the child, it was covered up with a blanket and no more in critical condition. He wasn't sure what kind of person would beat up an 11-year old like that, but he would certainly like to have a word with them. For now, he left then walked over to the mother, that was a bit out of it after he calmed her down with his technique.

"The boy will be fine, he just needs to rest. He should wake up soon."

The woman snapped out of it and looked at her boy, then to the scary-looking older man. She dropped down to her hands and knees, doing the usual head bobbing maneuver that made Matt uncomfortable, he could never get used to how quick these people went down to their knees.

"Thank you, Senior, how can I repay you... I don't have anything to repay you with, I can be your slave, I'll do anything... even..."

The grandpa in question moved back slightly after hearing the woman wanted to become his slave and even wanting to do extra services.

"What? girly what are you even on about. This was free treatment, I don't need any slaves."

He turned around, still trying to keep his elder persona up. He swished his sleeves and moved so that she could only see the back on his head.

"Haven't you heard, the generous and magnanimous Zhang Clan is offering treatment free of charge, they are truly a virtuous family. If you want to be grateful to anyone, be grateful to them. I also heard that they are accepting children from broken homes into a special school, your child has some cultivation aptitude, you should go ask about it... and stop bowing your head already..."

The woman didn't look at him, just hanging her head down as if he would poke her eyes out if she dared to look at his face. But she soon moved her gaze upwards as the elder started talking about a special school and that everything here was free.

"M-my son has potential?"

"Ah yes, with the right schooling he shouldn't really have trouble in reaching the foundation establishment realm."

He checked the youth's potential, it wasn't anything great just a C. But this was enough and slightly above average from what he could tell. Most people had potentials in the F - C range, with F being quite rare and people with that having zero aptitudes for cultivation. Though an 'F' aptitude also showed up if people had some illnesses like blocked meridians that didn't allow for cultivation.

The 'C' potential was the top one an average person could have, 'C+' was the start for gifted people this would be the start of the gifted tear. 'S' was the most you could have, the largest potential that Matt had ever come across was the one his two disciples had being at a 'B+'. So this kid was top at the average mark, which wasn't bad at all.

"F-foundation establishment?"

The woman got dizzy, her child wasn't even at the first level of Qi condensation the family not having any cultivation manuals at all. Though people reached that level naturally in their older teen years even without any manuals just by passively absorbing the rich Qi in the surroundings.

"Ah yes, he'll probably reach the first level of Qi Condensation soon, maybe even the second level, his body absorbed a lot of my healing energies, guess you could call that a side effect..."

The woman gasped once more, there were a couple of the workers listening to the conversation from the side as they gathered waiting for their punishment.

'Side effect my ass, this is a big scoop!'

The workers started to think, that maybe it wouldn't be such a bad idea to go into some alleys and get themselves trashed by some hooligans. When the elder healed them afterward, maybe they could get through their cultivation bottlenecks.

"But I need to get some things done, just stay with your son he should wake up soon."

He walked back to his office, glaring at the workers from a side profile which made them get goosebumps. It was time to punish the infidels, he needed to show how things were run here and explain to them that they couldn't just leave injured people outside in the cold.

"Everyone into my office!"

He walked in first, hunched over slightly and with his hands behind his back. He was getting used to acting like an old geezer, it was kind of fun he could have temper tantrums and the people just thought it was normal. He waited for them to enter his large office, there was enough room for everybody to sit down in a heel sitting position.

Everyone was nervous, they had their back straight and knees tightly pressed while sitting down in this uncomfortable position. Their boss was sitting at his desk, just sipping on his tea while everyone was quiet and afraid to mutter a word. Finally, he placed the teacup to the side and spoke up, his voice stern and domineering.

"Do you know what you did wrong?"

The people looked at each other, no one really wanted to speak up but someone had to, one worker finally mustered up some courage as he answered.

"W-we didn't follow orders and caused the Elder to lose face?"

Wei Hung's face twitched a bit after he heard that reply, the people in the room not sure if that was the right answer but it seemed logical. The Elder and Zhang Clan wanted to look magnanimous for some reason, so if the Seniors came to that decision it would be a loss of face if their juniors didn't follow through on that order. They didn't realize that the answer that this man was looking for, was a lot simpler and he just wanted them to show some compassion.

"Ho ho? So, it was all about me losing face now, is it..."

The man rubbed his long white beard and glared at the people in the room. From his reaction, the workers knew that something was off.

"Damn you people, show some empathy once in a while! This isn't about saving or losing face you fools!"

A teacup was flung at the wall, whizzing past the man's face that did the reply, the tea leaves and the residual water in the cup making a mess on the wall.

"Please Elder Hung, appease your rage, we were in the wrong, it won't happen again."

The members pleaded while bowing down again.

"You're damn right it won't! But that's not the point, you lot better listen well now. Helping people that have nothing isn't wrong, showing compassion to strangers once in a while isn't either. You must lose that backward mindset of yours, this is not how the Zhang Clan or this clinic operates!"

He soon started lecturing them about the virtues of life, words like 'sympathy', 'kindness', 'mercy' were just some that he threw out at them trying to make them understand his point of view and that it wasn't a weakness to being a good person. But he wasn't sure that he was getting through to these people, that just bobbled their heads at him, their expressions mixed.

"And another thing, don't be afraid to call for me, there is a little button to the side of the door of the room I do my pill concocting. If you press it I will know that you need me and I will arrive shortly, you will not be punished."

He tried a couple of angles, presenting them with hypothetical scenarios.

"How would you feel if your family got annihilated in some useless squabble about face and there was no one that helped you out. You could only die outside in the cold or get devoured by beasts, no one willing to give you a helping hand. How would you feel then, try putting yourselves in their shoes once in a while."

"You might not know this, but the Dao of compassion is a powerful one!"

He wasn't lying, you had to be compassionate for the holy elemental energies to actually work. That's why you mostly saw only people like priests and nuns using the holy healing arts, you had to have a vitreous hart for it.

"Behold!"

His finger glowed with a golden light, the area filling with comfortable holy energies that made everyone in the room feel at peace. They could feel their fatigue receding as they were gaining their stamina back.

"Maybe if you show some warmth to your fellow people, you might awaken this power too..."

He left them with something to think about, maybe if the words didn't get to them. The show of an unknown Dao would, their eyes went wide as saucers the moment his finger started glowing. He would be happier if they realized that being nice to your fellow man wasn't so bad. But if he could get them with the show of future gains, it would have to do for now.

'This will be a long process... I spend to much time crafting for these past years. Thought these people were getting better, but not much has changed.'

"You can leave now, hope you learned something."

The workers slowly walked out in an orderly fashion, seaming quite confused about what they had heard. Matt in his Wei Hung disguise just slumped into his chair, his hand going to his face as he did a normal facepalm gesture.

'Ahh... that was stressful... but I've gotten better at things like this now...'

He didn't suffer from stage fright as much recently, his fear of conversation had mostly gone away by now. He wasn't sure if he just got used to talking to people or if it was the Tranquil technique at play. It being quite a quality of life one, the more he used the calmer he got and the less outside factors could affect his calm demeanor.

'I miss the old cash shop... most of the techniques I got from that library aren't as good and I can't even get points from slaying monsters.'

He didn't feel as motivated to battle other people or monsters since his system had changed. He could still get cores to absorb but those items were better used as crafting materials for armor or weapons, most of the beast he hunted were demonic ones that were bothering the people around the area that he owned. This also adding more daily point gains that were added to his system as his people felt safer.

'Ah, I forgot to get one of the workers to clean the wall...'

He looked at the shattered teacup and the tea leaves on the ground that scattered into all directions after it shattered. His grumpy old man act had gone well, the people sure were afraid of him. He raised his posterior from the chair he was sitting on and went out, the moment he stuck his head out to see if one of the nurses was around he heard someone shouting loudly.

"No, you mustn't. Zhu'er you've just gotten better, you must rest."

"Let go of me mother, you don't understand, I need to go back... The others..."

Matt raised a brow as he could see the boy squirming around in his mother's grasp. He was trying to move down the bed but the woman was clinging to him tightly. The boy obviously didn't want to hurt his mom so he only tried to push her away, but the woman wasn't having any of it.

"No! Do you know how much your poor mother went through, you can't go!"

"But the others, they are in danger... those cultivators are going to kill them!"

The boy was a bit frantic, still a bit weak as the holy healing art wasn't perfect just yet. It seemed that the men that had beaten him out would be heading to the urchin's hideout, the boy heard them talk while they were giving him the beatdown. He wasn't sure how they would track them down, but they apparently had some kind of tracking treasure with them and wanted to punish the little thieves. He was lucky enough to have played dead and them just kicking him to the side, then he barely made it back home and finally woke up in this clinic.

"Oh? Who is going to kill who now? Could you explain?"

The family of two stopped squirming and looked to the voice, it was the large elderly uncle that had healed the boy. He was standing there while stroking his beard, wondering what this was all about.

A note from Kuropon

Finally did my forward chapters, the free releases will be coming out with the Patreon ones.

Join the Patreon for some more Chapters https://www.patreon.com/kuropon

Also, join the discord https://discord.gg/fWefdgn

Chapter 111

Matt looked at the mother and son duo, were they doing some kind of comedic routine?

The boy was still almost naked, at least they didn't remove his underwear before the procedure. The youth in question looked at the old man beside the bed he was getting bear-hugged by his mother. He instantly knew that this man wasn't simple, his disposition and sharp stare could only be attributed to experts. But in reality, it was only Matt squinting and trying to keep his elder act together.

"P-please... my friends are going to die... we offended someone that we shouldn't have..."

The boy replied to the question, his voice trailing off at the end.

"Oh, who did you offend? Could you tell this friendly grandpa?"

The workers faces contorted at the 'friendly' part, who was the person that threw that one worker at the wall. The poor guy then was slapped awake only to get lectured and then only get teacups thrown at him.

"Ah, bow your head boy, this Senior Uncle saved your life!"

The woman immediately pushed her son's head down, making him bow to the man. The man in question just moved his hand upwards trying to signal to the two that this act was unnecessary.

"That's fine, just doing what I was hired for by the Zhang Clan. I'm not sure if you have heard about the Zhang Clan, but they are quite the magnanimous people, yes they are."

He made it sure to mention the clan whenever he could, he liked to spread awareness, branding was very important. They weren't sure why this elder was mentioning that clan every other sentence, but not like they could ask him. The boy had some tears in his eyes which he was able to wipe after his mother finally let him be, soon he started talking and told the two the full story.

"Me and my brothers just wanted some coin for the little ones... the young master came out of the restaurant and he was already drunk so we thought he would be an easy snatch..."

The boy looked at his mom, not really wanting to tell her that he was out in the streets and stealing. But he was doing it mostly for the younger children, they had even some four-year-olds in his group. They weren't abandoned but their parents died one way or the other, mostly offending some bigshots or getting in debt with the wrong people. He looked to his mother stuttering a bit as he saw her brows twitching.

"A-anyway, we tried doing the usual routine... I fell in front of the young master and just started apologizing to keep his attention on me... that was when big bro..."

Matt stroked his beard while listening, it was a regular stealing maneuver that you would see anywhere. Someone would bump into you then start talking loudly and shuffling about. While you were distracted their partner would move in from the back and quickly snatch your wallet or purse from your pocket.

"But you got caught, right?"

Said Wei Hung while glancing at the boy that lowered his head at the reply.

"Y-yes, the guard next to the master was very vigilant he moved between the young master as my big bro was reaching into his robe. Luckily he managed to jump back before he got caught."

"So, they grabbed you instead?"

"Y-yes sir, I was on the ground bowing so I didn't have enough time..."

"That's why I told you not to hang out with those brats!"

The mother was fuming, she had told her son not to hang out with that riff raff. They were a known band of little bandits that robbed and plundered the streets. She didn't want her only child ending up as those thieves, this was also the reason she was working so hard.

"I'm sure the boy had his reasons... right?"

The elderly man asked while trying to smile, but made the family duo flinch in fright instead.

"Y-yes! We only did it to feed the young ones!"

Matt went back to stroking his beard while the mom started reprimanding her son for being a little thief. He, on the other hand, was worried that they even had children on the streets below the age of five running around with no parents or supervision. Even more that they had to resort to stealing and burglary to survive.

"And another thing!"

The mom shouted out while smacking the head of her sun that looked disgruntled.

"Hm, how about you show this grandpa where those children are? I'm sure I can 'talk' that young master out of harming them..."

He couldn't let some young bratty young lord just beat up some pre-teen kids, he knew that those types would even resort to killing if they got offended enough. He stood up a bit straighter and tried striking a valiant pose complete with a bright smile so that the child would trust in this old uncle, but the only thing the kid saw was an old man grinning menacingly.

"Um..."

He looked to the side to his mother, not sure if he could trust this ominous looking elder. The mother looking between the two and finally speaking out.

"Y-yes... uh... if Senior insists Zhu'er will show you where they are...isn't that right?"

She looked at the young boy, a bit of worry in her eyes. She was grateful for the help that this man had given her son, but she didn't want him to involve himself further with those band of urchins. Her motherly instincts were telling her to take her son and run, but she couldn't offend the elder man that helped them out, he also seemed quite powerful.

"Well, let's not dilly dally for too long, little one, if we don't hurry your friends might get hurt."

The youth instantly steeled his resolve as the old man mention his friends getting in trouble. He quickly jumped up, his mother shaking her head as she could oppose the older man's decision.

"E-elder please take me along!"

She asked out while her boy was already close to bolting down the stairs.

"Ah sure, you can come along, don't see a problem with that."

Matt didn't mind if the mom tagged along, not like she needed to do anything and he felt confident in being able to protect the two of them. He also thought of alerting his new police task force for this job, but he knew that they were spread thin. Also, it would probably take them a while to get to this store, then take the kid out for the search. He was worried that the younglings might already be getting beaten up.

"Follow me, I know all the shortcuts!"

The little guy bolted for the sliding door, Matt just skipping along even though he didn't look like he was going fast and his feet were moving slowly he had no problem in keeping up with the energetic child, the mom was trailing a bit in the back though. He went deep into the neighborhood, the buildings started looking worse and worse.

'Man, this sure is a shit hole...'

He could see beggars supporting themselves against some building walls, their bodies dangerously thin. The buildings looked more like storage sheds after a while, the roofs probably leaking and if a storm came along they would be folded in half.

'Think I need to invest some money into renovating this section of town...'

This part of town was the slum, while skipping along Matt brought out his system map to see in exactly what area he was in. The coloring was dark red, the worst color you could have. The health hazards in this area were the biggest, you could see human feces on the side of the roads and in the alleys.

He wanted to stop and help a couple of people out, they looked in dire need of medical assistance or at least a warm meal. After he was done with this young master business he would go back to headquarters and have a team come clean this mess up. This wasn't a problem for him at this point, he could cover the costs by making core formation-level items. He could probably even trade in some of those to the richer families in this city and they would do it instead, but he wasn't sure he could trust them in doing a good job just yet.

They were going quite deep into the slum area, the people were quite scary looking as he noticed a lot of them giving him the stink eye. He tried diffusing the situation with a bright smile, but to his dismay when he did that the people looked frightened instead.

'Guess they must be shy...'

While Matt was skipping through the poop-filled streets of Moonlight City, wondering if he would ever be able to wash this stench away from the new boots that he was wearing a group of kids were shivering in the corner of a large damaged building. This looked like some type of old storage space, the wood had been eaten away by time and there were many puddles due to the water dripping in during the times it rained.

A young man below the age of twenty was sitting on the back of another youth. That youth looked beaten, you could notice it by the number of bruises and his cut-up lower lip. He was on all fours and trembling, the other young man was sitting on his back with his legs crossed over one another using the other person as a chair.

"Hey, stop moving. A chair isn't supposed to move you, cretin! Can't even do that right you trash!"

The young man smacked the 'chair' on the head with his hand and laughed out. This was the young master that was almost robbed by the street urchins, he was sitting on the back of the person that tried snatching his purse, this was the oldest member of the group and the big brother.

"If you don't stop shivering I might decide to punish those little ones there, you wouldn't want that to happen now would you?"

There were about ten other kids all gathered together and surrounded by five cultivators, this were the guards of this young master. They had a little nifty treasure that helped them track these people here, one of the guards specialized in tracking as well. It could home in on a person that was recently touched by the person controlling it, one of the guards had touched the boy as he was trying to grab the young master's purse and so that's how they found the little guy's hideout.

"Young master, these kids won't be worth much I'm afraid. They all look frail and lack any cultivation."

One of the guards reported while looking at the children, they ranged from the ages of four to thirteen, the oldest being the one that his master was sitting on and he was just fourteen. They had miscalculated this robbery, the hidden guards weren't noticed as they were of quite the high caliber.

"Damn, useless as always. Why is a bunch of trashes like you even in this city, not worth the dirt under my boots."

He smacked the kid that he was sitting on again, thinking about what he should do with this bunch of useless urchins. He was mad at the new Zhang Clan, usually what he would do to people like this was having his people sell them for whatever they could to the slavers as criminal or debt slaves. The new power in town had decided to ban slavery though, this being a bit of a thorn in this young master's side.

"Those damn Zhang Clan retards, why do they prevent us from making a living, not like you can do anything more with trashes like these. Though we could still sell them on the side, no one has to know... hehe..."

He finally got fed up and stood up from the youth's back, giving him a kick to his stomach that sent him rolling over against a wall and towards the shivering children.

"L-leave big brother alone, you big bully!"

One of the younger children spoke up, it was a young girl that was now rubbing her brother's belly while looking at the young master with tears in her eyes.

"Huh?, you dare look at this young lord with those kinds of eyes! You there, give her a good slap!"

He pointed to one of his guards, the man in question just nodded and moved in the direction that the child was standing in, ready to follow his master's instructions. But as he was about to give the poor trembling girl a good smack he was tackled from the side by another youth, this youth came from outside and was little Zhu'er.

"Leave my junior sister alone!"

Well, the youth couldn't really bring the adult man down. It felt like he hit a brick wall, the adult guard just standing there with vacant eyes.

"Get off me, you little shit!"

But before he could smack the child away he felt a chill run down his spine, he could feel someone looking at him.

Chapter 112

The men looked in the direction that the voice was coming from. The boy that tackled the man fell onto his butt, then quickly scooted to the side to protect his little junior sister.

"Who dares!?"

The young master looked at the old man, not knowing who he was. He had a long beard and looked intimidating, but looks could be misleading. The young master was just a lowly Qi condensation practitioner, not even that high up there at only the 8th stage. He liked spending his time drinking and partying with the ladies in the pleasure district not really one for training. That's why he glanced to one of his guards, the man looked quite experienced and was in the middle level of foundation establishment.

The guard scanned the elder with his senses, he could tell that the elderly man was also in the foundation establishment stage at a similar level that he was. But he wasn't alone here, each guard here had at least a cultivation base of foundation establishment early stage and there were five of them against just one old guy.

Taking their ages into consideration, the bodyguards were men in their forties and fifties and the opponent looked to be sixty or seventy. In this world, you could mostly tell one's strength by the cultivation level and the age. An old age gave you hints that the cultivator wasn't very talented and couldn't advance past the stage that they were currently in and would probably be stuck in it for the rest of their life. This indicated that they should be weaker than younger cultivators at the same realm as they probably had more talent and vigor.

The bodyguard gave the young master a nod, signaling him that he felt confident in taking out this elderly man. This youth wasn't stupid, he knew that it wasn't wise to offend unknown people, they could turn up to be some kind of old powerful monster. Still, you could offend risky targets but you just had to make them vanish from the face of this world.

"I'm not sure who you are old man, but you better scram."

The young master proclaimed, while hiding behind his bodyguards smirking from the back at the elder that was about to get trashed by his group.

"Oh don't mind me, I'll be on my way soon. I'll just take these children with me and we will be on our way, what say you?"

Matt didn't want to cause a scene, no one was actually dead and he could make these cultivators collapse with a wave of his finger. He was planning on remembering the youth's face, maybe getting his name out during the conversation and then have his police force bring him in. Playing a superhero was nice and all, but these people had to learn to trust the new faction in town to help them out in the future and not rely on random cultivators to help them out. He wanted to have the man serve a normal prison sentence, but things weren't that easy and the kids were also thieves.

"Heh did you hear that men, he wants to take the poor kids home."

The people that were standing there just burst out in laughter not taking the man seriously. They were feeling quite content, the man was even speaking to them respectfully probably afraid of a beating.

"Yes, you can take these kids for a mere... five hundred... no, make that a thousand spirit stones! How's that for a fair price?"

The youth just laughed to himself, no one in their right mind would cough up a thousand spirit stones for some useless orphans.

"Oh, a thousand? Wait a moment sonny...I just need to check...how about these?"

The young master raised his brow at the old man's response, it was as if he was willing to pay that amount for these street urchins. He looked at the man who was looking at a storage ring a glint in the youth's eye as he saw that thing.

'That's a high-quality spatial ring, where did that old fart get it?'

The old guy then pulled out two swords, from a glance you could tell that they weren't simple weapons and that they were made by quite the master blacksmith.

"Here you go, two high-quality perfect grade mortal swords, they should go for around five hundred maybe even six hundred spirit stones at the auction house, this should do, right?"

Everyone gasped as the old guy pulled out two shiny new swords, they were radiating that perfect grade aura and were extremely close to something at the core formation stage. The guards in the shed gulped, they wanted weapons like those but they were forced to use lower quality goods given to them by the clan they were from. This clan was the Xing Clan, which this young master belonged too.

"B-bring those treasures over..."

The young master said while staring at the two weapons, he just had to have them. Trading some brats for even one of those would be a win in his opinion.

'But where did this old man get those from and he probably has more things in that storage ring...'

The youth was already thinking about his next step, should he risk offending anyone that was behind this old man or not. The man wasn't wearing the Zhang Clan robes, so he probably wasn't with that family.

'Even if he was with them, nothing will happen if he just vanishes..."

The Xing Clan had a bandit background so they were quite ruthless in their actions. From a young age, their offsprings were taught to never allow any loss of face and to be throughout with their actions. If you saw an opportunity for getting more power, you should go for it if the situation allowed for it even if there was a risk involved.

"Here you go sonny, now I'll just take the kids and we'll be on our merry way."

The bodyguard grabbed the two blades and carried them over to the young master, the kid took one of them while the guard kept the other. Both of them could see that these were quality goods, neither of them had a weapon of this quality on their person. While the old man was walking towards the kids, seemingly thinking that the deal was made.

The Xing young master had other plans, he was going to risk this. No one should miss one old fart, and even if they do they will be long gone and can blame it on bad luck. He gave his men a hand signal which the group knew well, they went to cut off all escape routes. The elder wasn't really doing much, he was now by the kids petting the crying girl that was standing next to the boy that tackled one of the bodyguards.

"Okay kids, just follow this uncle outside I'll bring you somewhere safe."

All of the kids looked to Zhu that came along with this strange old fart, they looked to him if they could trust the man or not. The boy gave them a nod and a couple of reassuring words.

"Don't worry, you can trust this Senior."

The boy said while trying to aid his injured brother, that was badly beaten on the ground his ribs probably broken due to that last kick he received.

"Mmm, you're not willing to let the kids go? But the deal was already made young man."

The old man spoke up which prompted the kids to look at him, he was looking at the smirking young master. His men were pulling out their weapons while encircling the group some of them standing back in the case that they fled.

"You think I'm stupid, give me that ring of yours and we might let you live old fool!"

The kids started crying again, the younger ones hiding behind the older ones the grandpa in front. The old man in question looked at his hand, his high-quality store ring on one of his wrinkled fingers. He moved his hand so that the backside of his palm would face the young master, the ring visible to the youth.

"Oh, you want this little thing? How can I trust you that you would let us go after I give it to you?"

The youth was getting more and more confident in his decision, this man wasn't bringing up any outside backing into the conversation. This meant that he probably didn't really have anyone more powerful behind him but still, the old man was getting on his nerves as his tone was quite relaxed.

"Stop messing around you old fart, hand over the ring! We are done playing games!"

He nodded to one of his guards, the man charged forward. This man wasn't the strongest from the group nor the weakest. This would be a test, they wondered what the old man would do. Would he use some kind of defensive treasure, would he charge in and try his luck in hand to hand combat, or would he try to run away.

The old man didn't move from his spot at all, he just looked at the incoming warrior. The bodyguard was holding a large saber with his hand, he swung it from over top his head like he was trying to bisect the elderly man that was just standing there. His weapon whizzed through the air, the children's eyes not even being able to fathom the incoming man's movements as he used some strange movement art, appearing like a blur in their eyes.

The kids closed their eyes, they expected to see the poor grandpa getting split in half. They felt the wind pressure from the attack suddenly hit their faces, their hair getting kicked up. But that was it, they couldn't hear the old man screaming or groaning. When they opened their eyes they saw something strange, the old man was holding the saber's tip between his index and middle finger. The attacker's biceps was bulging out indicating that he was trying to push his weapon downward, but the saber wasn't budging at all.

"Ho ho, how ferocious, this grandpa almost had a heart attack, so fearsome indeed!"

The old man laughed and chuckled while the bodyguard tried his best to pull or push his saber away from the clutches of those two fingers. The elder then flicked his fingers, the saber that the man was holding got flung upward and lodged itself in his shoulder, blood spraying into the air and the man screaming out in pain.

"What are you fools waiting for, get that old fart!"

The young man screamed out, he didn't anticipate the man to be so ferocious but he still had more guards one stronger than the other, they should be able to handle one old man. The muscular men charged at the man that in return slowly walked towards them, his facial expression not really changing.

They attacked him from all directions, they had swords and spears heading for the man's weak spots, the head, the heart, the solar plexus, and even his groin. But before the weapons could land they suddenly shattered into many pieces, the shrapnel heading in the directions that the attackers made their strikes. The sharp metallic parts embedded themselves in the men's faces and bodies, quickly making them retreat and squirm out in pain.

"W-what are you idiots doing, kill him!"

The young master was fuming as he saw his men just scatter, wounds all over their bodies the old fart just standing there and grinning. The men tried standing up, but they were seasoned warriors and knew that this elder in front of them wasn't even trying hard. He was probably hiding his cultivation level and could slap them to death if he wanted to. They groaned as their young idiot of a master wasn't realizing that fact yet.

"Oh, you shouldn't be that quick to murder people young man."

Suddenly the youth felt some wind hit his face, the man just vanished and was now standing right behind him. He was holding onto the Xing Clan boy's shoulder while talking.

"Don't touch me, I'm the Xing Clan's second son! If you touch me my father will kill you and your whole family!"

The youth turned around, the old man had quite the grip on his shoulder as he felt most of his power leaving him.

"Oh shut up you caricature of a person."

*SMACK*

The young master was slapped on the cheek and not lightly. His body spun around his arms floppy as the youth lost all power in his limbs the moment he received the hit, he made a nice arch and hit the shacks wooden wall and crashed through it right outside. He was instantly out cold and foaming at the mouth, some of his teeth knocked out.

A note from Kuropon

Patreon for some more Chapters https://www.patreon.com/kuropon

Discord https://discord.gg/fWefdgn

Chapter 113

Matt looked down at his palm that just slapped the youth into the wall, he didn't think he would make him fly that hard.

'He was weaker than expected... good that I lowered my strength... could have killed the kid...'

He gulped, he misjudged how strong that young master was. He was still in battle mode from fighting his bodyguards so even though he meant to give him a gentle pat to the cheek, that would at most make him go down to one knee. He gave him a strong enough smack to make him comedically fly to the side while knocking out a couple of teeth in the process.

'Well, at least they are down and don't look like they will be resisting anymore.'

He glanced at the warriors that were clutching various parts of their bodies, the metal shrapnel had lodged itself into their flesh and probably hurt like hell. The kids were protected behind him thanks to his transparent shield, so they were all fine and dandy.

'Well then... what should I do now...'

He looked at the disgruntled bodyguards that were squirming on the ground, trying to remove metal pieces from their cheeks. He could try to round them all up, make them carry the young master over to the police station. But there were these crying children behind his back, he was slightly afraid that the orphans would just run away if he wasn't paying attention.

"Hey you there, what's the Xing Clan second son's name?"

One of the bodyguards that wasn't injured looked up at the scary grandpa and quickly replied.

"T-the young master's name is Xing Shie, please elder show mercy, the Xing clan will surly repay you handsomely."

The man quickly bowed, hoping that this crazy old fart wouldn't just kill them all. If they made it back to the Xing Clan compound they could get some backup and take care of this elder.

Matt decided to just use his police force for the job, he also wanted to see how they would handle the procedure of apprehending a young master. He wasn't sure if everyone was on the same page as he was though, after the fiasco with the lady and her son that his workers and clan members refused to help out.

'Hope they won't take any bribes... but this would be a good opportunity to see if they do. It might be better if that happened now than later.'

Matt didn't kid himself, there were a couple of bad apples even back in Spirit Spring City, but they were far too afraid of him to do anything about him. Still, he knew that they were waiting for him to slip up, little schemers that they were. He already disowned the clan members that left the city during the time he was at that secret ground. He couldn't trust people that just run away whenever times got tough.

'I need to open that school soon so then we can start indoctrin... training the kids to be good policemen, yeah...'

Matthew knew that most people in this world liked to be placed in groups. They would stay loyal to the person that gave them the opportunity to better themselves, for instance by giving them some cultivation manuals and some resources to break through a realm or two. But there were always one or two of those scheming types, that everything was just a stepping stone for their way to the top.

He had the young master's name now, so he just turned around being sure to reply with a resounding snort to the pleading that the bodyguard was doing.

"Don't worry, I'm not the one that will be taking care of you, I will be sure to report this incident to the brand new and glorious, Zhang Clan, Police Department!"

He made sure to pronounce the Zhang Clan name clearly, it would surely send the cultivators trembling in their boots. In reality, they didn't know what the old guy was on about, they knew that the Zhang Clan was doing some strange stuff in the background, but they still thought that even they would just take a bribe and be done with it.

He finally turned around the group of children, the enemies were slowly removing themselves from the old shed that was close to crumbling due to the release of the warriors fighting aura. The kids were still scared, tears in the eyes of some but some of the older ones had that glint in their eyes, like someone that had been through a lot.

"Don't worry children, grandpa here will protect all of you, come with me, we need to treat your friend here first, then let's all go to a nice restaurant, you probably haven't had a warm meal in quite some time!"

The kids looked at each other, the younger ones were instinctively on board after the grandpa mentioned a warm meal. The older ones were more apprehensive as they didn't really trust adults anymore. They didn't have any role models and most of them had no older family members left alive or caring for them. The boy that Matt healed being a rare case that still had a loving mother with him.

Luckily he had the boy to speak up for him this time around, otherwise, he would probably have to stuff the kids into his energy bubble.

"Don't worry, we can trust this Senior, he healed my wounds too!"

Thank's to the youth he earned some trust, the other kids looked at their older brother and nodded they knew him well enough to know that he wouldn't lie to them. They were always worried about their beaten elder brother that was slowly succumbing to his internal injuries.

"I guess we should give this young fellow some first aid, first."

The old man proclaimed while moving over to the collapsed youth on the ground. The kids parting to the side after they got the nod from their other brother that was vouching for the old man.

"Let's see..."

Matt's eyes glowed slightly, this was quite the nifty physician skill that let you see the internal injuries that a patient had. But could also be used during battle to notice your opponent's weak points. He could see the youth's shattered ribs, some lacerations, and the head trauma. He was still conscious though and it would probably be a problem to get him to insert those acupuncture needles into the frightened teen.

Instead, he moved in closer and leaned over, he would use a less direct approach. This was akin to a regular healing art, he just placed his index finger on the youth's upper Dantian on his forehead. The kids weren't sure what this man was doing, but the moment his finger touched their brother's forehead something astonishing happened.

They could see the elder's finger glow in an astonishing golden light. He was directing his healing energies through the boy's forehead and gently guiding them through his meridians, which then dispersed them all throughout his body. This was a slower procedure than when he used his acupuncture needles. This one had to go from top to bottom in order, while the needles were able to disperse his healing energies simultaneously to all the injured parts.

The youths never came across such a healing method, but they haven't really seen many powerful cultivators in general. The injured youth started feeling lightheaded, his muscles relaxing as the healing energies washed over him. He felt like he was floating on a cloud, the healing art also having the boon of removing the pain while the body regenerated.

Soon enough the child was healed, the kids rejoicing as they saw the wounds vanishing from their elder brother's face. He was even well enough to stand up, looking at the palms of his hands some of the fingers that were previously broken weren't hurting at all anymore, he only felt a strange tingling sensation like some ants were running inside those previously broken digits.

"W-what?"

He looked at the elder that was now standing up, hands behind his back and already in his master cultivator pose. The youth instantly dropped down to his knees and started bowing, the boy knowing well that this man had to be some kind of powerful master that the couldn't offend.

"Well then little thief, you have offended some pesky people, how about you follow me along with your juniors, I'll give you all a place to stay. But don't think it's going to be free, you'll have to work for your wage."

The boy stood up, his head dropping down as the elder mentioned the part about offending other people. He knew that his band or urchins had bit off more than they could chew. This was the young master of the Xing Clan we were talking about, that was a scary family to have offended. Normally they would have needed to leave this city, there was no hope for them after offending a powerhouse clan like that, but this Senior here was offering his help.

"Work? Wage? You're offering us work?"

The youth was even more suspicious, who would offer work to a band of pickpockets with no background whatsoever. They had no value unless they showed some kind of talent for cultivation.

"Yes, just regular work, the Zhang Clan is creating an orphanage in this city, you will be fed and have a roof over your head. In return you'll have to do various tasks, mostly cleaning out these ghastly streets from all this garbage."

"If you are old enough, you can even join the police academy they are making. You just need to pass some tests, you'll get some cultivation resources and will be able to work for them if you are a promising recruit. But, let's get out of here first, I promised you some food first!"

He was actually hungry himself, having quite an appetite for this world's cuisine. The spiritual energy-rich foods were a lot tastier than the ones back on earth, he just couldn't get enough of those.

The children took the man up on the offer, but they still were thinking about running away if the opportunity presented themselves. They only really trusted themselves. Though they wanted those things that he was talking about to be the truth, they didn't really like living in the slums with a leaky roof over their head, not knowing if they would have any rice to get by each day.

They all wandered into the richer part of town, the elder was walking in front while some people whispered from the side. The first child and his mother were with them as well, the woman was also feeling uncomfortable due to her shabby appearance. She rarely came to this part of the city, mostly here to clean up after some young masters drinking spree as no one really wanted to tend to vomit.

Logically they were denied access to the restaurant that the old man wanted to bring them over, but after the elder produced a big sack of golden coins the restaurant owners started singing a different tune. This gramps was loaded, the children got quite the feast as they even occupied one of the upper floors all to themselves.

'Man, they must have had it harsh...'

Matt groaned inwardly as he saw those kids devouring the food, almost forgetting to breathe between the chomps they were taking. They were eating like this was the first meal that they had their entire life, snoot, and tears filling their eyes from the sheer happiness they were experiencing. Some of them even made a vow to follow this strange grandpa for the rest of their lives, Matt would probably sweat if he found out that peoples devotion could be so easily bought with some food around here.

While the kids were eating, he took out a communication jade. It was already close to night time after he headed out from the clinic, so he needed to get these kids shelter. He notified Zhang Kuo, the man knew that he, the Patriarch was disguised as the clinic doctor at the moment. He ordered him to arrange shelter for these kids and also to make a report to the police unit, noting him down as the prime witness.

"Hm, things are all set now. I hope my juniors won't disappoint me too much..."

Chapter 114

The kids were a bit apprehensive to go with the Zhang Clan members, but the elder that saved them reassured them that it was fine.

"I'll be at the clinic, for now, if anything happens you can just come running to this grandpa and he will protect you with all his might!"

He proclaimed to give the kids somewhere to go if things got rough, but he couldn't really stay with them any longer. They would be placed in an orphanage and watched, they were still pickpockets so they needed to be punished so, for now, they would be on lockdown. They had a program to teach kids at a gated school, they would have a dorm to live in as well.

The whole project was more or less a one package deal, with the orphanage, dorm, school, and various training facilities being at one spot. The kids would get basic education and even some basic cultivation manuals to get them going. The children could slowly adapt and after a certain period had a choice to make, they could either join the Zhang Clan as one of their lower-level sub-factions or just leave and do their own thing.

Matt was planning to school the kids in the basics of pill forging, crafting and various other professions. He wanted to let the kids find something they were good at, so then they could find some work later on in their life. It would probably be easier to study under a master if the disciple had some proper foundations in the basics of the craft they were studying in.

'But let's try not to put them in too much of a debt...'

There was a small catch though. The kids were required to pay some of the tuition fees later on in their life, he wanted it to be free but after some calculations, the numbers just didn't add up. Either he would need to cover the price himself, or have the people learning to repay the Zhang Clan later.

He went with the second option, he wanted to teach the youths a lesson that nothing was really free in this life, but also that you should repay your debts. They would have ample time to repay it though and it was a reasonable price mostly for the food eaten, lodging fees and the teacher fees.

Zhang Kuo was swift to organize the exchange, he couldn't let his Patriarch waiting and soon a group of Zhang Clan cultivators was standing in front of the restaurant. They had their orders and meet with the clinic doctor in question but they didn't know that it was their glorious leader in disguise.

He got the children to come with him and that group, escorting them to the dorm they would be living in now. The new building was more styled in the earthly ways, with many smaller rooms with bunk beds. The kids would be staying here while some Zhang members taught them how to read and some basic cultivation methods. Those methods were slightly better than what other cultivators used, but still, nothing that would impact the Zhang clan's hold on its power.

Matt had upgraded all the core Zhang Clan cultivation methods, plus added a lot of the manuals he copied over from the sacred grounds. The new cultivators would be advancing swiftly with a high-quality foundation. Zhang Zhi was already a core formation expert and Zhang Jin moved over to the middle stage not long ago too. There were many members that were on the cusp of breaking through, but everyone had to reevaluate their foundation.

With the new addition of the updated books, everyone had to go through a process of retraining. The cracked and shaky foundation pillars had to be repaired as much as they could before the practitioner could advance. This process was a whole more tedious for people at an advanced age who had this kind of shaky foundation, so mostly the younger cultivators would progress further. Some of those cracked foundation pillars just couldn't be repaired without dumping in a lot of resources.

At least that would be the normal outcome, but they had their Patriarch with those holy element powers now. He could somehow repair a damaged foundation pillar so if you were deemed worthy, you could advance further with the help of Zhang Dong. The process was slow, so not everyone could get that treatment at this time only the elders that came back from the secret ground would get treated. From the twenty that went in, fifteen returned with five of them dying during the beast waves or while fighting the demon cultivator.

The kids looked at the grandpa that was waving at them, he brought them over to a strange place in which they were going to stay. There were some friendly people around, mostly women that were good at tending to the kids.

"Now stay with the elder sisters here, they will take care of you. Listen to them and don't cause trouble."

The old man parted with the kids and headed out. It was already late, the kids were moved to the rooms by the attending elder sisters that would explain how things worked there. Now the only problem was that Xing Clan's young master, the police unit was informed and the old man that was the prime witness was now at the new police station.

He was in the classic interrogation room, it even had a one-way mirror with some other police members on the other side. Before entering this place Matt could see his police-men working, they were bringing in some ruffians that were spouting the usual gibberish about being some big shot.

"So, Senior Wei Hung. Let me just go over it once more. You encountered Xing Shie in the city slums area..."

Matt was sitting opposite some unknown clan member that was wearing his police uniform, he was still trying not to smirk at the cultivation nuts wearing more modern clothes. They just read some questions down from a parchment about the encounter with the Xing family. They clearly were inexperienced, the man kept sneaking peeks at the paper not knowing wwhat to ask about while taking notes.

He was free to go afterward, they knew that he worked for their clan at their new clinic. The next step for them would be to apprehend the suspect involved in the beating, the suspect's biggest transgression was the half beaten small boy that the elder healed as the other children weren't as beaten up as that one was. But the normal officers would only bring him in, the judging would be carried out by at least a sergeant.

"Xing Clan, this could get ugly..."

One of the Zhang officers said while they were gathering people. They knew about that family and knew that it was one of the stronger ones that didn't like to play by the rules.

"Think we might need the Captain to tag along with us..."

"Well, we have orders to go with a smaller force first, then call for backup if they start resisting or deny us entry into their living area."

Another police member said while fixing his police cap, he was reading things from some booklet. They had some basic procedures written down in there, like breaking down the door if the offenders don't comply. There was no judicial system quite yet, so they didn't have to tell them their rights yet.

The group of Zhang Cultivators gathered, they were somewhat experienced as they were doing this back home in Spirit Spring City. But back there no one in their right mind would ever oppose them, in this town things might be tricky at the beginning stages. The leading sergeant was one of the elders that survived the secret ground mission and was at the foundation establishment great circle.

He took about ten people with him and headed over to the Xing Clan main mansion. They had to go through the pleasure district to get there, the mafioso like family not caring in the slightest that they had their main house in this kind of environment.

While they were making their way there, the Xing Clan young master was back home getting treatment.

"Ah it hurts, my face... he damaged my handsome face! Father, you must avenge me!"

The youth was squirming while holding on to his face, the injury was still new and you could see a handprint plastered over one of the man's cheeks. His pearly white smile was gone as a couple of his teeth got knocked out in the process, pills that could repair teeth didn't come cheap so he would have to wait for some to be delivered.

"Calm down Shie, tell me again, what happened? It was an old man? Did he really just want to save some useless brats? He also had many high-quality treasures?"

The father was sitting to the side while some other people tended to his son, he couldn't really wrap his mind around a friendly grandpa just wanted to help some kids out, that didn't make any sense.

"Yes Father, he just came and started spouting some nonsense! He even gave me two good swords to trade for those damn kids, ow my face..."

"Then you got greedy, you should learn to measure people's strength better. Don't depend on your retainers so much."

The father took a puff from his large cigar, worried that his son was such a useless little shit.

"Yes, it was all their fault then need to get lashed to death, that idiot was confident in taking that elder in battle. I would have never offended him otherwise!"

The father nodded, he needed to make an example those bodyguards failed in their mission of protecting his son, they needed to get punished and severely. While Xing Deng was about to speak up one of his retainers walked in, moved over to him and whispered something into his ear.

"THEY WHAT?"

He stood up instantly, his hand moving into a fist as he crushed the cigar that he was holding.

"What do those Zhang Clan bastards want? Why do they want my Son to come with them?"

He looked at his injured brat and then headed out of the room, not knowing what these Zhang Clan members wanted but he wasn't in a position to give them the cold shoulder.

"Let them in, get bring over our strongest warriors to come too, this might turn ugly..."

He wasn't sure what they wanted his son for, but it probably had something to do with the old man that beat up his second son.

"Shie'er stay here and don't come out and be quiet!"

He strode out, some bodyguards instantly appearing next to him half a step behind him. He relocated into the main room that he usually brought in guests, he sat down on a large chair and got himself a new cigar as well. He then waited for the other people to come over while going over the things that his son and his retainers reported.

"Now entering, the Zhang Clan... Moonlight City Police force?... s-sergeant..."

One of the Xing clan members announced the people that arrived, they were ten cultivators wearing dark blue robes with strange hats on their heads. Xing Deng instantly tried to measure their fighting potential, his retainers, and bodyguards stationed all around the room, they were there to jump in if a fight broke out.

'That sergeant cultivator is the strongest... the rest is weaker... not that much of a problem.'

The current Xing clan forces could probably defend against these invaders. He himself could probably handle the strongest member from that group.

"Welcome friends from the Zhang Clan, please sit down and explain to me what you need with my Son?"

He wasn't one to beat around the bush too much, some other people would probably try to butter up to these Zhang Clan members. He, on the other hand, wanted to know the main reason they were here and how much cash they wanted. From his perspective, this was just a way of the new clan to flex their cultivation muscles and they probably just wanted to extort some spirit stones or treasures from them.

"Let's get straight to the point then, Mr. Deng. Your son is charged with assault on a young boy and a couple of other youths, he had beaten them severely almost resulting in death. He had some men with him that have the same charges."

The commanding officer from the group spoke out, he was your regular looking cultivator elder that looked to be in his fifties or sixties. He presented the charges that the men faced.

"We demand you hand those men over to us, they will be put on trial and their sentence will be decided later. I urge you to hand them over willfully as we will use force if you don't comply."

The man looked around the room, spotting the angry Xing Clan members that were taking a hit to the face right about now.

"I'd like to remind you, that our Captain is a core formation expert and if you resist we will have to call for him. You probably wouldn't want that, now would you?"

The elder that was just speaking grinned widely while looking at the Xing Clan Patriarch, the man in question had quite the large vein popping out on his forehead just now. It was now up to him, would they resist or would he hand his son over to these cultivators dressed in blue.

A note from Kuropon

Patreon for some more Chapters https://www.patreon.com/kuropon

Discord https://discord.gg/fWefdgn

Chapter 116

Matt looked around, he was still in a highly-populated area, should he go into a more secluded one or should he see what those people that were tailing him would do. He didn't think they would attack him in a populated area, they probably just wanted to silence him. It was probably for losing face and so he couldn't testify in the new court he was setting up.

'But yeah, my clan sure is useless... was hoping for at least someone to notice and shadow me from the side, no one is thinking ahead...'

This would be a good opportunity for the police force to tail him as well, if someone attacked him they could swoop in and apprehend them. It would be a shut case and then they could even try to bring in that clan Patriarch for questioning. Though taking the head of a kind of strong clan would probably result in some bloodshed, but that couldn't be helped.

'Would have been a good show of hand, would show people that we don't look kindly at criminals that retaliate, but alas...'

Matt wasn't sure about these squad of shadowy figures tailing him, they were probably one of those death warriors he read in books. They would probably kill themselves sooner than getting apprehended by him. He had to swiftly capture them, but they might do some drastic things like swallowing their own tongue.

The truth-telling formation had a weakness, if the person was very adamant about it, it would start divulging copious amounts of pain. This showed that the person was lying, but would also spring in if he didn't reply to the question. A warrior trained for death would probably not talk and just die in the courtroom, so they didn't make for great witnesses. Some stronger cultivators could probably just tank the formation's painful treatment and not die.

There was one other more drastic way to tell if someone was telling the truth or not, which was soul reading. This was an extremely hard technique to perform but it let the one performing it read the truth from the person they were using it on. This would leave the person dead outright though and you required a high cultivation level to not suffer damage to your own soul in response.

When the technique was used the two souls collided against each other in a sort of battle, the one that came out on top could read the truth from the weaker one. It would destroy that soul in the process and the soul that won out, would receive some wounds. Due to this it was quite unsafe for the person reading it as well. It could lead to problems in the cultivation down the road, so it was rarely used only sometimes when there was no other way or maybe if someone's life depended on it.

'Why do these things keep happening whenever I want to get some food?"

He was standing outside a restaurant the sun already going down, he sighed and walked on, he didn't want to risk those cultivation hobos getting the people inside the establishment involved. He started going to a more secluded area of the city where the people living there wouldn't get involved too much. He hoped that the assassins that were tailing him don't chicken out as this was an obvious trap, who just wanders into an empty plot of land in the middle of the night?

'Well, these cultivator nuts are always very prideful they probably think this will be the perfect opportunity to kill me. Too stuck up to think that someone noticed their movements and is stronger than them. Though I'd rather deal with these types than with those that won't show their fangs right until the end while letting their own family members die instead.

That was indeed the worst type of person in these kind's of worlds to go against. They would act all chummy with you, being some third cousin of the Patriarch from god knows where. Always losing against their own siblings but in reality, having some kind of strange technique that made them insanely strong. They would slowly build up their power base on the down low, then pounce you when you were on your weakest just to be sure that they could take you out.

While he was moving through an empty alleyway he noticed some movement, he wanted to go further in and even outside the city if you could but these men weren't willing to just tail him that long.

'Hm, did they notice that there was something fishy?'

He could feel them moving in front of him, they had some kind of shadow art that made them blend in within the darkness of the night. He could feel their presence though, even without his detection technique the gap in cultivation was far too large. It felt like he was about to pick on some kids, but these men were ruthless killers, he was already past the point of feeling bad about killing people like that. He still wanted the police to bring them in, but he wasn't sure that these people would come quietly.

It was creepy looking, he could see the shadows wiggling about like some kind of dark liquid was going through it. Inside that dark mass were cultivators just shuffling through the walls, they went past him probably to cut away his only route of escape. He kept on walking, letting them think that he didn't notice something, but inside he was slightly mad that he couldn't eat those nice meat buns at that restaurant he was going to go to.

There were three people in front and three people behind him now, but those weren't all of them. There were also two people on each side up on the buildings. There were exactly ten attackers, the weakest one was in the middle stage of foundation establishment and they even had two in the great circle, most of them were in the late stage though.

Matt wasn't sure if he should be honored that they sent such a big murder force after him, or if he should feel bad that these guys were going against someone that was half step into the nascent soul realm.

'Ah, should I just finish them quickly or play around...'

He thought back to the time in the secret area, where he was a bit too prideful for his own good. It would probably not be a good thing to not take these guys seriously, even though they had no way to harm him, they could always try taking hostages while fleeing. They could even blow up part of the city if the scuffle got too obvious.

'I guess I should put on my business face and wrap this up.'

While he was thinking that, he heard something whizzing through the air. This was something that he was quite knowledgeable of. Every serious weeb would know what these things coming towards him were.

'Oh, throwing stars? shurikens?'

They were coming at him from all sides. He could see them spinning around in slow motion while they flew towards all of the vital points of his body. These guys weren't playing around, they were trying to snipe him with their throwing stars. He had a couple of ways to take care of these projectile weapons, he could even let them hit his body as he didn't think they could pierce through his body refining technique. He could also release his aura to slow their approach or even use his shielding technique.

He went for a more rudimentary approach though. Firstly he moved his hands upwards, stretching them out while examining where the first batch of shurikens was coming from. His hands were fast as lightning. A normal cultivator would only see afterimages or even less than that as Matt in the form of the elder started catching the incoming weapons with his hands.

The men from the shadows didn't relent though, they kept at it the clinging and clanging of metal quickly resounding through the alley as Matt didn't have enough space between his fingers to catch all of these projectile weapons. He started bouncing them backward, his palm strikes formed a sort of dome around the area that he was standing in.

The assassins looked at the spectacle while sweat formed on their foreheads, they could barely follow this old man's movements. The stronger ones from the group could somewhat keep up, but in the reality was that killing this elder wouldn't be quite easy. They were even astonished that he wasn't going down, he clearly smacked the weapons back with his hands, the shurikens were laced with poison that on skin contact would dull the enemies movements and render them defenseless within a short amount of time.

"The poison isn't working, everyone attack together!"

Matt noticed before the weapon's hit that there was some liquid on it, but his body was way too tough and resistant to be affected by such crude venom. There was a small pile of metallic stars next to his feet now, the enemies finally deciding to go into melee range. They charged from the back and from the rear while the assassin members that were on the roofs continued with the range attacks.

He could now get a good look at these attackers, they looked quite familiar and the weapons that they kept throwing at them fit their appearance quite well.

'Damn, nice ninja outfits...'

They looked quite similar to a certain ice slinging ninja game character, though their ninja robes were pure black with some metallic parts here and there. They had armguards on their hands and some shoulder guards as well, the part that covered their mouth was a separate piece from their hood part and it looked like it could function as a gas mask to boot.

'Guess I need to be wary of any strange fumes coming out from them.'

The attackers had various ninja-themed weapons, there were the usual katanas here and there. One person had a hooked sword of sorts while another was holding on to that weapon that looked like a sickle attached to a chain with a weight at the end part of the chain. One was dual-wielding sickle-like weapons outright, he could even hear the top cultivators switching to other weapons which blew darts this time around.

"Quite the ferocious bunch aren't ya? Did the Xing Clan send you to silence this old man? I'm not sure you'll be up to the task though."

The assassins didn't reply and just charged in, they knew that this man was taking them lightly and they wanted to profit on his lax attitude. The attacks were coming from all sides and they knew how to work together, no one under the core formation-level could be a match for this group. But this was the problem, the man they were facing was a lot stronger than that.

Just before one of their attacks was about to land and the other members were following up for a combo, the man vanished. The six ninjas came to a stop, their eyes bulging as they couldn't see the old man anywhere he just vanished from the spot not leaving anything behind. Well, the shurikens that were on the ground were flickering now as if some electricity was got infused due to something.

"GAH! ARGH!"

They soon looked up, the man was holding one of their squadmates in his hand and by the neck. The other three were already falling down from the building and out cold.

"Always go for the support first!"

The men with the blow darts couldn't even get one clean hit as Matt charged upwards while using his thunder steps. He had gotten it to such a high proficiency that it looked like he was teleporting at this point. The man in his grasp convulsed and twitched as he was getting choked out with one hand. He didn't kill them just yet as for now he just infused them with his Qi to make them pass out, they wouldn't wake out for quite some time with his superior energy interfering with their inferior one.

The old man tossed the enemy that was now more or less a rag doll to the side. He then hopped off the building he was standing on and kicked himself off some bricks that were at the top part of the wall. His kick caused part of the wall to crack, he was soon back on the ground. He did a flip and landed on his feet, the ground shaking under the pressure and spider-like webs forming in the earth below.

He kicked up quite the dust cloud and made a lot of noise, the assassin ground still went after him, failure was not an option and they would die anyway if they let this man go. The old man wasn't as passive anymore though, before they could reassess the situation his fist was flying towards the strongest member of the group.

The man didn't have enough time to activate any of his defensive treasures nor to dodge this fast attack. He took a clean hit, his cheekbones breaking as he flew like a puppet with its strings severed towards the alley. He bounced and bounced as he flew further and further finally ramming into the side of the wall, out cold and a bloody mess.

Soon his friends ended up in the same way, their faces were all battered and bruised this elder wasn't playing around. Soon enough he was holding up onto the last member of the group. Matt pulled his mask down to reveal a forty-something man, the man was looking at him with fear in his eyes probably not willing to die here and now.

"So, you willing to answer a couple of questions, I'll guarantee your safety if you do, you might even only have to work in a mine for a while instead of getting killed, sounds like a good deal, right?"

Before the man could answer the old man looked to the side, the grin from his face replaced with a frown. The assassin squinted with his eyes, trying to see who it was that came, was it help from the Xing clan? When he heard the voice though, he knew that it was someone else entirely.

"Stop right there criminal scum! Nobody breaks the law under our watch!"

Matt looked at the half beaten man in his grip, he had blood on his fists and looked like the bad guy in this situation.

'Awww, shit...'

A note from Kuropon

Patreon for some more Chapters https://www.patreon.com/kuropon

Discord https://discord.gg/fWefdgn

Chapter 117

Matt was holding onto one of the beaten-up Ninja wannabes, the person looked like a man in their forties with a busted lip and a swollen eye from the smack he received from this old man named Wei Hung. He slowly turned his head to where the voices were coming from, to his dismay the Fuzz had arrived in the worst possible moment. It was as if he was the bad guy in this situation, all you could see were many people on the ground some of them were even twitching.

He even had blood on his hands, which made him look even worse. The whole situation was noticed by a couple of policemen patrolling the city, they had heard a ruckus the moment Matt landed on the ground after he jumped off that building. These two people weren't any regular police officers though, they were wearing uniforms that Matt was quite familiar with as he was the one that made them.

'Damn, guess I'll have to go talk my way out at the police station. This might look bad, but I bet I can explain everything when we go back.'

He was still the key witness in the case, the new police force should be able to figure out that the people here were trying to murder him so that he couldn't testify. Though he wasn't sure they were so good at detective work just yet.

"Ah, this can all be explained, I'll come peace..."

He wanted to say that he would come peacefully but before he could do that the two 'officers' charged at him.

"Quiet you scum, let go of that person this instant!"

A woman's voice could be heard behind the mask she was wearing, it was quite the youthful sounding one as well. Her partner was running right behind her, giving her some backup.

'So, you're not even going to ask what was happening and are just going to beat the suspect up from the get-go?'

It didn't look like diplomacy was an answer in this situation. The glorious Zhang clan Patriarch had a decision to make, would he let these two juniors smack him around, then maybe drag him back to the police station. He might be thrown into jail if he didn't reveal his true self, but what would happen to these two. He was the freaking Zhang Clan Patriarch, the other clan members would probably never let this slide. Being disrespectful to the clan leader was akin to treason, they could be thrown out, be ostracised or worse.

'But what should I do... should I just run...'

While he was thinking about his next move a heel was flying towards his head, he almost forgot that the two were coming for him. He stepped to the side, it looked like a very relaxed and slow type of movement but in reality, it was very swift. The woman flew past him missing her target, caught off guard as she flew forward with her momentum.

"Sister Ai, watch out, this elder isn't simple!"

This was, of course, the duo that saved the young girls from the fat slaver. Zhang Teng swooped to the rescue, afraid that the elder would strike his clan sister while she was off balance. His hands coiled like two snakes, the strange attack making the youth's arms extend in length. But before they could reach the elderly man's face they bounced back, Teng's hands snapped backward as if getting deflected by something hard.

"Hey, I'm innocent! These guys attacked me, aren't you supposed to hear me out before you start attacking?"

He tried to reason with the two, but after knocking the snake youth back the sister that flew past him moved back into the fray. She pulled out a black tonfa, this was a standard weapon that came in various grades and sizes. Matt found himself dodging all of these attacks, the two youths were promising young talents but they were nowhere near his level of strength. The hardest thing for Matt was holding back, he didn't want to hurt any of these kids, he could probably snap them in half with a flick of his finger.

"Stop resisting, you criminal scum!"

The two weren't relenting though, he had to give it to those two, they were stupid but brave. Maybe if he played with them for a while they would tire out and then hear him out. He must have overdone it with the policeman guide that he made, guess it wasn't smart to put that clause about going harder after criminals that were resisting.

However, while he was thinking about his next move more people started showing up. He forgot that they all had communication treasures that would alert other coppers if some of their squadmates were in trouble and fighting. He was surrounded once more, this time around there were even more people as this alleyway was getting crowded.

'Are you serious?... For god's sale, I'm your damn Patriarch!'

He bit his lower lip, trying not to give these fools a good thrashing. But his passive attitude was probably making these idiots feel like they had a winning chance.

"Altogether, he is clearly at a disadvantage he can't even attack!"

He was right, due to only dodging their attacks and smacking them away gently here and there, the junior members thought that the old man was just having a hard time evading them and couldn't counterattack. He looked as many police uniform wearing cultivators charged at him from all sides, they were mostly using tonfa like weapons. A sigh escaped his mouth, the man finally having enough of this farce.

"Don't get cocky now..."

The people were doing a joint combination attack that would rain down justice on this murderous elder, they could almost see him wincing on the ground and begging them for mercy. However, they suddenly felt a strange sensation like something was telling them to quickly escape. It was too late though, the elder's facial expression suddenly changed and he moved his leg upwards slightly. He then stepped forward or at least that was what it looked like.

This unthreatening motion was accompanied by a spike in the elder's cultivation aura, the moment that foot touched the ground a sudden repelling force was produced. The magnificent combination attack that these cultivators trained for months was instantly broken, they were all sent flying backward as a shockwave destroyed any forward momentum that they had.

"C-core formation?..."

Everyone was down on their knees, the old grandpa that looked meek and weak just a second ago, now looked like a monster to these cultivators. They didn't think that this man would be this strong, they finally realized that he was just playing with them and he could have killed them at any moment. The group of people looked up, their legs shaking a bit as they stood up, not really sure what to do.

"Have you calmed down now?... Can I finally explain mys...."

While he was talking he suddenly felt something, he quickly jumped up into the air only to see the ground beneath him explode into dust. The cultivators that were standing in the alley were of course hit by the residual blast, which caused them to fly in various directions, the buildings were already shabby looking but now the walls were destroyed as well.

'No... is it that idiot now...'

Matt looked in the direction that the attack came from, his eyes squinting as he could see a man on a sword flying towards him. He knew this idiot samurai quite well, it was his number one fan Zhang Zhi charging at him with murder in his eyes.

"You shall not hurt these people, you criminal scum!"

'But you are the one that almost killed them with that attack...'

Matt noticed that this man didn't think about collateral damage at all. This explained why he was okay with slicing the Cheng Clan's ship in half. There were non-combatants on that ship, luckily none of them was killed but some of them were heavily injured. Luckily the cleanup crew had enough pills to heal the slaves on the ship, they brought them back to the cities afterward.

'What now...'

This was slowly getting out of hand, he didn't think his own people would start chasing him around town. For now he had to lead this idiot Zhang Zhi out of this city, so that he wouldn't destroy it in the process of capturing him. He turned around and started hopping from building to building, the other man chasing after him while the juniors below groaned out loud due to having been caught in the aftershock of Zhang Zhi's attack.

"Stop you criminal! This Zhang Zhi will follow you to the end of this continent!"

Matt was planning to leave the city, then show his trusted clan member who he really was and explain that he was doing a secret mission. But things weren't working out, this man started swinging his sword around producing those flying dragon attacks of his. Buildings started exploding and people screamed in the streets, this guy was clearly ignoring others around him and just caring about the mission that his Patriarch had given him.

'Damn, he is holding back a bit... but he might actually hurt someone like this...'

The rooftops were exploding and more policemen gathered as they followed their captain. The old man suddenly jumped really high and flew through the air, landing at an open plot of land with a lot of empty space around him. He then faced their captain, the policemen cheered their captain on as they saw the two ready to duke it out.

"Get him Captain!"

"Show him what happens to people that go against the Zhang Clan!"

"He was clearly resisting, we must bring him in!"

They shouted from the back while slowly encircling the spot that Matt landed, they were keeping their distance though as they knew that they couldn't get involved in a fight of core formation experts.

"Surrender now!"

Zhang Zhi held his sword out and pointed it at the old man, Wei Hung in response frowned while looking around. He had enough, he didn't care if his cover would be blown and he would look like some weirdo that dressed as an old man while being the clan leader. He couldn't let these idiots do their thing anymore.

"You want me to surrender?... Me?"

Zhang Zhi prepared to swing his sword once more, but he suddenly stopped, no he even took a step back. The elder person in front of him suddenly looked a lot scarier than before. He could feel the elder's power rising, it went way past the early level of core formation that he previously felt and shot up so high that he didn't even know how strong this man was.

"You damn idiot, what do you think you are doing by destroying this city!?"

The man started floating into the air, his eyes started glowing with a golden hue. Lightning bolts fired off his body and you could hear the sound of thunder as he rose upwards into the sky above.

"H-how can this be?"

These cultivators didn't really have much experience with nascent soul cultivators and Matt here was someone that was extremely close to the cultivation level of one. At this time they had mistaken the old man for an expert in that realm, he was even floating which was the staple of nascent soul cultivators.

Zhang Zhi started thinking, who could this man be. He had a similar air to him as his Patriarch, this cultivation method was a dead giveaway. But what was the relationship between this man and the glorious Patriarch he thought? In his infinite wisdom he figured it out, this was the only logical conclusion in his mind, there was only one person that this elder could be.

He quickly dropped down to his knees, his head hitting the pavement as he spoke out.

"Junior apologizes sincerely, I didn't realize who this glorious elder was!"

Matt reacted with a sharp gaze, did he finally see through him.

'Well guess the jig is up, hope I can come up with a good explanation.'

"Well, glad that you understand."

Matt nodded while Zhang Zhi replied.

"Yes, this junior didn't realize that this elder must be the illustrious master of our Patriarch!"

"Yes glad that you... wait, what?"

Chapter 118

This wasn't as silly as Matt thought it was. The cultivators here had limited knowledge about experts at the Nascent soul level. Even though Zhang Zhi was back there in the secret ground, the whole fight was quite hectic. They didn't have time to measure the power levels of those two masters that were fighting, so when Matt flexed his cultivation it could seem to be at the nascent soul level.

The other thing was the blind trust in the Patriarch that Zhang Zhi had. He would never think that Zhang Dong would take the form of an old man and just wander around the streets of this city. He thought that his Patriarch was busy cultivating or thinking about ten moves into the future of the clan.

This old man looked to have the same type of cultivation method as their Patriarch, but due to Zhang Dong increasing his expertise in all of his cultivation arts, he was stronger than he was back then in the secret ground. So this mistake wasn't as far fetched if you considered how these people operated.

"Grandmaster..."

'I guess I'll roll with it... better than explaining to them why I'm pretending to be some old fart...'

He quickly thought back to the way a lofty master should act. Should he go with a more stoic approach, or act angry as the juniors didn't give him any face. For now he just stuck his chest out proudly and played around with his long white beard, his eyes locked on the trembling core formation cultivator.

"Oh, I see that you have figured it out, little friend, took you long enough."

Zhang Zhi just trembled and started sweating, his theory came true and he was speaking to someone that was even above the Patriarch. What if this show of disrespect from him would cause trouble to Zhang Dong, what if this old man punishes his disciple for having incompetent subordinates as him? There was only one thing he could do!

Matt in the form of Wei Hung hovered up in the air, not quite sure what he should talk about but he wanted to talk about this cultivator didn't care for collateral damage at all. But before he could speak out again the man below him acted out, he drew his sword and stretched out his hand. His face was resolute and his will was unshaken as he looked at that hand of his.

"This junior has made a grave error, please let this junior offer up a hand to appease the senior's anger!"

Matt's eyes bulged out and went bloodshot as he saw the man going for a slice. He was going to sever off his entire hand a bit above the wrist, this was some devotion to the clan right there. Matt quickly activated all of his skills to get as much of a speed boost as he could, the other Zhang Clan members that were standing around the area only saw the elderly man vanish.

Zhang Zhi was aiming for his sword hand, he was quite devoted and wanted to let the old man know, that he was really apologetic. His swordsmanship was fast and decisive, but as he was feeling the cold dark blade against his forearm, it suddenly got stopped by something. This something was the elder man's hand, he grabbed the entire blade it not even being able to nick his skin.

"You damn fool!"

SMACK!

Zhang Zhi got slapped by the old man, the man quickly tasting blood as he staggered to the side. The smack wasn't serious, if Matt was serious he could probably smack the head off his neck with one hit.

"What do you think you are doing? Did you even ask if I wanted you to do this? Don't you have a small child? What would your wife and child do if their father became a cripple?"

The old man started shouting at the samurai looking cultivator, who was back down on his knees and rubbing his cheek. The other Zhang clan members just looked one from the side, not being able to add anything to the conversation and being too afraid to even try.

They just looked as the old man started lecturing their Captain. Zhang Zhi perplexed and just nodding, not being sure why the old master was mad at him for trying to show him face by cutting off his hand. But after he heard him mention his child and wife, he shrunk back. He forgot that he had his own family besides the clan to think about, maybe he was too hasty in his actions.

"J-junior was wrong, please forgive me..."

"Enough, I'm not mad at you... but you must start thinking before you act... think about other people that will suffer from your actions..."

Matt wasn't sure what he should do now, the dismemberment of limbs kind of made him forget what he was going for in this conversation.

"Listen up... those people back in the alley attacked me, they were probably related to the boy that you apprehended, think it was the Xing clan. If you are going to run this 'Police force' that your Patriarch created you need to do it right, you can't just attack people randomly... also look at that..."

The old man pointed at a spot in the distance, there stood a destroyed building that Zhang Zhi sliced apart while he was chasing the old man. Some people were standing outside of it, tears in their eyes as their home was now destroyed.

"Go pay those people for that house, or repair it! Don't forget to do the same with anything else that you destroyed!"

"Also!"

He turned to the sides, every Zhang Clan family member was trembling in their boots as the elder master swept his gaze through the area.

"Harming yourself just to give me face is forbidden! If Someone from you tries to do something like this idiot here, I'll have my disciple banish you and your closes family members from your clan, is that understood?"

Everyone just twitched and dropped to their knees, they quickly shouted 'Yes Grandmaster' as a show of respect not wanting to get kicked out from this Clan of theirs that was on a fast rise. They were gaining momentum, their Patriarch was young and strong and he could only get stronger.

"Now, no word can reach that I'm in this city, so you must all swear under an oath that you will not tell this to anyone... but don't die... dying is forbidden as well... old don't kill anyone for trying to pry into my affair... still keep it a secret..."

Matt twitched, he was glad that he changed his statement at the end. He already imagined these cultivator nuts trying to silence anyone that was asking about this so-called 'Master of the Patriarch.' They might even try to kill themselves over it if they misunderstand a situation and try to keep his secret by taking it to the grave.

All the cultivators nodded in unison and swore that they wouldn't bring this up anymore. They wanted to say that they would take this info to their death bed, but that was apparently forbidden by the elder master.

"Now... I bid you farewell..."

The man suddenly vanished, some static electricity left in the place he was standing just a moment before. The Zhang Clan members gave out sighs of relief, the old monster was finally gone and they could relax. They weren't quite sure what the Senior wanted them to do, they shouldn't talk about him which was fine, but they shouldn't protect the secret with their lives. So it was fine to talk if someone smacked them around enough that it would threaten their lives? This was quite the lax secrecy oath.

The night came to an end and the sun was rising again, the Xing Clan patriarch was looking out through a window already realizing that his men had failed in their task.

"Damn useless bunch of fools...report!"

Some other clan member that had similar looking ninja clothes as the assassins from yesterday stepped out, made a small bow with his hands clasped and started talking.

"Reporting to Patriarch, all of the men have been captured by the so-called 'Police Force' of the Zhang Clan. The scouts report that they are held in a tightly guarded facility that is protected by a defensive formation. You would need a cultivator above the core formation early stage to hope of destroying this formation as it is very advanced."

"The elder that is referred as 'The witness' is still alive, we assume that he was stronger than anticipated, probably in the core formation level. If not, then the Zhang Clan helped him and lured out men into the trap. I assure you, Patriarch, that those warriors would die sooner than speak any of this!"

Xing Deng waved the man away who in response dissolved into the shadows.

'Guess I'll have to offer them up my son...'

The man rubbed his chin, he still had his oldest son, he also had more of them so he didn't worry that much. His fatherly love only went this far, if he had to choose between one of his sons and the family business he would choose the latter any day of the week.

"Time to wait it out, but damn Zhang Clan, you'll regret this in the end..."

He was an old schemer and time was one thing that these cultivators had in spades, if he managed to reach the core formation level he would have even more. He could just wait for an opportunity to stab this clan in the back, or just hug some strong uncle's leg if he needed to. He couldn't really do much about it though unless he got the backing of the other two big families, even then the possibility, of winning was slim.

"With that Patriarch of theirs still out there, there is no hope of retaliation and they still have that Zhang Zhi, he took out that Cheng idiot."

From what they knew the Zhang Clan only had three core formation experts at the moment, Zhang Zhi, Zhang Jin and Zhang Dong. If they were hiding more somewhere was unknown but it wouldn't be odd if they had one or two more in reserve. None of these big families in Moonlight city even had one of those experts to spare.

"It's just a small matter, as long as we have the pleasure district, our wealth is secured."

The Xing Clan made their money mostly with slaves and prostitutes, they might have taken a blow with the slaves but they still had the women of the night. Those women didn't fit the slave criteria even though they were being worked in a similar way. The Xing clan had another large venture, which was being loansharks.

How it worked was like this, the women would take out a loan due to various reasons, mostly lack of food or place to stay. Then the Xing clan would hike up the percentages of the interests that came with those loans. The longer the women weren't able to pay up the interest, the longer they worked for this clan. So, it was kind of a legal way that you could keep the ladies slaving away.

They also made it sure that the women didn't earn too much. If they received a lot of monetary compensation for their work they would be able to pay back the debt too fast, but every month the interest ticked down, the longer they took to pay the Xing Clan back the longer the family could suck them dry.

The prostitutes weren't the only people that they pulled in with their loans, there were various other 'loan slaves' that they had, like ones that were used for arena fighting that was quite the popular betting addicts. He decided to at least wait till the so-called trial, wanting to see what it was all about, but just after a couple of days had passed some bad news arrived again.

"Bad news Patriarch! The Zhang Clan is buying out our loan slaves!"

Chapter 119

Matt returned to his quarters in the previous Cheng clan main house, this was the room that he was supposed to be staying at and only a couple of people knew that he was running around town. He needed to think about his police force more throughout, he only wrote down some main points he remembered from some police-themed shows back in the day.

His clan members were a bit violent in their approach, they kicked ass and took notes down later as well. This needed to change a bit, the collateral damage that some members caused while chasing down criminals was also a problem. The high-level cultivators were akin to supermen just busting through buildings, one badly placed Qi attack could cost someone's life in the near future. Injuries were already happening constantly, like when Zhang Zhi split the flying ship apart without caring for any for the slave girls on it.

'I'll need to write down a better guideline for them...also about that Xing Clan.'

He grabbed a jade slip from the side, on it was the detailed information about what that family did and where they produced all their income from.

'Hmm... slaves...prostitution...gambling...debt collecting... quite the stereotypical mafioso or yakuza bunch...'

That wasn't all that was in there, there was also information about the other families.

'Situ Clan eh? They sound like a farmaceutical company from Earth... just hiking up the prices for things that cost close to nothing, guess they are a bit better than the previous one as they don't force anyone to buy their stuff or threaten anyone. '

'Kuan Clan just sounds like a stingy landlord, though they are going a bit overboard by forcing the farmers to pay up even during drought seasons.'

The two other clans didn't sound so bad on paper, they mostly just strongarmed people to sign bad contracts or milked the populace that had nowhere else to go to for food or medicine. He would just have one of his more intelligent people crunch the numbers and see what would be a good price. It was supposed to be a good price for both parties, so the farmers wouldn't starve or the landlords wouldn't go out of business either.

It would be nice if he could replace everyone in this town with his own family members, but they didn't have the sheer numbers for that. All of these cities were large and required a lot of manpower to manage. At most he could place some trusted people here and there to manage the things from the top, just keep the other clan's up on their toes so that they don't suck the regular people dry.

'The Xing Clan is considered the largest one from these three and they are the shadiest one as well.'

He found that out just previously when he got attacked by ninjas, and they weren't dudes with blue hair but actual assassin warriors.

'Hm, maybe I should make my own ninja unit...'

He had an information and spy division, but he didn't look much into it as his grandpa was responsible for those guys. He would need to have Zhang Jin fill him in.

'I only gave him some techniques that could be used for things like that, he sounded ecstatic back then...'

He knew by now, that the cultivators were really crazy about new techniques. The moment they found something even half worthwhile they wanted to lock themselves up in a cave of months and train.

"Hmm... so should we continue with the Xing Clan... or shift our attention to the other two..."

There were plans in the works to lower the taxes, build free schools and free clinics around the city but the Zhang Clan hadn't moved against the other two clans that much. At most they inspected their stock and told them to shape up before the next one came along. It would cost quite a penny to transport food from their own town, but it would stir up the monopoly that the Kuan clan had. The Zhang Clan was also proficient in making pills, so they could slowly edge the Situ Clan out, forcing lower prices onto the market.

'Not like they can threaten us if we lower the prices, if they want to survive they will have to meet us in the middle.'

He could outright force the three families to work for him, even doing things like killing their Patriarchs if they didn't listen. But he thought that it was better to do it on more peaceful terms, he didn't want the Zhang Clan to just look like another group of bloodthirsty cultivators. The people would probably be happier if they knew that the ruling clan wouldn't just react with violence in the time of some kind of transgression.

Still, he also wanted his clan to earn their upkeep. It was always hard to find that fine line where the profit margins were high but the people working were still happy and content with their jobs. He was thinking about one certain thing that didn't really exist in this world, this thing was the weekend... and days off work.

Something like a Saturday and Sunday that were free was a foreign concept in this world, you were supposed to work all day every day or at least that what the landlords wanted you to do. What if he implemented a mandatory day off work, to spend with your loved ones or just chill.

In his previous world, things like this were already tried. A certain business owner observed and created the weekend because the workers would work harder and spend their hard-earned money back into the company that they were working in. This was a win-win situation for both parties, soon enough it was widespread and became the norm.

No one wanted to work ten or twelve hours a day for six or seven days a week. If they did that they were far too tired to spend their money on anything and just rested which was a blow for the economy.

'All up to the business owners if they give their workers a steady hourly wage, some of them have to work the whole day depending on the workload...'

He wanted to boost the people's productivity while lowering their workload, he would give them more time to enjoy the world around them while still making a profit as the workers would work harder at their jobs even though they worked fewer hours.

'This will also generate more opportunities, people will have free time on the weekends and will be able to spend all that hard earn cash!'

Most regular people weren't really able to enjoy things like theaters or concerts, not having money or free time to do that. But Matt was planning to convert that hologram technology into something more accessible, building a cinema wouldn't be that far fetched.

He had various crafting manuals, he could produce various weapon and armor pieces as well as magical accessories that shielded you from harm. It shouldn't be that hard to produce something like a camera or a screen that showed those recordings, he just needed to find the right materials and make it work on spiritual energy, he was even close to producing a prototype but it was quite bulky making it look like one of those old-timey televisions, just ten times bigger.

'But I'm getting ahead of myself, let me clean up this mess with these three families first, after they are contained I can move along with the other plans.'

He nodded to himself and placed the jade slip to the side, the thoughts of using slips like these as digital storage devices already crossing his mind.

'The Xing Clan sounds like the worse... they might be the hardest to deal with and might not want to change their outdated ways...'

He rubbed his chin while sipping on some green tea, it tasted quite nice along with the honey made from some spirit bees.

He looked back to the jade slip and brought out the information about loansharking, he was quite informed how things like these worked. They would hike up the interest rates the longer you didn't pay it back, though in his old world you would mostly have to put something down of worth so that the company lending you money had something to gain even if you didn't pay them.

'Guess the lives of these women are the thing they are after...'

There was a shortage of food and necessities in this city, everything required coins or spirit stones. People died a lot and the women were forced into taking those loans to support their families if anything happened to their husbands. Though there were other reasons, like gambling and just badly made decisions or bad investments.

Though these things were more or less legal in a sense. The people didn't have to take those loans, no one was forcing them. But not like they really had a choice, it was either this or getting thrown out of their houses, starvation or getting turned into a beggar.

Matt didn't really have anything against prostitution, he thought it was a good source of revenue for the city. He just didn't like that the working ladies weren't getting much for their time, the pimps were taking like eighty or seventy percent of that the women earned in the day. If they caught one of them trying to sell her services on the side without giving them a cut, she would be beaten up harshly.

'Should I just force them to make changes, or is there any other way...I guess we could try that...'

The escorts were low-level cultivators, mostly ranking in the ones that couldn't get past the 3rd level of Qi condensation bottleneck. So most of their loans were taken in coins.

'Gold coins are easy to come by, if it's not in spirit stones I think we can stomach it...'

Even though he didn't consider a gold coin to be much, even one was more than what a normal person could earn in a month. But if you took it into account that a gold coin didn't even compare to low grade spirit stone at all, it wasn't so bad. A lot of cultivators wouldn't even trade spirit stones for coins as they valued cultivation materials way more.

Matt had quite a lot of coins on himself, he had sold of various weapons of lower quality while bringing his crafting back up so he could cover the costs. He used up most of the spirit stone resources, but gold coins would be fine and this was an investment for the future as he was aiming to get more daily system points after getting the happiness of the citizens up.

He took out his communication jade and called Zhang Kuo, after receiving a greeting he gave out his order.

"I want you to organize something for me. Get some people to go to the pleasure district, mostly target the working girls. I want you to buy off their debts, the women will have to pay it back partially at least but lower those insane interest rates that the other clans were forcing them to pay up."

"That's not all, they can still work in their old profession but they would take most of the cut. Also set up the usual, in case they have nowhere else to go."

They had a system set up for people that had no living quarters and no families to take them in, they could stay in some Zhang Clan made shelter. They would perform some manual tasks for the clan, acting as errand boys and girls, cleaning ladies or handymen. If they showed talent in martial arts they could even be recruited into the clan.

"Well then, I'll leave you to it. As always, don't try to be too forceful."

Zhang Dong hung up as Zhang Kuo received the message. His brows showing a tint of sweat, the man seemed to be on top of things, but even he was getting tired from the strange requests that this new Patriarch was giving him, he needed an assistant.

Chapter 121

Matt while wearing his demon hunter disguise wasn't sure what to make of this, the man was bowing as a show of respect. But at the same time, he was badmouthing him, well he was badmouthing that Zhang Clan Patriarch. He was apparently an evil demonic cultivator, that raped young girls and drunk their blood during the full moon.

'Gotta give it to them, that's some imagination...'

This was clearly a ploy to get his demon hunter persona that was known for killing evil cultivators and beasts to slay Zhang Dong. The problem was that he was this Zhang Dong that they were talking about, he didn't really want to commit suicide.

'Well, I guess I can just bring them in for trying to assassinate me... I'm my own witness... but wait...'

He wasn't sure how his public image would look, they would clearly deny it. Not like he couldn't just pound those two clans to the ground any time that he wanted, the thing holding him back was his conscience and his public image. He didn't want to look like a regular tyrant for the people and this was how a dictator acted.

'Guess I could pretend that I take the offer... but make it look like the three clans hired him to kill the benevolent leader instead, bet my popularity will spike, but will I have to kill off my demon hunter persona... '

This sounded like a good chance to milk these three clans, they were probably desperate enough to give him the bulk of their wealth in spirit stones which he could use to finally get himself into that Nascent Soul Realm. The problem was how he should do it, in other novels the protagonist mostly had a clone of some sort to help them out in situations like this. At most he could fashion an automated doll, but its looks were plain it would not pass for him in any shape or form.

'I guess I could go with the smoke and mirror approach... maybe use those holograms or just plant some speakers here and there...'

He wasn't sure about his acting abilities, but the people didn't need to see the battle happening from close up. He just needed to kick up a big fuss and make the three clans believe that the two experts were fighting it out. It would be really easy to implicate the three families in the assassination attempt, so that everyone was on his side.

Matt was really surprised that he was thinking about such a scheme, normally he would find things like these too bothersome to go through with. Now, he was just chuckling inwardly thinking about the dumb looks on people's faces when he would be performing the show, he was slowly moving on from his shy shell.

He looked at the man in his disguise, his facial expression changing into one of rage and discomfort.

"Oh, is this true?"

The bowing man bowed some more and nodded.

"Yes my lord, the Zhang Clan Patriarch is a true demon!"

He turned around, making it look like he was thinking hard about something, the man could see Lei Ying-Lo from the side.

"If you are telling the truth... then I can't let this go... but it won't come cheap..."

His eyes shined slightly as he mentioned the part about the payment, he wasn't sure how much spirit stones the three clans had but he wanted them to fork it all up.

"Ah yes sir Ying-Lo, the clan leaders will discuss the pricing with you outside the city..."

Matt got the rundown by the servant, he would meet the three stooges outside in a secluded area. There they would discuss their dealings and the payment, he wouldn't budge on that one and wanted to drain as much as he could from the old man trio.

"I will inform the families that you have agreed to meet with them!"

The man quickly run away, probably happy that he got a positive reply from this scary uncle. Matt that was standing there with a jade slip in his hand, the time and place of the meeting were all in there. It wasn't that far away from Moonlight City, probably due to the fact that the three families didn't have any flying swords to travel on.

'Soon I won't even need this thing anymore...'

He looked down at the black sword he was riding on, the item would lose its purpose after he leveled up as when he did he would be able to fly around like superman.

'Though flying around like that looks kind of silly...'

He tossed the motion of flying with two fists forward back into his mind while he headed back to Moonlight City, he had to prepare for the show. He couldn't really do it alone, so he had to pull Zhang Kuo into the mix. This man performed his job quite well and in return even got some top tips from this expert Patriarch of his.

Matt noticed that the stoic glasses-wearing man sometimes made bewildered faces at him, like the time he ordered them to pay off the debt, or when he ordered to set up the free school for the kids. He was loyal but he still was an old fashioned cultivator nut, giving things out for free was something that he still didn't understand all that well.

He went back to his temporary room and took out some paper and a pen. He liked to write down his ideas and contemplate on them first. He made a short outline about what he could and couldn't do in his little scheme. He clearly couldn't have both of his personas out at the same time, some magic tricks would have to be implemented into the plan. Nothing too hard as the plan could fall through if he got too excited and made it harder for himself to pull it off.

'Think this could work... but it will be really cheesy...'

He nodded and called his trusted retainer into the room, explaining his plan in detail. Zhang Kuo already knew that Zhang Dong was the famous Demon hunter. His brows furrowed slightly as his family head started explaining what this plan was supposed to be.

"S-sir, wouldn't it be easier to just bring them in..."

The man was clearly confused, why do some strange charade when they could just bring those three family heads in for questioning. Not like they even needed to question them, with his own strength he could just order their execution or banish them from this city. No one would really ask any questions about it.

Matt, on the other hand, felt like this could be quite fun. Plus, the people would know that the three families ordered a hit on him after it all played out. If he just ordered their deaths, the people might think that he was too overbearing and not any different than all the other aristocratic like family clans.

Zhang Kuo was vetoed on the spot, Zhang Dong handed him some treasures that would be used for this charade and ordered him to prepare. He had already prepared the most important stuff for those and now just needed to go meet with the three Patriarchs that were trying to murder him.

He zoomed out of Moonlight City, the rendezvous point was in a secluded area surrounded by forest and by a lake. There was a log cabin there not used by anyone, the three families didn't want anything getting traced back to them so they set up the meeting on neutral ground.

He made sure to look extra scary this time around, he had to make them feel like he meant business. That wasn't hard though, he just needed to spill some of his aura out, his looks were already extremely menacing. He made sure to not use his lightning element or holy one, as that could have blown his cover.

He was hovering above in the clouds, he could clearly sense that there were a lot of people hiding around that log cabin. The three family heads must have placed their bodyguards around the perimeter to keep people out, but none of them would be his match. He could sense three cultivators in that small hut, they were all in the great circle of foundation establishment.

Kuan Yin, Xing Deng and Situ Rong were all waiting in that cabin. The inside looked quite nice as they made their servants clean this place up preparing it for the Demon hunter that was supposed to come soon. The three came to an agreement, they would hire this man to kill that pesky Zhang Dong.

After the man was dead, some other powerful clan could be bargained with. They wanted something similar to happen like the time where the Zhang Clan was weakened after the first expedition didn't pan out for them.

"Do you think the man will do it? It might cost quite the penny..."

Said Situ Rong while rubbing the bald part of his head, that was shining from the sweat that was gathering.

"Do we have another option? If we don't pay up now we will all be finished in a couple of years!"

Xing Deng replied, the man was hit the hardest from the three Patriarchs here. The other two made their own calculations, they would take significant losses to their fortunes if they agreed to what the Zhang Clan was planning.

"I have to agree with Brother Deng, those Zhang dogs clearly have something against us."

The old man said while fanning himself some, he also took quite the hit to his stock. They were forced to pay the farmers more, and what was this blasted weekend thing, it would just bring in more losses for them.

Their conversation was interrupted after they felt someone getting near, this someone wasn't hiding his aura at all. They had some servants standing outside, so they just waited for now. Soon the door creaked open, a large scarred man entered their field of vision, his rough appearance made goosebumps appear on their arms.

"Greetings Senior Yinglo! We thank you for listening to our plead for help!"

Kuan Yin was the first one to speak up, a bright submissive smile plastered all over his face. The other two quickly clasped their hands and bowed towards this man, they could clearly feel his overwhelming cultivation.

The man in question walked in slowly, not saying much as he just observed the three morons that had called him here.

"So, I've heard you discovered a demonic cultivator in these parts, is this true?"

Matt asked with his gruff sounding voice, the there cultivators just glanced at each other and started talking, this would be the moment of truth for them.

"Tiss so, that monster Zhang Dong is a real fiend!"

"We are sure that he has some kind of demonic treasures in his home, some of our people discovered it!"

"Yes, we even lost family members to these monsters, they never returned back home, we are afraid that they have fallen to some kind of demonic ritual!"

The three started talking, trying to convince this man to act without asking too many questions. They had more than just words to back it up though, one of them pulled out some kind of curved dagger. The weapon was clearly radiating demonic energies, Matt was surprised after he grasped it.

"Our people managed to find this ceremonial dagger in one of the Zhang Clan compounds, then we quickly tried to inform you about it, Senior. Your fame precedes you, we are just simple cultivators we have no way of defending ourselves against such a strong demonic cultivator like the Zhang Patriarch, please aid us!"

"I'm sure there are more of these foul treasures in the city, but we weren't able to uncover the whole plot of that demonic fiend!"

The three were quite crafty, this wasn't the only demonic artifact that they had. They had their ways of doing things, bribing some servants wasn't hard. They had planted various demonic treasures in the buildings that the Zhang Clan members were using, they were hidden there so that when this cultivator did his own research, he would confirm their story.

This wasn't anything new to Matt, as his senses were quite high so he noticed the strange artifacts getting placed around the buildings in the city. They were all low level treasures, that would be easy to dispose of. Moonlight city didn't have its defensive formation updated yet, so something like this could happen.

'You crafty foxes...'

He just nodded for now, while rubbing his chin.

"If what you say is true... then the man must die..."

The three just nodded, their scheme seemed to be working for now.

"But... I'll need a substantial payment in spirit stones for it, this Zhang Dong won't be an easy opponent..."

They all nodded once more, already knowing that it would be costly to hire this man, but it was already a miracle that they found someone that would face that monster of a Zhang Patriarch.

"I'll check if there really are demonic treasures or cultivators first, you have a day to get the payment ready. Hm, two hundred thousand low grade spirit stones should cover the expense...I'll take one hundred thousand as a downpayment, sounds fair?"

The three men almost collapsed onto the ground after they heard the price.

"S-senior... please show mercy... that price is a bit..."

Kuan Yin's bald head shined even brighter as he tried to plead for a lower price.

"What? Don't have it? Fighting someone of that level won't be easy... you don't need to pay all of it in spirit stones, you can cover the rest with treasures or other materials like beast cores. You have a day to get it all ready!"

The man snorted and then walked out of the cabin. The two hundred thousand stones were about the amount he needed to get a million system points. Before he would need half of that, but the system gave him fewer points now. This price was something that the three old schemers should be able to pay up, but they would probably need to empty all of their reserves, this was something he was counting on.

'You leeched this city for decades, now it's time to pay up!'

Chapter 122

The door shut behind the demon hunter, the servants outside just bowed and looked as the expert jumped into the air. A big black sword appeared out of thin air under his feet and then he took off into the clouds, making the people watching envious of this amount of power. The three Patriarchs were left in the cabin in distress as the amount they were thinking was about half of what the man was asking for.

"Damn... this man might be even worse than the Zhang Clan leader... and he wants it upfront? What if he fails, how will we get our spirit stones back?"

"He didn't look like he would take the job otherwise..."

"Luckily we don't need to use only spirit stones for it..."

They huddled up, they needed to split the expense three ways and none of them wanted to pay more than they had to. They got their accountants on the job, this was an amount that they could stomach somehow but if the man failed they would be finished. If they cleaned up most of their inventory they could gather most of it, at least they only needed to give him the first part upfront, the rest could be gathered later.

"Hope both of them kill each other!"

They grumbled to themselves, in reality, they could somehow recover from the losses if they just worked with the Zhang Clan normally. They would not earn as much as before, but not like they would end up poor. They would still be wealthy, but their pride wouldn't allow them to work it out with the other party, they would rather risk it all and come out on top than cower in fear below the Zhang family.

While the three families were scattering to gather all the resources the demon hunter flew into town. He used his Wei Hung persona to move around town and discovered various demonic artifacts around the city. They were mostly low-level mortal weapons, probably the only thing these types of clans could get.

'Still, they got to some of the hired help... or they already had them in the bag from the start...'

This was a new city they were now running, they needed the help of the locals for various tasks. It wouldn't be surprising if some of the servants and workers had ties to one of the three larger families. Maybe they were in debt, a promise of lowering that would probably make them do this in a heartbeat.

'Not like these people feel very thankful to my clan just yet... have to give him some time...'

He didn't blame the ignorant masses that much, things just worked like that here. That didn't mean that he wouldn't punish anyone if they were caught doing it. He would give the people that helped the three families one more chance, after his little act that was about to happen he would take off the training wheels.

'If I was a real demon hunter I might have even believed these people.'

Without doing much research Zhang Dong could fit a demonic cultivator template. He went missing from the clan for ten long years. He returned with some strange cultivation method that made him insanely more powerful than others. He also was managing to burst through realms like crazy being now in the great circle only after two years.

Demonic cultivators were known for sucking away the lifeforce of other cultivators which prompted them to mostly have a higher cultivation realm than your regular cultivator. The downsides to these types of methods were, first the body count left, then the practitioner's psychological problems. The demonic energies would corrupt their very being and soul, making them act like psychopaths that didn't care about anyone but themselves.

Zhang Dong was also rarely seen, this was due to him spending times cooped up in his crafting abode. When he actually decided to go out, he used a disguise like he was using now. So he no one really knew what he was up to these days, but not like other Patriarchal types of cultivators were very social either.

'Okay, let me get this over with.'

He removed all of the demonic artifacts that were placed around the city, then went back to the meeting spot after the day had passed. The three family heads were waiting for him, each one of them having a spatial ring with various treasures in them. Matt counted about sixty thousand in low grade spirit stones, the rest were other various materials like spirit herbs, metals and beast cores.

"We will need some time to gather more assets, I'm sure after Senior defeats that foul demonic cultivator, we will have everything ready for you!"

One of the men mentioned while handing over his clan's spatial ring, his hand quivering as he was parting with the fortune.

"Hm... I'll count it later... should be enough in here as a down-payment, but don't forget to gather the rest after the deed is done!"

The men nodded, they weren't planning on cheating the man they were far too afraid of his power to even try that. They were curious how the demon hunter would handle this, would he lure the Zhang Clan Patriarch out. Maybe he would wait for him to leave, he probably would be going back to Spirit Spring City sooner or later. They all thought that such an expert had to have his ways of taking care of high profile targets like this.

They looked as he rose up from the ground on his black sword and just flew back towards Moonlight City. The three looked at each other, wondering if he would use some kind of disguise to hide, he wouldn't just go and attack him outright, now would he?

Little did they know that Zhang Dong was the demon hunter, and he was planning to implicate them in the hit.

'Well, time to get this show on the road.'

The three clan heads were still in the forest, returning from the meeting place at the log cabin. Suddenly they could hear a booming voice, this voice was familiar as it belonged to the man that they just hired. He was shouting while using his Qi to make his voice travel all around the area of the city and it even reached them all the way back here.

"Zhang Dong come out! I know who you are, it's no use hiding!"

Everyone looked up into the sky and stopped anything that they were doing. They spotted an angry-looking cultivator in a black robe hovering right above Moonlight City. He was clearly here to cause trouble and apparently he was after the Zhang Clan head.

"I know that you are a foul demonic cultivator, the Situ Clan, Xing Clan and the Kuan Clan have provided me irrefutable evidence! You must be cleansed by this Lei Ying-lo!"

The Moonlight City residence started whispering among each other, they heard the man's name and instantly knew that the name belonged to a famous demon hunter.

"C-could it be true?... but wait... this sounds fishy..."

"Yeah... would those three families even tell the truth..."

"Sounds like a hoax!"

The people didn't trust those three clans one bit, there was far to much shady stuff around those three clans. While the people were whispering, the man on the flying sword looked down as if he could hear what they were talking about.

"What? You don't believe me? Why would those three established families lie to me? What could they possibly gain from this? Not like they are losing bountiful amounts of spirit stones due to the new laws or anything like that... Yes, no reason at all!"

The citizens looked at each other, their brows twitching after the man continued to talk. Was he here to fight the Zhang Clan Patriarch or talk badly about the three families. He was also contradicting himself, speaking that the three clans were good people and then mentioning a good reason why they would want to kill Zhang Dong.

"They clearly hired him to kill the Zhang Clan Patriarch... but what a strange fellow..."

The people whispered some more, the whole thing was quite odd.

"Now, Zhang Dong come out from your hiding place and let our fists do the talking! I'll see for myself if you are a demonic cultivator during out battle, you won't be able to hide your foul energies from this Lei Yinglo!"

More people started gathering, a lot of people from the Police force were dispatched but they were sweating bullets as they knew that they stood no chance against this powerful uncle. Zhang Zhi was also moving towards that area, he had to protect the good name of his patriarch but before he could speak out he heard Zhang Dong's voice instead.

"Oh, why isn't it the famous demon hunter, I'm quite intrigued that those three fools got you to agree to this... But if it's a battle that you want, then a battle you will have!"

The voice was coming out of the old Cheng Clan main building, the Zhang Clan leader was probably somewhere in it but people couldn't really see him.

"Patriarch, you should leave this to me!"

Zhang Zhi shouted out, he wanted to at least face this man in battle first even if he would die the Patriarch could perhaps see the man's fighting style, this could lead to a win later on when he faced him.

"No need! What kind of person would I be if I let one of my junior members fight my battles for me?"

"Demon hunter, face me behind the mountains in the East, we can't get the city people involved in our fight, there would be massive casualties!"

"Promise me this fellow Daoist, if I lose you will leave my Zhang Clan alone and this city as well, they have suffered enough!"

Zhang Zhi got denied and Zhang Dong scored a couple of points with the public as he appeared to be worried about their well being. It was a given if two top core formation experts fought above a large city like this, there would be casualties and destruction.

Zhang Dong's voice that everyone was hearing was of course done with a speaker type treasure. He was holding on to the microphone while being in his demon hunter persona. No one could really see what he was doing, he just covered his mouth with his hand and spoke into the little treasure that produced the sound. The speaker was placed in a good spot and Zhang Kuo was guarding it, making sure that the plan doesn't get discovered by other people.

"Very well, you have my word. I'm only here for demonic cultivators."

Soon, Lei Yinglo agreed and headed over behind those mountains leaving the city airspace. Then a sudden boom of thunder could be heard followed by a flash of light up in the sky. The people turned to it out of instinct, they saw the Zhang Clan Patriarch hovering up in the sky, golden lightning shooting out of his body as he also flew towards those mountains.

Matt used an old magic trick, kicking up a fuss at one spot. While everyone was trying to find the source of the noise he quickly changed his appearance while being above the clouds where no one could see him. He then used his movement technique to get into that spot in a flash, making it seem as if he took off from the old Cheng Clan main building.

Everyone heard the exchange, the three families were in distress as the cat was out of the bag and everything depended on that blasted demon hunter now. Why did he have to tell everyone that they were the ones that provided that evidence? It was obvious that they just wanted to use that as an excuse to kill this man off.

Suddenly a loud booming sound could be heard, some strange beams of light rose up into the air as people could feel an overbearing aura flying their way.

"Oh no, they are fighting... what strength!"

"Can the Zhang Patriarch win? That Demon hunter is really famous..."

"What are those three clan's planning... hope Senior Dong wins!"

While the people were talking among each other, Matt was punching some boulders into dust. He was kicking up a storm, shouting out loudly. He hoped that his mock battle with himself would come off as realistic, otherwise he might get embarrassed if his super sneaky scheme came to light.

'Think I need to work on my lines, they were quite corny...also how long should I keep this up...'

Chapter 123

Everyone from the Zhang Clan gathered in the city and they were looking in the direction of the faraway mountains. The aura fluctuations were quite chaotic and reached the pinnacle of core formation which made the regular Qi condensation people shake in their boots.

"What a battle, shame that we can't see anything..."

The common cultivators could profit when two experts fought each other. They could see their techniques and get inspired which would allow them to reach a higher realm. So wanting to be there to see how those two monsters performed was quite enticing, but it was also very dangerous, one bad step and you could be flattened by a Qi strike.

"You're not half bad, Zhang Clan Patriarch!"

"You're not a slouch either, Sir. Demon Hunter!"

They were a bit perplexed that they could hear the two men talking, it was as if they were shouting out in the direction of the City or something. Which was just what Matt was doing, both of his hands placed in a cone shape, his shouts were accompanied by some Qi so that his voice would travel far and wide.

Luckily Zhang Kuo was smart enough to order the clan members to set up a perimeter outside the city, so that no nosy person would bother their Patriarch's scheme which looked as if it was working. After some back and forth, the people started cheering out Zhang Dong's name.

They had considered the pros and cons and they came to the conclusion that it would be a travesty with the Zhang head perished here. What would come of these tax cuts and new laws, would the other three families gain back their position and bully them once more? An even more ruthless clan could even show up, which would mean their downfall.

The three big Moonlight City clan heads were standing outside the forest, they were afraid to return afraid that the Zhang clan people would apprehend them the moment they tried to sneak in.

"Blasted idiot! Did something eat his brain! Why does he have to implicate us too!"

They were pulling their hair out, they didn't think that the famous demon hunter would just waltz into the city and demand a duel with his assassination target. This would be fine, but he had to babble out that he was coaxed into it by them, a child would figure out during that speech that they were the ones that hired him.

"Calm down... if he beats him then only that other core formation expert will be left... Judging by his temper he will attack the demon hunter..."

"Yeah if he kills all of their core formation experts we will be in the clear..."

The three talked while hiding behind some large trees, the loud thunderous sounds could be heard even from the place they were in. Their conversation got interrupted though, by someone they were talking about.

"Oh? the other expert? Did you mean me?"

Zhang Zhi was hovering on a sword above the group of cultivators, Zhang Kuo already filled him in on where the three stooges were hiding at. The location was provided by Zhang Dong, but no one besides Kuo would know about that little detail.

"Don't move, I'll cut you where you stand if you try to run!"

Zhang Zhi pulled out his sword and held it over his shoulder, the long blade glistering with water Qi which made everyone below him gulp in fright. The man in question wasn't in on the plan, so he was still on edge as he thought that his clan head was fighting a ferocious opponent. He had no way of telling how strong that Senior Yinglo was, he was truly astonishing.

The glorious Zhang Dong at this moment was leaning against some rocks, here and there he fired off a bolt of lightning from his finger which caused more noise than damage. He was munching on a meat bun and looking at the sky, quite relaxed. Here and there he would shout out or produce a loud roar which would make the people back in the city gasp in worry.

'Hm... is this enough? How long do experts fight for... I don't really want to blow these mountains up for this silly play I'm doing.'

He glanced around, the area looked quite silent as every creature in a ten-kilometer radius had scattered away. He was hoping that they don't cause trouble for some villagers or something, he'll have to send out a squad of warriors to check that out.

'Guess the Demon hunter will have to go out with a bang...'

He wouldn't kill of his other person but he had to make him lose in some shape or form. He had one ability that didn't require him to be in the vicinity of it so he would go with that.

The people in the city suddenly felt a surge of Qi, the power was truly immense. Out from behind those mountains they saw a bright golden dragon emerging, it was made purely out of golden divine lightning energies. It was truly immense a couple of kilometers in length and powered with Zhang Dong's Qi.

"Look... what is that! It's flying into the air..."

"That's a giant dragon... wait is that a Daoist magic of some sort?"

The dragon was roaring out and chasing someone on a sword, the man looked beaten up quite a bit his hair and clothes were disheveled.

'Is that the Demon Hunter? Looks like he is fleeing from that dragon...'

The dragon shot of lightning bolts all around the area and flew right after its enemy. The fleeing cultivator couldn't shake it off as they danced around in the sky. Finally, the people gasped as they saw the dragon's mouth closing on the man, the cultivator dressed in black holding that mouth open as the two flew up into the air.

The man looked like he was holding on for his life, not letting the dragon construct close its large maw on him. The two flew straight up into the air and vanished behind some clouds. Just a couple of moments later there was an explosion, the shockwave reaching the people standing outside and made their hair flutter in the wind.

Everyone started looking and running to see what happened, the clouds were blocking the view but the explosion kicked up quite the strong wind which blew the white sky marshmallows to the side. The revealed the demon hunter, he was still alive but the top of his robe was no more.

He was floating up in the air, covered in red which indicated that he took quite the hit from that.

"You're quite a strong fellow Daoist Dong, this is my loss... I have made a mistake you are clearly not a demonic cultivator, it would be impossible for a foul demonic cultivator to possess such divine abilities like these..."

"That's fine, we all make mistakes fellow Daoist Yinglo. You may leave with this experience, it would be a travesty if our land lost such a talented master such as yourself."

A disembodied voice came from somewhere sounding like the Zhang Clan Patriarch, apparently, the demon hunter lost but Zhang Dong was letting him go.

"My humble thanks, I should have known that those three clans were up to no good and placed those demonic artifacts to make you look bad!"

"Yes, don't worry my clan will take care of that."

The two chatted for a bit before the Demon hunter swished away, he flew high up into the clouds and vanished from sight. Matt would wait for the coast to be clear before returning back to his quarters. Zhang Zhi and the others would take care of those three family heads their businesses would probably fall into his clutches now.

The three Patriarchs tried to defend themselves, accusing Lei Yinglo instead. They proclaimed that he was the mastermind behind everything and that he even stole their money after threatening them. They would have a lot of time to explain everything in the court, the lie detection devices had proven to be quite the handy commodity which made the trials progress at a rapid pace.

You just had to ask the right 'yes' or 'no' questions, which forced the truth out one way or the other. The only way to circumvent this procedure was not to talk at all, but almost no one could stomach that pain. This might feel like it was a bit tyrannical, more or less torture. But it got the job done and the truth came out easily.

Still, the device wouldn't kill a person a safety device was put in place after the death warriors that the Zhang Clan captured wouldn't talk. They lit up like Christmas trees from the high voltage and almost died at the court hearing. If you refused to talk would just be incarcerated with no way of getting out, so there was no reason to take the pain unless you were covering for someone.

Matt made sure to write out the penalties for any transgression, he knew how murderous these cultivation nuts were. He didn't want them killing people for stealing food or some coin. The crime would fit the bill, the death penalty would exist for certain nut jobs like the demonic cultivators or cultists. Mostly you would get a jail sentence with some hard labor added on to it.

Matt returned to his quarters after the night came, he was uninjured as the blood was fake. It was a contained explosion the Qi blast that resulted from it was dispersed into the air.

The city seemed quite peaceful most of the goons and thug types were too afraid to cause trouble after what happened this day. The police were patrolling the city and the pleasure district was quite barren, it would take some time before some of the more raunchy establishments resumed with their work.

He took a sip from his tea and sat down on a large beanbag pillow, he had one made just so he could laze around.

'Well, I'm making progress the daily points are going up!'

He looked through his system window, the city was progressing and he could see the red area's changing from red to yellow, yellow areas going blue and blue areas changing to a nice shade of green. This showed him that things were improving, getting everything into a nice blue color was the least he wanted to achieve, all green would be just a nice bonus.

The city needed more work though, it was one thing to make it safer for the citizens and lowering the taxes to keep them happy. It was another thing to provide them with a steady job. This city needed something that they could use for profit. Like Spirit Spring City that had the Zhang Clan which had a good business in pill making.

There was a plan of bringing some pill making masters over here to train people, setting up another division that would produce more income. There also was a plan in making other things, like daily necessities like plumbing. The construction of factories that would hire people to produce parts was already on the way. This would be a long term plan, but they were hoping to replace some outdated products with some easily manufactured treasures that worked on spiritual energy.

'Well, guess it's time to go back to Spirit Spring, wonder how things are going back there...think grandpa sais something about a clan get together or something...'

'He said that it was for the junior members... sounded like some tournament, probably to show off your disciples.'

Matt looked at the ring that he was holding, in it were the spirit stones and loot that he got from the three clans. He then looked at his current amount of points, a bright grin appearing on his face.

'Well, thing gramps can just go there instead of me, think it's time to get ready to reach a new level!'

He calculated that if he grabbed the remaining spirit stones that those three stooges offered him, he would have enough to absorb and get those ten million points. He needed to return to his home city and get ready, he would soon be in the nascent soul level he needed look over those nascent soul techniques he got from that secret ground. There was also something that he wanted to talk about with his two friends Huo Qiang and Feng Liena.

'Well, that Bankei guy wasn't that bad, can bring him over too...that last guy felt a bit opportunistic...will have to think about that one some more...'

'Well, guess I'll head out in the morning and tell gramps that they should go without me. I'll just tell him that I'm busy with cultivating and can't be bothered. Gotta love the perks of being the clan leader, can shove babysitting onto others, he he.'

'But I guess if I'm going to talk to those two, I should think about a good name first...'

The man continued sipping his green tea while looking at the system screen, thinking that after he rose up to the Nascent Soul level, things would get hectic.

Chapter 124

A month had passed since the Zhang Clan recaptured their old city. At the moment the clinic people were bowing to an old man that had a fu manchu mustache and beard. They were giving him their farewells as he was leaving the clinic and leaving it to a new physician instead. He had stayed in the city for a bit longer, making sure that the police station was up and working correctly.

He wasn't sure if his people would be as lenient as he hoped them to be, so he made sure to stay and correct them during the judging processes as well. They weren't perfect but it was in working condition, he would check up on them later but it looked like they were doing fine and sticking to the guidelines that he had written down.

Thanks to the changes in the city, the Zhang Clan mine enterprise had gotten quite a bit more workers and they were quite cheap. The of course were the incarcerated criminals, now wearing slave collars, some of them having their cultivation crippled or lowered. Matt made sure that the criminals actually earned their keep and not just lazed around in prisons bored out of their minds.

It was time to move on, he nodded at the workers and headed out his next stop would be the new Zhang Clan estate which was now occupied by Zhang Zhi the new city mayor who was also the police chief. His amazon wife had already moved here along with their child, he was just here to bid the two farewell.

"Zhang Zhi, I'll be leaving this city to you, be sure not to destroy it too much like last time..."

He chuckled to himself, the samurai styled man blushed a bit as he recalled the day that he destroyed a couple of houses while chasing this Patriarch's 'Master'.

"Don't worry about Master, you probably won't see him again, he likes to keep to himself, so no need to feel down about it."

He gave the man a reassuring pat on the shoulder and a Patriarch brand smile to go with it. A small energetic one-year-old was getting held up by a large lady, Matt just petted her head which made the toddler smile.

"Patriarch, you should go visit the old Matriarch once in a while, she used to talk quite about your time in the secret ground before I left the old Clan."

Zhang Daiyu said while holding the child in her hands, she was previously a member of the Feng clan but in this world women took on the names of the clan's of their husbands.

"Oh yes, didn't want to bother her too much, I bet she is busy cultivating and all..."

Matt gave out a weak laugh, not really knowing how to reply. He was somewhat interested in the Feng Clan Matriarch, but he didn't really know how to court her. He had zero dating experience and the women in this world were far different than the ones back on Earth.

"Oh, think she should be attending the Dao Festival at Jade Grass city, they always host it every five years and all the clans attend it, you should go visit it, Patriarch."

The woman gave Matt a little wink before heading out with her child, he soon bade both her and her husband farewell as he was ready to head out.

He already knew about the festival, but to be precise it was more of a tournament for the junior's to attend to it was also quite a popular betting event. It was more or less a place to show of the skills of the younger generation, the age cut of was at twenty-one. His two disciples were going to compete in it, along with some other young members that med it to the foundation establishment level.

You could compete at the age of sixteen, but no one was counting on you to win. Reaching the foundation establishment stage before the age of twenty was quite rare, but not that difficult if you had a clan backing you with cultivation resources. Zhang Dong gave the two the okay to take part in the tournament, but he would probably miss it as he wanted to finally upgrade himself to the nascent soul level.

He counted the resources he had and came to the conclusion that after absorbing all of those spirit stones, he would probably need to wait a couple of days. After that, the system would give him enough passive points from the clan building section. He didn't really want to go there and be stuck in some foreign town, this was quite the serious jump in power which needed to be done in secret.

He knew that the Dark Palm Sect goons would be knocking on his door if they found out. He had just the spot to level up though, it was in the medallion treasure that blocked out any energies from sipping out of it. He could upgrade himself in there, then train some nascent soul techniques.

'I'll probably be able to craft a Heaven grade weapon after I jump that realm'

To make a heaven grade weapon you needed a couple of things, first were the materials that were very hard to come by as those sects liked to buy or steal them off everyone. The other thing was that it was extremely hard to produce a weapon of a higher realm than at what the blacksmith was at. It would be possible with some external help or some specialized treasures that fed the crafter spiritual energy, that was required to produce a higher-tiered item.

So you would need like a team of core formation experts providing spiritual energy to the master blacksmith that was forging the weapon, or substitute it with some item that gave that crafter the required Qi energy for the crafting process.

Also, heaven grade items were a lot harder to process for a weaker cultivator, took quite a bit of time to hammer that special spirit ingot into shape. It was even harder if you didn't have a hammer that was also in the heaven grade, thus it was much easier to try it after reaching the nascent soul realm.

Matt headed out, his flying sword was upgraded to a perfect graded earth treasure and with the boost in his cultivation he could make the trip in under a day now. He could probably do it even faster if he actually pushed his cultivation to the limit, but he wasn't that much in a hurry.

The people in the villages that saw him wooshing by just bowed out of respect, eyes wide open as the passing man produced shocking thunderous sounds. He made sure to fly high up in the sky, if he did it close to the ground he could do some damage to the fields and livestock.

He left Moonlight City early in the morning and arrived at Spirit Spring City early in the night, the familiar scenery filling his field of vision as he made his return.

'Still quite the sight for sore eyes!'

He breathed in the Qi rich air, the many springs in the city were glowing with light along with all the lanterns. The place looked the best at night, the illumination made it look quite otherwordly. He slowed down his descent, taking in the sights no one stopping him, the guards just bowed and turned their heads and went back to work.

This city was his home and he was slowly treating it like that. The people also started growing on him, his old grandpa was quite the funny character even at this age he was sneaking out into the night trying to woo the young ladies that fell for his charade. He tried talking him out of it, but in return he got bombarded with questions about his own relationship problem.

After he was settled in at his Patriarch position he was always bombarded by his Clan members with the question about getting married. His grandpa wanted an heir to the throne or something, he even got many marriage proposals from other Clans. His friend Huo Qiang was quite forceful, trying to push one of his sisters on him.

The only clan from the area that didn't send any eloping requests was the Feng Clan, that was due to the fact that the person that was suited to marry him was the Matriarch herself. She blocked any schemes that her granny had about sending the letters, Feng Maling finally gave up on that notion and just tried to bring it up whenever she met anyone from the Zhang Clan that could pass the message on.

Matt was the type of person that the more you bothered him with something, the less he wanted to do it. So he locked himself up training his skills for the past year, trying to evade the looming danger of marriage and responsibilities.

He descended into the main hall, the spirit water gushing all around him and revitalizing his soul. He expected his two disciples to pop out and ask him some questions, the two buggers always kept nagging him for pointers and insights into their Dao. Now that he actually took the time to practice his techniques he was able to point the two in the right direction, that B+ potential wasn't just for show as the two absorbed the knowledge like sponges. Luckily training and cultivation was a slow process, so he didn't have to spend that much time with the two kids.

The one to greet him this time around was his cousin and the mother of his disciples.

"Greetings Patriarch, glad that you made it back, how was Moonlight City?"

They chatted for a while, he found out that he just missed them by a couple of hours the kids and other clan members headed to Jade Grass City for that festival thing.

"The two were quite saddened that you didn't come with them, but don't worry they know that their master is a busy man. Also don't worry, the spear arrived and Xue'er was quite happy with it."

"Hah, well glad that they are keeping their noses out of trouble."

Zhang Dong replied while talking to his family members, the woman was close to reaching the core formation level due to the betterment in the cultivation techniques and her latent talent.

"Can't be helped, but I'll give them a little surprise after they return, think that the festival will take a week or two, right?"

Zhang Jie nodded and wondered what this surprise would be, the two parted ways soon enough and Matt headed back to his room. He jumped into his cushy bed and looked up to the ceiling. His eyes on that status page as he was counting down the days till he hit that ten million.

He already had a couple of magic techniques that he wanted to learn, he already absorbed the knowledge thanks to his system but performing techniques meant for a nascent soul cultivator could harm a core formation practitioner so he couldn't really train them just yet.

One of those skills was a giant sword formation, he would summon thousands of Qi blades that shredded into his opponent. The sword formation had some variations but was quite draining. There was one ability that let you summon a gigantic lightning bird, it looked like a phoenix only made from electricity.

The old techniques could also be upgraded and used, his Avatar Form would reach new heights and the condensation technique would probably allow him to momentarily fight even stronger foes. He just needed to wait a couple of days for his points to gather, he had already absorbed all the spirit stones and beast cores that he could and now it was time to wait. But not like he was in a rush, there wasn't anything dire happening at the moment and the kids were out of the house so he had lots of time to train and get stronger.

"Soon..."

Chapter 125

Half a day before the Patriarch of the Zhang Clan returned, his family members were all packed and ready to leave. They were slowly boarding the large flying vessel. This flying ship wasn't the same one that they used when going to the secret ground, it was a new and improved version with more space and better defensive formations.

This one looked like an elongated galleon, the characteristic dragon head was at the bow of the ship. This flying contraption also lacked any forms of sails and was propelled thanks to spiritual energy and something called a floating stone that was placed in the middle of the ship as its core. The various formations etched into the spirit wood would propel it forward while placing the cultivators inside in a thin membrane. The membrane was more of a shield that kept the winds out during a fast flight, it was even strong enough to repel cannon fire. Though there was a limit on how much damage it could take and would give out under prolonged bombardment.

There were cannons lined up on the side, the crew knew well how to use them in the times of battle. The middle part of the ship still had a steering wheel, but this flying galleon wasn't made for fast maneuvers as it was mostly designed to go forward in a straight line.

At this time Zhang Xue and Liu were sighing, they were expecting their master to come back to Moonlight City and come on this trip with them. The two of them didn't get to see their master all that often, most of the time he handed them a new technique here and there, with his teaching method they could learn the basics of the new techniques in a flash.

He was a very busy man though, they didn't get too see him often and he vary rarely gave them practical lessons. Most of them consisted of them waiting for him to show up and then getting left with a splitting headache during the transfer of knowledge via his index finger. They were quite grateful that they gained so much knowledge, but the two wanted to get closer to their uncle never having time to just chat or repay him in any shape or form.

This was why they were looking forward to the Dao Festival in Jade Grass City, it was held every five years and it was more or less a spot to show of your young disciples to the world. They wanted to make him proud by winning it, or at least making it into the top ten. There were no age brackets, so a sixteen-year-old could be facing someone five years older, that was quite the difference in experience.

The two had quite a high opinion of their Patriarch's skills. This was confirmed when they fought against their peers that were sticking to the water-based Zhang Clan techniques. Those techniques didn't stand a chance against theirs, even though they were also refined by their Patriarch.

"Wish Master wasn't always so busy all the time..."

Zhang Xue pouted a bit while looking at some people that were carrying provisions onto the ship, her brother standing next to her the two youths looking quite different than they used to.

"Don't be like that sister, he is the clan head, we are lucky that he even agreed to teach us."

Zhang Liu replied but he wasn't that convinced in his own words, longing to be praised by his Master that was the strongest person in the clan.

The youth changed through these two years, mostly due to practicing that special body refining skill. His frame changed and he gained quite the attractive jawline and muscular body shape that quite a lot of ladies were found of.

On the other hand, the Sylph physique that Zhang Xue was practicing turned her into an otherworldly beauty, her features turned from cute ones to more refined ones, her figure got enhanced quite a bit too boot. Whenever she walked she would make the men and boys crane their necks in her direction, but luckily most knew who her Master was and were far too scared to approach her or try something funny.

The two were quite popular in their home city, but neither of them showed an interest in the opposite sex. The two just were quite the cultivation junkies and their Master was just feeding them more and more skills just to get them to leave him alone while he himself immersed himself in his own cultivation and crafting.

"I heard that Master was going to be returning today, but he must have been held up by something..."

"What, are you not happy with me coming in his stead?"

Zhang Jin made his appearance, the old man seemed invigorated he had broken into the middle stage of core formation and the late stage wasn't a dream anymore. The improved cultivation techniques that his grandson gave him were working wonders on his old bones. The downside of his recent boost in vigor was his attempts in courting more women, due to this the men of the family looked at this elder with awe while the women held him in contempt.

"It's not like that grandpa..."

The two smiled at the older man who just moved onto the ship, his arrival indicated that they would be taking off quite soon. The two nodded and headed inside, they weren't the only promising youths from the Zhang Clan that were on board there were other participants even some of their old friends from the 9th Platoon, but people like Zhang Ai and Zhang Teng wouldn't be making it as they were busy with their police work at this time.

Zhang Jin moved to his cabin before liftoff, Zhang Dong's female retainer Zhang Ya was waiting for him just to check up some things before they all left.

"Grand Elder, are you sure that it's wise to keep the nature of the Dao Festival a secret from the Patriarch, he doesn't seem to be informed about it that well."

The old man looked at the lovely retainer and rubbed his chin before replying.

"Yes, this will be for the best."

He paused for a moment before continuing with his answer.

"Dong'er isn't that good with politics and he doesn't seem to care much about face... It will be better if he doesn't go to that city..."

"I'm afraid that his kind heart could be his undoing..."

"Don't worry, I'll be there nothing bad will happen or my name isn't Zhang Jin!"

The woman waited for a moment before cupping her fists and walking away, being the Patriarch's personal retainer she didn't like keeping secrets from him. But deep inside she too thought that the new clan head was a bit too soft. He very rarely showed off his superiority, if he did it felt kind of forced. You wouldn't notice it normally but if you stayed around him for a prolonged time, his act would start to fall apart.

The two parted, the ship started floating up and everyone outside of it was ordered to step back, the close families came to the dock area to wave at the promising youths that would be taking part in the friendly exchange. Though this was a friendly competition, some rivalities came to be during it, things could even turn bloody.

Sometimes deaths occurred, the cultivators in this word took things like honor and respect very seriously. If someone was defeated by a person that was seen as someone weaker or of lower status it would be quite a hit to the face of the defeated cultivator and their whole family. Sometimes disputes broke out outside the ring, even the seniors fought sometimes with each other when their pupils suffered an embarrassing defeat.

The Zhang Clan wasn't afraid though, they had gained some fame lately mostly thanks to their Patriarch. They also had some backing now in the form of the Huo and Feng clan, so anyone from the clan's there would think twice before trying to start anything with them.

The people cheered at the youths that just waved from the flying ship that was leaving.

"Show them what the Zhang Clan is made of!"

"Make us proud!"

"Be a Zhang!"

People kept shouting while the junior clan members held their noses up high, they were the elite members of their generation heading off to battle the other strong families. They were in high spirits, their techniques were all overhauled by their new clan head and they reached new heights.

The ship's speed wasn't all that great, at maximum, it could go at the speed of a core formation middle stage cultivator if you overheated the engines it could reach the late stage. It would take a couple of days to reach the destination, Jade Grass City city was located a bit further away than Moonlight City was and it was a neutral zone not ruled by any particular clan.

There was a reason for that, it was under the control of the ruling sect in the area, the Dark Palm sect in particular. This was mostly the reason that it was picked as the gathering spot, as the weaker clans felt that the stronger clans wouldn't do something overbearing if they were being watched by the sect overlords that ruled the land.

The Dark Palm sect members stationed there weren't really the core members though, they were mostly composed of outer sect disciples that didn't really have any pull in it. Due to this, the sect people acted a lot more snobby as they had an inferiority complex that came from the fact that they were outer sect disciples. Because of this they always found a reason to show of, or act as if they had something stuck up their posterior. But they were still part of the large sect, so the people that were exposed to this behavior had to always give them face.

There was about a week till the competition started, but it was advised to arrive a couple of days early. There were some procedures that every clan had to go through, each competitor had to get a number assigned to them and there would be a preliminary test heald before the fighting started.

The tests were quite easy, there were various treasures that measured the cultivator's strength, Qi amount and there was even a course to measure your agility. This was a must as if they let just anyone participate in the competitions they could spend a month or more. This world was large and the number of cultivators was immense. The number of small clans was quite immense and everyone could participate if they made it through the preliminary round.

This was a big chance for the smaller clans to shine. The large sect had their members stationed there and even though they were just outer sect disciples, there were some sect elders with some pull. If a junior member showed some promise it wasn't odd for them to get picked as a disciple by one of the elders. If they were exceptionally talented they would be sent to the main sect area to train, the ender that the disciple belonged too would be praised and rewarded accordingly for finding a talented person for the sect.

While the clans and their contestants were slowly gathering into their flying vessels a peculiar scene was playing out in the city that the Dao Festival would be taking place.

A particular elder with the Dark Palm insignia on his robe was pacing back and forth. He was a man that looked to be in his fifties, he had dark hair and quite the long crooked nose. It bent upwards and then made a sharp turn to the left, giving the man a peculiar look.

"No good, no good... why is that person coming... this is just a small festival for those clan trashes..."

He was holding a communication device, he had just received word that an important person from the main sect area would be arriving to take part in this year's festival. The man didn't know why, but one thing was clear he couldn't offend this scary cultivator, if he did his life would probably be over.

"We must get everything in order... damn is there enough time to prepare everything for his arrival?"

The man activated the communication device and started calling his underlings, he had to prepare a grand welcoming party for this important visitor. They needed to get the best food ready, the best lodgings the best everything that they had. The problem were these random clans that would be swarming the city in a couple of days, they were a random factor any one of those people could end up offending the important people from the main sect.

"Be sure to assign as many people as you can to our special visitor, we can't let anything happen, I don't care if anything happens to those useless clans, you have my permission to get rid of anyone!"

The man put the communication device to the side, this was quite a big problem but also could be a blessing in disguise. This was a high ranking member from the main sect, if he made a good impression on him he might get a promotion. He was a big fish in a small pond now, but he longed for better cultivation manuals and an even higher position. This was all attainable at the main sect area, it boasted the largest Qi condensation and had a vast library of knowledge.

"If everything goes right, I might finally be able to leave this backwater sinkhole!"

Chapter 126

The Zhang Clan flying ship moved through the air, most of the people were just sitting in their cabins cultivating but some of them were out and about, looking at the scenery that zoomed past them. It was quite the sight, the closer they got to their destination the greener it got, the city the festival was being held was famous for its lush grass fields.

Spirit grass was a staple in this area and it was a very potent pill concocting ingredient. This was why it was procured by the ruling sect from the area, they wouldn't let a green goldmine like this be conquered by any of the backwater clans in the area. The spirit grass export and price was regulated by the Dark Palm sect, making sure to have the people that they deemed unworthy to have to pay up more.

This was an important ingredient, but it wasn't super essential that's why only lower-level members from the Dark Palm sect were stationed here. It brought in quite the penny but wasn't as important as some other assets that the sect was defending, like a spirit stone mine that was far more of a flexible asset.

This wasn't the only thing that grew in this city though, there were vast rice fields, that added to the greenery. The whole area was more or less fertile land, that allowed most plants to bloom and grow. The name coming from the vast fields of green, that made the outside look like green jade.

The Zhang Clan ship was close to reaching their destination, the youths on the deck were slowly coming out from their secluded meditation. There weren't that many of them, the clan only chose the most promising members that would participate, some of them were well-known figures that made their fame from partaking in the expedition two years ago.

The two most prominent ones were of course the Patriarch's disciples, both of them had reached the foundation establishment realm before the age of twenty which was quite the achievement. Their salt and pepper hair turned mostly white after they formed their perfect Dao pillars, now they only had a large patch of hair at the forehead area that was pure black, the rest was snow white. Their mom didn't come this time around, leaving everything up to their grandfather.

Next in line was their senior brother, Zhang Tai. He was older than them but still made the cut, he was still quite talented. His potential was at a B grade, which wasn't much below the two siblings. Thanks to his achievements he had earned better cultivation methods and the Patriarch even gave him a more fitting cultivation method as well as some manuals to aid him in with his swordsmanship skills.

That was all the members that were from the old 9th Platoon, the rest were recruited for police work and sitting back in Spirit Spring City training up new recruits. There were a couple of other promising youths, but most of the juniors that were at the expedition were too old to participate now and the ones here paled in comparison to the three previously mentioned youths.

"Junior Sister Xue how do you fare?"

Zhang Tai walked over to the edge of the ship, his junior sister was standing there and looking at the lush greenery. The young man had a slight smile on his face, but it quickly turned around after he saw Zhang Liu standing next to her.

"Ah, I don't get a greeting, senior brother?"

Zhang Liu asked, a cocky grin plastered all over his face. The two had built up a kind of rivalry over the past two years. In the beginning Liu wasn't a match for Tai at all, but now they were at exactly the same cultivation level and were more or less equal in strength. This was a slight hit to the face of Zhang Tai, having someone younger be his equal but considering that the person in question was the Patriarch's disciple, he could somehow stomach it.

"Well, if it isn't junior brother Liu... don't get your hopes up too much, I'll be taking the number one spot!"

He stuck out his chest, hands behind his back as if he was trying to imitate that Zhang Dong pose. He also glanced at Zhang Xue's expression from the side, the younger girl caught his eye as the man was gunning for her affections. This was something her older sibling knew and didn't agree with, thinking that this senior brother was far too pompous for his lovely sister.

"Haha, I see senior brother has cultivated a sense of humor, I'll be sure to congratulate you on your spot, after I'm the tournament winner!"

Sparks flew between the two young men, the girl just covered her face with her long sleeve and started laughing. She took quite the joy from these two, they bickered and fought like an old married couple which was quite fun to watch.

"Oh, you want to have a go at it?"

Zhang Tai shouted out, his finger pointing at Xue menacingly.

"I'll be your opponent, anytime!"

Liu replied while getting ready for some fisticuffs.

"Brother, Senior Tai please calm down. Use that anger against the other clans that will be participating."

She tried to defuse the situation, a bright smile on her face the moment Tai got a glimpse of it, he felt a devastating blow to his heart. His face went slightly red and he turned away, worried that the beautiful junior sister would find it funny and he wanted to come off as a gallant gentleman.

"Ah, if junior sister says so..."

"Hah, you always chicken out when Xue is around."

Tai turned to glare at his junior brother once more, this time around he was more willing to give him a good trashing. The two released their cultivation aura which alarmed all the other people in the vicinity, but they weren't going to jump in or anything most of the youths were just interested who from these two would come out on top.

"Brother Liu you can do it!"

"Brother Tai, don't let that junior speak to you like that!"

"Fight, fight, fight!"

The two of them moved their palms up, Zhang Tai was holding his hand out, blue energy slowly enveloped his mitt. On the other hand, Zhang Liu placed his palm in a ninety-degree angle, lightning energy started crackling as he was preparing to receive his senior brother's attack. But before the two could clash a booming voice filled the entire ship, which made the two fighting peacocks ferocity deflate like a poked balloon.

"What are you two idiots doing, cease your squabbling!"

This was Zhang Jin flexing his aura, which made the two youths drop down to their knees in an instant. The crowd on the side that were egging the two one just a second ago dispersed, doing it only after cupping their fists at their grand elder. The two didn't get to leave unscathed as a lump appeared on their heads after the elder gave them a good smack.

"Now, sit down and be quiet you two, we will be arriving shortly, can't have the other clans see you two idiots bickering!"

Zhang Jin glared at some other elder members from the clan that were previously in the crowd. They didn't do much to stop the fight as they thought that it would be too bothersome. Also, no one really wanted to offend the Patriarch's disciple as that was a fast way of getting yourself in trouble.

The whole place quieted down afterward, the city was just a couple hours away and they could already see more of those lush rice and spirit grass fields. Some villagers were there, they bowed to the flying ship. Regular people would preform these acts of courtesy, flying ships were a sign of power as you had to have quite the amount of cultivation resources to buy or build one.

Soon you could see the more refined architecture, many large pagodas were sticking out also in that green color which made the whole city look like a piece of jade. All the buildings were made this way, the pavilions and the palaces all had a green tint to them, the cultivators apparently liked the green jade theme that went with this city.

At the front was a massive gate, people were lined up on one side and moving in while on the other they were moving out. This city was a coastal one too boot. From the front, it was surrounded by greenery while from the back by a giant mass of water. By the sheer size of the body of water you would think that it was a giant sea, but this was only a really large lake. Things were larger in this world, so the lakes that were the size of an earthly ocean were quite common.

This city was larger than Spirit Spring City and Moonlight City that boasted a population count close to ten million each. It was about twice the size of those, but it was still smaller than some main cities or the capital city that had a population of over one hundred million.

The population was densely packed and the buildings were built high up, which allowed for such a huge amount of residents in one place. But such a high population brought in the usual problems, like a high poverty rate and rampant disorder. This was fueled by the fact that most ruling powers didn't care about the commoners and let them handle their own disputes, as long as they paid their taxes and were courteous they were left alone.

This made what the Zhang Patriarch was doing back in his two cities stick out like a sore thumb, the news was slowly reaching the outside area's, it had a mixed reception with the crowd. Mostly positive from the poorer demographic, but they were also unwilling to trust the rumors. Their spirits were already broken, so they wouldn't have faith in the news of a just clan that would tend to their needs with minimal recompensation needed. Still, the curiosity was there if things got too rough they might not be against trying their luck out there.

On the other hand, the ruling forces were even more skeptical about the whole thing. For them, it looked like some kind of ploy to get people's attention. It seemed like the Zhang Clan was trying to lure the downtrodden people in with the promise of milk and honey, then do something unfathomable once they were in their clutches. They just couldn't get their heads around someone trying to help people with minimal or no gain in mind, that would just be something a fool would do. If it was true though, they just chucked it up to the Zhang Patriarch being far too young and uneducated for his position.

The Zhang Flying ship moved around the city, which allowed all the people to get a good look at it. They had to fly around to land on the big shipyard in the lake, some of the other clan ships being already stationed there while others were just arriving as them. The descending ship slowly landed in the water, an anchor getting thrown out, the ship could very well function as a normal water faring vessel.

They were finally here, people started descending and a man dressed in a baggy robe with a clipboard in his hand came out to greet them. He was wearing quite a large pointy hat and his beard was long and excessive.

"Greeting fellow Daoists, from the insignia I can see, that you are probably from the Zhang Clan, right?"

Zhang Jin nodded and let one of his retainers get the paperwork ready, they would get some accommodations and a guide just as any other clan. He didn't think they would get much though, his clan was still considered one of the averages ones, the word of their Patriarch's strength was still being questioned which made them quite the underdog. It didn't help that he was rarely seen and most of his accolades outside were under his demon hunter persona.

Chapter 127

The junior members of the clan looked out of their ship, they were standing on the deck of the boat. There were other flying vessels slowly descending into the water below. The last part of the descent made the waves splash to the side which made their own ship shake. There were quite a bit of them anchored here, many unfamiliar clan insignias could be seen ones belonging to small and one to the middle-sized clans.

The Zhang Clan was still considered a middle-sized clan, Clan's like the Xing family from Moonlight city would be considered a small-sized one. Still, some of them had enough spirit stones to buy themselves a sky fairing flying vessel, this was a good occasion to show of their clan members and make some connections with the other families in the Dark Palm sect area of influence.

The country this was taking place was called the Azure Dragon Empire, the Long Clan and the Azure Emperor were the ruling factions, but there were various other powerhouses scattered around it. In this world, the density of spiritual energy determined where people would set up their settlements.

The more you traveled towards the Long Clan occupied area the denser the Qi condensation got and the easier the cultivators could progress. The Empire was divided into smaller state like areas where various powerful clans and sects ruled. Due to this, sects and clans wanted to set up their bases as near to the Long Clan area as it was possible, so those cities were always built close to the state borders. The further away from the border you got, you'd find weaker and weaker sects and clans residing there.

The so-called states didn't really have any particular names, they were just areas ruled by a powerful clan or sect. The area that the Dark Palm sect was occupying was about in the middle of the map, the land further in was the spot that was occupied by the truly strong forces, ones that even this sect wouldn't be dumb enough to offend.

But in response, the space that they occupied was deemed inferior for them, letting this sect grow in power while the powerhouses further into the empire fought with themselves, leaving sects like the Dark Palm one alone to do whatever they pleased. They wouldn't care one way or the other what happened to them, they would only react if someone tried moving onto their territory.

Thanks to this, these kinds of sects could flourish. They were deemed strong enough to not be worth the hassle of losing any troops if it came to blows, the nascent soul cultivators being a strong enough deterrent. Yet, the probability of them getting stronger was quite low as the better resources were all further into the empire, things like secret grounds were far more common there.

There was also a thin balancing act that the more powerful sects had to go through. If they suddenly ordered a large chunk of their nascent soul cultivators to attack a sect like the Dark Palm sect, another powerhouse could use this and move in on their turf. So, unless something drastic happened they wouldn't keep to themselves.

Jade Grass City was one of the spots affiliated with the sect, they had a small force stationed here and even a direct line to the main sect. Though it would be used for emergencies, for moments of a revolt or if a particular strong beast attack.

The bustling of the crowd could be heard everywhere, some people on flying swords were also buzzing about. They were all people in high places and with connections, normal cultivators were forbidden from flying on their swords above the city.

Zhang Jin was still on the ship, one of his retainers was outside handling all that paperwork and showing them the proof that they were truly from the Zhang Clan. There was a small fee you had to pay to participate, this small payment was already too much to stomach for some smaller clans.

There were about fifty junior clan members from the Zhang Clan, mostly everyone was twenty or twenty-one, and in the early stage of foundation establishment. There was no reason to take Qi condensation cultivators as they would never make it through the preliminary round of the test, failing at the first one where the all-around strength was measured.

This was actually a high number, all things considered, thanks to increasing the ranks of their cultivation techniques the Zhang Clan was seeing a new renaissance. Their younger generation was profiting the most as it was easier to change things up before you reached the foundation establishment level. Creating superior pillars was far easier than reinforcing cracked or flawed ones.

Zhang Jin knew well how things stood and that his clan would be sticking out with how much they had progressed. But he was betting on that, he wanted to show that his family was getting stronger this would make people think twice about offending them. He was well aware of the looming threat of the sect but he knew that they wouldn't do a thing unless it was related to a nascent soul level threat.

At the foundation level, they had nothing to fear, they still had only three core formation cultivators which was nothing in the eyes of their overlord. Though, if they showed up with fifty core formation experts, the Dark Palm sect would probably start playing a different tune and engage them in combat.

The accommodations were ready as the Zhang clan retainer moved back to the ship and gave the news to the grand elder, he in response clapped his hands to get everyone's attention.

"Okay you rascals, stay close together, and don't get separated from the group at least till we get to our hotel, then you'll be free to explore the city."

The youths beamed with excitement, it was very rare for them to leave the main clan city and they were mostly cultivating diligently at their homes or cultivation caves. This would be a nice chance to see the world and have some fun, they all were snapped back to reality after their grand elder spoke once more.

"But be cautious, I'm sure you are all excited but remember where we are, be courteous to the other clans and the sect, don't cause trouble for me or the clan. If you offend someone from the Dark Palm sect or a strong clan, I won't be able to do anything for you."

The youths looked at each other, they knew well how this world worked. They were all highly regarded cultivators in their home city, but here they were more or less just country bumpkins. No one would bat an eye if they got stabbed in the back after offending some scary uncles or overbearing young masters.

"Still, don't bring shame to the Zhang Clan and the Patriarch, this clan isn't a bunch of cowards, don't let me see you tarnish our reputation!"

It was one thing to be honorable and civilized, it was another to just let people spit in your face. The elder's words were clear, if you meet someone from a stronger affiliation you should bow your head, but if it's someone of an equal status you are not allowed to defame the clan, losing face was not allowed,

This was also the reason that Zhang Jin didn't want Zhang Dong to be here. The juniors seemed to have more common sense than his grandson, that if push comes to shove would probably offend their sect overlords. Zhang Jin knew how to maneuver things which got difficult, there was no shame in bowing your head to someone stronger than you, it was the way of this world. He feard that his grandson would blunder and cause a scene that could cost him his life, he wasn't quite ready to take the next step.

"Well then, let us depart!"

The youths started moving in an orderly fashion, there were also members of the elder generation with them. They were all quite proud of how their youths were progressing, they knew that at their age they weren't nearly as strong.

They were slowly guided towards the main lodging area, people in various colorful robes were gathering there. The youths didn't recognize the patterns or insignias at all, the cultivators were from various sects and clans that were scattered around the area hoping to make a name for themselves.

"Have you heard, apparently this time around the winner will receive fifty middle grade spirit stones!"

"Fifty? But that's like fifty thousand low-grade spirit stones... I'm getting even more pumped up!"

While going in you could overhear people talking, besides the name recognition that you would gain from winning the tournament, you would receive quite the hefty sum of spirit stones. This amount was enough to fund your own small clan, you could probably build a small city with that amount as well.

The top ten participants would earn prises and even be allowed to join the Dark Palm sect if they so wished for. This wasn't anything strange, it was normal for clan members to study at sects. They were sworn to secrecy but that didn't mean that they couldn't protect their family members and improve their status. The sect wouldn't bat an eye if they shared some rudimentary techniques with the lower clans though, but the higher ones were forbidden from getting passed on outside the sect.

The building the clans were staying was huge, it was a giant pagoda in an octagon shape. It looked to be able to house tens of thousands of people inside of it, with various levels outfitted filled out with diverse equipment. There was a dining area, an auditorium for lectures and even a casino, betting and gambling was quite popular in this world, probably due to the fact that it was a way to gain easy money and all these cultivators liked taking high risk, high reward bets.

The thing was over a hundred stories high, there was something akin to an elevator installed. There were various platforms outside the pagoda balconies, they would slowly float upwards after you pushed some spiritual energy into them. They were only designed to move in a certain way so you couldn't use them like a flying sword. The requirement of spiritual energy was quite low, thanks to that almost everyone could use them. This was all thanks to something akin to spiritual energy batteries that were embedded to the floating platform, the platform only required a small jolt of energy to get moving.

The clan was situated at about the 30th floor, due to the fact that they had to switch those platforms constantly it took them thirty minutes to just reach their lodging. The higher the level of the hotel the more pristine it was, the pagoda was thinner at the top. That's where the penthouse suite was, it boasted the best qi gathering formations and was made from the best materials on the market, but it was reserved for the utmost important guests.

It had quite the view as well, letting the person staying there enjoy the jade green scenery below. At this time some people were staying in this apartment, they were brought here by the Dark Palm sect elder that was panicking just a couple days ago.

Two people were in this penthouse apartment at the moment. One was a handsome young man, he had the usual long dark hair and he was wearing a golden robe, the most peculiar thing about him was the jewel sticking out of his forehead. Its color was purple, which was associated with royalty in this kind of world.

The youth was clasping his hands in front of an older man, this man was sitting in a large armchair and just glancing to the side out to the scenery. The man was wearing a similar robe to the youth, but it was even more extravagant with various gems and sparkling metals attached to it, a large dark palm symbol glistering in the back.

The man's outer appearance was quite normal, he had a classical beard that wasn't all that long, just long enough to cover his chin and cheeks. He had salt and pepper hair and didn't look anything out of the ordinary, though when you looked into his eyes they would send shivers down your spine. It were the kind of eyes that made you cover in fear of what was hidden behind them.

Chapter 128

The man with the gem in his forehead looked to be in his twenties, but in reality, he was already fifty years old. He was quite the famous young master from the Dark Palm sect. He looked quite handsome and was adored by everyone, or at least that's how it looked on the outside.

"Thanks for letting me tag along with you, Elder Ming."

The man bowed with his hands clasped, the Dark Palm sect elder was on a little errand here and this young master had used this opportunity to join him on his journey.

"It's nothing really, didn't think you'd find this place that interesting little Kai, I'm just here for the items at the auction."

The old man sat back and sipped some green tea, the tea leaves being the highest quality that this city could offer, the water and tableware being the same.

"Hm, the tea is satisfactory at least..."

The young man straightened up and looked outside the window, his eyes narrowing.

"Ah yes the auction, to be exact I wanted my disciple to participate in that little festival those little clans are having."

"Oh? The Dao Festival?"

The sect elder's brow moved upwards slightly, but almost immediately went down.

"Well, I won't pester you for details, but if your disciple is taking part then be sure not to sully the sects name, he has to win."

The man waved with his hand at his junior member, even though this was the son of the Patriarch this elder outranked him by quite a bit, his cultivation level was something that made him a king among men already.

"Well then, Elder Ming rest well, I'll see you tomorrow."

The Dark Palm member named Kai exited the room that this elder of his was staying, he knew when this Elder Ming didn't want him around so he had enough tack to back of, on his own. He was stationed a flor below, which was still quite the expensive-looking apartment.

This man's full name was Yang Kai. He returned to his quarters, the view at the city was grand but the man in question wasn't really impressed by it.

"Mmm, give me your report..."

There was another man in that room, Yang Kai was sitting on an expensive couch, his legs spread apart in a nonchalant way. The man opposite him was a rough-looking gentleman in a less expensive Dark Palm sect robe.

"Yes young master, the 'target' arrived not long ago, they are staying at this grand dragon hotel on the fortieth floor."

Yang Kai licked his lips slightly after he heard that the person that he was here for was already in this hotel with him. He had to stop himself from just going directly there, that would just make him look bad and he would lose face, it was not yet time to strike.

"Good... good... now I just have to wait for this festival to start and then..."

The bodyguard was silent, his eyebrows quivering after seeing quite the devilish expression on his face.

"Ahh... tell my disciple to prepare, he is not allowed to lose or he will be severely punished! But not like any of those backwater clans can hold a handle to him."

"Now, leave."

He waved with his hand at the guard while smirking to himself. The moment the man left Yang Kai stood up, his gaze moving over to his spatial ring. He pulled out a thin scarf, it had a cherry blossom pattern sewn into it. He placed it soon up towards his nose and inhaled with vigor, his eyes closed but his eyelids quivered back and forth during the inhaling.

"You got away once and I thought that I lost you... but now here you are... If I wasn't stuck cultivating at the sect I would have come sooner, but that's fine...he he he..."

The man licked his lips in a gross fashion, the scarf he was holding looked a bit scuffed up.

"Soon you will be mine, this time I won't let you run away... even if I have to..."

The man didn't finish the sentence and moved the scarf back into his spatial ring, his head shaking.

"Oh my, I'm getting too excited here...

Yang Kai sat down to meditate, the chaotic thoughts in his mind calming down while the night ended.

At dawn you could hear people walking, all the shops were opening up and the day was starting. The Dao Festival wasn't only for the clan's but a lot of people saw it as a chance to make some coin or spirit stones. There was a big marketplace, with various cultivation materials and trinkets gathered in one place.

Usage of magical treasures during the fights was allowed, so was taking pills. The use of weapons was allowed as well, everyone could bring weapons of their choosing, using dual swords was also allowed. It didn't matter if the quality of the weapon of one participant was lower than the others, that was taken into account as your personal strength. It was the same with the defensive treasures or any magical trinkets, the cultivators knew that life wasn't fair and that everyone was born unequally. Having resources to back yourself up was something that these people agreed with, but due to this, you didn't see poorer practitioners winning that often.

The preliminary round would start tomorrow so everyone from the clan had some free time today, they could use it to tour the city or just stay and cultivate if they felt that it would give them an edge over the competition. Most of the youths were quite interested in the new environment and decided to form a couple of smaller groups. In front of those groups stood one of Zhang Jin's retainers, the grand elder had other things to take care of besides being a chaperone for these kids.

"Listen up, you are free to visit the city. Fighting with anyone is forbidden, remember that this isn't Spirit Spring city and Elder Jin won't be able to help you out if you offend someone."

"Don't worry, the other clans are also forbidden from causing trouble before the festival starts, anyone that doesn't follow the law will be banned from the competition, so use some common sense and don't bring shame to our Zhang Clan!"

"Yes Elder!"

The young adults all replied in unison, the loud shout even alerting some other tournament participants that were standing on the side. Some of them already whispering as the Zhang family was slowly gaining notoriety, mostly because their Patriarch apparently soundly beat the famous Demon Hunter a few weeks ago.

The acclaimed Lei Yinglo was someone with quite a high status, his strength was already legendary. He had built it up by slaying demon beasts and cultivators all in the late and great circle stages of core formation, which was quite a feat in the eyes of anyone without a nascent soul cultivator in their camp. Also, Zhang Dong made it sure to order to spread this information through the land so that he would gain some clout.

As long as it wasn't something pointing people to think that he was in the nascent soul stage, it was fine. Even this feat wouldn't really be taken seriously by the Dark Palm sect, the famous demon hunter was just a renegade cultivator with no backing so they didn't fear him much.

"Junior Sister, why don't we visit some sights in this Jade City, I heard they have really nice tea shops!"

After the Zhang Clan elder went back to his room, the first thing Zhang Tai did was walk over to Zhang Xue to ask her out. There were some other people around them, the youth would like to get someone on one time with this lovely younger sister of his, but their relationship wasn't quite there so he had to settle for some 'dead weight' to come with him.

"Tea shops? Why don't we go to the Jade Arena instead, maybe some experts will be fighting today!"

Zhang Lie chimed in, he was also with another small group of people. He smirked at Zhang Tai who was trying his best to not shout out in protest, this disciple of Zhang Dong was mostly just messing with his older brother. He found the courting that this senior brother was doing quite silly and loved to push his buttons.

"Tea shop?... Arena?... Hmm..."

Sparks started flying between the two youths some more, but before Zhang Xue could make her mind up someone else spoke up, it was a female voice.

"Hey, leave sister Xue alone, why would she spend time with you boys~"

A group of girls appeared out of nowhere, these were quite the cute and lovely junior and senior sisters that were also participating in this Dao Festival. There were fewer girls than boys at this event, with a ratio of five to one. They quickly shuffled between the youngest female member that was Zhang Xue and started pulling her away.

"Yes, this is time for us girls to bond, you boys go to your arenas or fight all you want~"

They all chuckled to each other, Xue did the same and let herself be escorted out by her clan sisters. The group of young beauties wasn't going out alone, they had a couple of clan elders go along with them, it would be unwise to just let a group of beauties go out without any bodyguards whatsoever. Though, all of those girls were quite decent fighters they still needed some backup if things got out of hand.

The girls left, Zhang Tai had his hand outstretched in the position where Zhang Xue went down the floating platform, his hand soon falling down and going limp as he gave out a sigh. One of the members from his group came closer and gave his shoulder a pat, then spoke out with a smile on his face.

"Don't worry senior brother Tai, there is no way that junior Sister Xue didn't notice you. I bet the next time you'll be able to share some tea with her!"

"Yes, there will always be a second chance."

His buddies cheered him up while on the other hand Zhang Liu just walked away while snorting, it was enough to see his senior brother mope around, he would poke fun at him at another chance. For now, he also wanted to leave and see the city, he had some other Zhang members with him to keep him company.

"Hah, while brother Tai sulks let us depart to see the city, that Jade Arena is said to have quite the ferocious fighters, even core formation experts do battle there!"

Zhang Liu proclaimed and departed down onto another floating platform, the trip to the first level of the pagoda hotel was quite tedious and took the same amount of time as before. Outside, the small group of youths rejoiced and departed they were all young men in their prime and they had a whole day of free time to play around. They all knew that they had a serious competition coming up the next day, but being young made them think that they could take on the world and they didn't think that they would actually have any problems with the preliminary round.

"I heard that they have quite the nice tasting wine in this city... the rice they make it from is rich in spiritual energy too..."

The youths looked at each other, they were planning to check out that arena and then go out drinking. Still, they had two elder members from the clan tagging along with them, but they knew these two uncles would probably give in if they offered them some alcohol as well.

"Yes, let us head out!"

Zhang Liu shouted out with a smile on his face, his friends smiled at each other and left. Soon they joined the sea of people and made their way towards the arena building. Even during the day, it was open it was quite the popular area for betting. But while Liu was taking a turn into another street, he felt something hit his chest.

"Ack..."

A cute voice cried out as the youth realized that a girl crashed into his chest. The youth cultivated his body refining technique to quite a high degree so the young lady rebounded off him and fell down on her butt. Liu instinctively reached out with his hand to help her out, the peculiar thing about the girl was the color of her hair that was light pink, her skin tone made you think that she was out tanning or spent a lot of time on a beach.

Chapter 129

The young man looked at the equally youthful girl that was rubbing her head. She had just bumped into him and was now down on the ground and on her posterior. The girl was peculiar looking, she could be described as flashy. Long nails with something that looked like little pink and purple gems stuck to them. Her hair was done in a twin-tail type of hairstyle, her lips were rosy and she was wearing golden earrings.

Her robe was unusually short, normally the female cultivators wore ones that went down to their ankles. They parted on the sides so that they had some wiggle room to move their legs around. The skirt of the robe that this girl was wearing could be considered a miniskirt. The young man's eyes stopped at the lower area as he could see quite the plump thighs, he then traced his gaze upwards and was greeted by quite the lovely mountain peaks. He gulped hard and managed to gather his senses, reaching out with his hand as he tried to help the girl up to her feet.

"Ahh, forgive me, are you alright?"

He wasn't sure if this girl was older or younger than he was, but they looked to be in a similar age range that didn't require any honorifics. The girl finally looked up without saying a word, her green eyes met with the youth. They didn't break eye contact for a good couple of seconds, which after the girl finally reacted.

"Ahhhhh...."

She jumped up to her two feet with haste, her twin-tails bounced around along with her upper chest part, her short robe having to strain itself to contain all of that weight there.

"Ohhhh nooo... I'm going to be late..."

Zhang Liu moved back a bit, the girl just bolting off into the distance and quickly vanishing from view leaving the youth and his clan companions stupified.

"W-what?"

"Brother Liu sure is a smooth talker with the ladies..."

"Haven't seen a girl run away that fast in a while, must be some kind of talent!"

Zhang Liu got a bit red in the face after his friends started teasing him, they quickly quieted down after he gave them all his death glare, but then they laughed out once more as this made things even funnier.

"Let us move on... the arena isn't far from here..."

Zhang Liu proclaimed as everyone moved out, the youth rubbing his chin while he thought about the cute looking girl that he bumped into.

'That robe pattern looked familiar... where did I see it before...'

He was sure that he saw a similar-looking robe on someone before, but he wasn't quite sure who was it. He was positive that he didn't know the girl from anywhere, but that robe and skin tone was unusual to see in this world occupied by jade-like beauties that liked to look like ghosts. Zhang Liu turned away from that motion after his master gave him a lecture about the importance of sunlight and how a healthy skin tone was vastly more beautiful than looking like a bedsheet.

'She might have been from that clan...oh well...'

He tossed his thoughts to the back of his head, but while walking forward towards the arena he found himself constantly getting reminded of the girl's chest area, guess the master's tastes were absorbed by this disciple.

Though, while the group of youthful cultivators went on with their day, they didn't notice that someone was following them. A bouncy tail of hair was peeking out from the corner, with the same girl that Zhang Liu bumped into peeking her head out. Her eyes were sparkling as she looked at the back of the young man that she bumped into. She clenched her tiny fist, a smirk covering her face as she whispered out.

"I'll show you that the ancestors weren't wrong! Stupid big sis!"

-------------

Back at Spirit Spring City Zhang Dong was pacing through his room. It seemed as if he was looking into a random direction where there was a wall, but in reality, he was looking at his status screen. He had absorbed anything he could, without tapping into the clan's reserve spirit stone stash and was now waiting for the system point count to go past ten million.

'God damn... it's really happening... and I'm not even stuck in some kind of death and life battle this time around!'

He had a dumb grin plastered all over his face. He was sure that he would reach the nascent soul stage soon and it would be happening in a couple of hours at exactly twelve at midnight. That was the time when his clan building portion of his system did its update and he would receive the required points for his advancement.

'It's still the middle of the day... the suspense is killing me...'

He was equally happy and scared, this would be his first jump in big realms. The previous small level-ups all happened while he was still in core formation, this would be the first time he would be reaching a new point of existence. There was also one particular change that he was afraid of, that was actually getting one of those nascent souls, or infant souls if you went with a more direct translation.

'Guess I'll have a little baby soul living inside me... well that will be weird... well can't be weirder than cultivating a whole universe in your own body like they do in some other works of fiction.'

Matt crossed his hands over one another and tried to recall any other strange cultivation methods. In a lot of those, the cultivators would perceive some kind of world inside of themselves, building palaces or large seas of spiritual energies, or even worlds with greenery inside. He had a similar thing inside of him in the form of the Dao pillars, but they were already there along with his core even before he arrived in this world so they felt kind of natural.

'What I got from the other cultivation manuals is that, you are supposed to shatter your core to produce a nascent soul instead of it... the cultivator might die in the process of doing that if they aren't careful and fully prepared though, but in my case, the system should take care of everything, right?'

Matt was kind of banking on the system to get him over the hump, when he upgraded his cultivation method to the golden lightning one the system did the hard part for him. It was as if he practiced this cultivation method instead of the previous one the moment he spent his points of it. So he was sure that his cheat ability would push him through it one way or the other. He just needed to make sure to hide the fact that he reached this degree of power.

'First I'll lay low for some months and train up some of those nascent soul techniques at least to an adept rank...'

He already had picked up a couple of techniques that he wanted to practice, they included better sword techniques, better movement techniques, and so on. He was also banking on producing better versions of his old techniques, he still got the cultivation manuals of them.

After upgrading his main cultivation method, he would probably receive the manual for it. He could then start mixing it with the other manuals he received from the secret ground. You didn't have to mix attack techniques with the same sort, you could pick and choose. One technique would be used as a basis, while the rest would add to it.

For instance, he could take his improved golden nascent soul cultivation manual and pair it up with another heaven grade technique, if it worked it would produce an improved version of the skill that used parts of his main cultivation method. An inferno palm strike technique could thus be transformed into a golden lightning palm strike that would fit his needs a lot more.

'All the possibilities! Though I shouldn't spread myself too thin... I could well spend years training new skills it's fine if I get one or two and just focus on them for now. I'd also need boatloads of crafting points to get new technique manuals... wish that store was still working...'

Matt was still feeling disgruntled after losing his cash shop. It would be much easier to just find a proper skill from there than play around with that upgrading machine in his crafting abode.

'I'd probably already be in the nascent soul a year ago if I still got points for killing demonic beasts too...'

He shrugged and went outside his room, the people that he met bowed to him in respect. He headed down into the secret part of the main Zhang compound where the spatial treasure in the form of the medallion was hidden. After the years the clan had figured a way to bolster it, but it was something Matt didn't like doing as he had to pour copious amounts of his spiritual energy into the thing.

The dimensional regalia only accepted pure holy element energies which only he possessed. The more of it he inserted into the thing, the more it grew in size. The increase was quite meager though, if he pushed 50% of his cultivation base into the spatial treasure the rocky area would grow by only a couple of meters. Though it grew in all directions, after two years he managed to add another couple of kilometers in diameter.

The guards greeted their Patriarch, they were already informed that he would be going into closed cultivation inside the dimensional regalia. They were ordered to keep anyone out and only bother him if there was some kind of emergency, like an attack from another clan or something in that range.

He entered the large room the medallion was placed in, quickly vanishing inside of it. The large dorm was still standing there, along with some other structures that were nowhere instead of the makeshift tents, that the clan used when they were preparing for the expedition. The dorm-like building was enlarged and another level was built atop of it, they even added a cafeteria for the recruits that were still being trained in here.

'Heh, nice to be the leader, everyone had to clear out of here.'

The innermost clan members were training in here, hidden away from prying eyes. Matt had written down each book from that library and placed it in here in a well-protected vault. Normally you would see people guarding it, depending on your clan rank and your potential you were allowed inside of that vault. The vault library had four levels, each of them having manuals and books ranging from Qi condensation all up to Nascent soul ones. The last area was only open to people at the top, which was the Patriarch and the Grand Elder.

'Well, the energies from stepping into the Nascent Soul level will be blocked by this treasure.'

This was the biggest reason he was here, the dimensional regalia blocked any aura from seeping outside. He would be safe in here to cultivate in peace, and unless someone stronger than him got their hands on the treasure they wouldn't be able to even come inside without his approval.

"Hm, what time is it now..."

He glanced at his system clock, which was quite handy for occasions like this.

"Still have a couple of hours till I get my points... guess I could prepare for the next stage of the plan..."

He still needed to make that heaven grade weapon, he was waiting to pass his realm first than he would start crafting. He didn't have that many materials for his training though, the blasted dark palm sect was keeping tabs on even the crafting component that could be used for heaven grade weapons and treasures. But luckily throughout the years, old grandpa Jin had managed to procure some goods for him. It was also one of the reasons that it was taking him two years to finally reach this point, the spirit stone expenditure was immense.

"Well then, time to say goodbye to the crummy core and welcome the baby soul."

Chapter 130

Back in Jade Grass City Zhang Liu and his friends were moving through the stalls, they had some food in their hands something that looked like to be a shish kebab on a stick. All of them were munching while walking forward, wondering if they would get to see a good show at the arena.

"Hm, wonder if someone good will be battling, would be nice..."

"Yeah, someone like our Patriarch... we missed his fight with that Demon hunter..."

"The leader taught him a lesson, he was a hundred years too early to even try that!"

The young men chatted around, Zhang Liu didn't talk all that much as he didn't know these junior and senior brothers all that well himself. His old 9th platoon buddies weren't here and the only one from them was someone that he was in a feud with.

"Ah yes, shame that I could not see Master's fight, supposedly the Demon Hunter was just misguided, but Master was magnanimous in his decision and let him live."

The other young men nodded, their eyes shining brightly as they heard Zhang Liu call their Patriarch, Master. They thought that it would be an honor if they were also his disciple, this was also a reason that they were pumped up. If they managed to reach a high standing in the tournament, or even beat this Zhang Liu than maybe Zhang Dong would notice them and give them some pointers.

"We are here brother Liu."

While they were chatting and eating they finally arrived at the spot, they were greeted by a large gate, behind the gate were stairs that went upwards. There were some people in front of the gate, you had to pay the toll to get inside which the youths did. After slowly walking up they saw a large open space, in the middle of that area, was a large square ring made from some kind of brick-like material.

On the west and east side of that ring, they saw many regular looking seats. There were already some people sitting there and cheering for some warriors that were battling it out. On the North side, besides some more seats closer to the ring stood a large tower, in that tower were the more expensive seats for the more influential customers. They came from the south side and above them was a more narrow looking tower and on it was the booth with the announcers that commented on the fights and introduced the fighters before each fight.

To their immediate left, you could go under the seats. Inside were various booths and stands for betting purposes but you could also by some refreshments. The young men looked at each other, people were going back and forth from within that area.

"Well... I'm not really interested in betting, don't even know the fighters... how about you brothers?"

Zhang Liu asked, not really keen on spending his allowance that his mother and master gave him. He would rather spend it on something like interesting treasures, he knew that Zhang Dong was quite a skilled craftsman. Maybe if he found something curious, his Master would praise him, he always said something about needing more treasures for deconstruction.

Some of the men went in to take a look, but the complicated board that had some numbers and names on it was quite confusing. Though they found something quite interesting, if you signed a contract you could participate in the arena. You didn't even need to face other cultivators, in particular, you could fight untamed beasts or even have small skirmishes with your clan members against other clans.

"Quite interesting...though the grand elder told us to not cause trouble and not fight."

They all looked at each other, the warrior inside of them was telling them to go for it as they all wanted to prove themselves in a fight. But the Dao festival was coming along, what if they got injured or used up too much Qi during combat. There was also the threat of their opposition seeing their hidden techniques, then having something in store for them if they ever clashed.

"Let's just see who is fighting... maybe after the Festival is over we can try our luck in here, you can apparently earn quite a sum if you keep winning."

They headed out and found themselves a good spot to sit in, the area was slowly getting filled up and they were lucky enough to get enough seats for all. They could see someone getting carried out by two buff looking uncles, they were holding him by his wrists and ankles the person was just dangling like a ragdoll, probably the loser of the bout.

Zhang Liu looked inside the ring, there was one person standing there he was waving at the people a large smile plastered all over his face. He was wearing a red robe and had similar short red hair. The robe was peculiar in the way that it had no sleeves and you could see the young man's quite thick muscular arms.

"Oh, looks like the fiery youth has taken another victim, can no one stop him?"

You could hear the loud voice of the announcer that traveled around the arena, apparently, this youth had been on a winning streak.

"Can no one stop the blazing inferno? Already four people have failed!"

Zhang Liu squinted with his eyes, getting interested in this youth, he looked to be of similar age as he was. By the looks of it, he was also in the same cultivation range as him. One of the laws of this arena was that opponents had to be close to each other in cultivation realms. They wouldn't allow someone in the early stage of foundation establishment to fight someone in the great circle, unless the weaker person could use some treasures to lower that gap or something similar.

"I will be your opponent you shitty brat!"

A large burly man with tree trunks for arms jumped into the ring, his descent causing a commotion in the arena.

"Oh, if it isn't a brave challenger, let me remind you that everyone is allowed to challenge the winner of the previous bout! Fighters that are participating in this year's Dao Festival are also allowed! Just remember to register, if you want to participate!"

Apparently it was some kind of challenge event, where anyone of a similar cultivation realm could confront the previous winner. The more someone won, the more money they would get, you could also steal the previous winner's stash and then call it quits. The winning person could fight up to ten bouts but after winning all of those he wasn't allowed to participate anymore, this was a safety measure for the arena owners. This law was created to lower the losses if some kind of overpowered master appeared. The no fighting before the Dao Festival decree was apparently abolished in this neutral zone, you could participate at your own risk.

The large cultivator charged at the red-haired youth, he in response moved his forearm upwards to block the man's punch.

"Ha, idiot. I'll snap that toothpick in half!"

The red-haired youth had a good physique, but his enemy was far larger than him. You'd expect that giant fist to snap his arm in half, but this wasn't what happened. The fist flew at the forearm that started glowing red, soon it was engulfed in flames. It was too late for the attacker to stop and when his fist collided with the fire an explosion occurred. The large man was forced backward his hand smoking, his flesh charred.

"Hm, what were you saying?"

The fight wasn't over just yet, but the burly man's right fist was out of commission. The two were apparently close range specialists, the burly man probably being a body refiner. Zhang Liu observed from his spot, the red-haired man charged in. He had both of his hands clad in flames with some strange patterns showing up on both his arms.

Each time the two clashed the burly man got pushed back, he was even using his damaged arm to block some hits his face contorting in strange ways as the pain struck.

'Quite the will power there...'

Zhang Liu thought while complimenting the older man, who showed quite some resilience. This wasn't enough though, soon he was pushed back, well more like he flew in a glorious arc and left an imprint of a human on the arena wall. The defensive formation activating so that the residual rubble didn't hit the audience members.

"Oh no, the challenger is down! Only five more to go can no one stop this fire demon? If you think you are up to the challenge please register with one of our staff members!"

Apparently, the people around here measured your strength before the fighting took place. They couldn't just have random people jumping in from god knows where. Someone could also setup easy fights for himself and cheat. This was possible but hard to pull off, also if you got caught cheating you would be severely punished.

"Brother Liu, maybe we should register..."

Some of the Zhang members got excited after hearing that fighting in this arena was allowed even for festival participants. This was quite an alluring proposal, Zhang Liu never got much practical training mostly training his techniques alone and his sister wasn't quite up to par when they sparred with each other, he as the older brother couldn't really go all out in fear of injuring his younger sibling.

"We could do that..."

"We will be holding a short intermission, please place your bets or register if you want to participate in the event."

The announcer proclaimed while the red-haired man at the arena crossed his arms over one another, even a bigger grin plastered over his face.

"Hah, let's go..."

The young men all nodded at each other, the more elder members that were keeping tabs on them weren't that thrilled about what these youths were doing. It looked like fighting before the festival could cause unneeded injuries, but it also could be a big confidence booster for their clan members. They let it slide, for now, they were just registering and weren't fighting just yet.

Every one of the Zhang Clan youths, Zhang Liu included got a certain engraving on their palm. It was the rank that they were deemed worthy of fighting with, they also noticed that the exact same emblem, the emblem looking like a tiger was next to the man's name that was currently in the ring.

"Huo Kong... the Huo clan?"

Zhang Liu read his name that was on the betting board, he knew the name of this clan they had fought together with them in that secret ground but he didn't know this young man.

'He wasn't in there with us at that time... guess he stayed behind?'

The Huo Clan was a larger family that owned five cities and other various assets through the lands. It was one of the largest clans from the Dark Palm sect area, with more resources and manpower than what Zhang Clan could produce.

"Oh, is it a brother from the Huo Clan? The elders said that we are allied with them and our Patriarch and the son of their Patriarch are close friends..."

The Huo Clan and the Zhang Clan had formed an alliance after what happened in the secret ground. They weren't the only ones as the ladies from the Feng Clan also became their supporters. This was quite advantageous for the Zhang Clan, who had gained two powerful backers and business partners. Zhang Dong had sold quite the amount of treasures and crafted weapons to both of those clans, who gave him beneficial prices.

"Guess we should cheer the brother from the Huo Clan on."

The youths felt a sense of comradery with this fire family, mostly Zhang Liu that fought with them against the countless beast waves.

'I should exchange greetings with him, Master had quite the favorable opinion of that clan.'

Thinking nothing about it, Zhang Liu moved closer to the edge of the arena wall, closer to where the youth was standing and waiting for the intermission to be over. The youth suddenly heard someone calling out to him, his eyes fixated on a certain white-haired youth with a patch of black hair wairing a blue robe.

"Greetings brother from the Huo Clan, we from the Zhang Clan send our regards."

He was being formal with his greeting as he wasn't sure who this person was, the order of not causing trouble was still on his mind. Huo Kong while still having his hands closed looked to the side, one of his brows moving upwards as he looked at the man that spoke out.

"The Zhang Clan? You're from that small clan?"

He replied in a mocking tone, the grin never vanishing from his face as if he was trying to start a fight.

Chapter 131

Zhang Liu and his companions got taken aback by the way the youth was speaking. He was clearly being condescending towards their Clan name.

'Small Clan? Guess if you compare it to the Huo Clan then that's true.'

Zhang Liu thought to himself while trying not to get offended, but he had to fight against his natural disposition of wanting to jump in and give the Huo Clan member a good smack. His friends that he was with were slightly less composed than him, picking up on the tone he was speaking in, knowing well that by calling them a small clan he was saying that they were weak.

"What did you say?"

"Are you looking for a fight?"

None of these people fought together in the secret ground, so they only heard tales about the other clan from others. So there was no real sense of comradery there.

"Hah, talk is cheap, if you want something just face me!"

The man moved his right hand outwards pointing it towards the blue robe wearing group of young cultivators and beckoned them over by moving his palm towards himself. The Zhang Clan members were furious, veins started bulging on their foreheads as they just wanted to jump in and fight.

"Oh what is this, the contestant is challenging someone from the audience? Are they brave enough to take him up on the offer? Or will they cower in shame!"

The veins on their foreheads started bulging, even more, the moment the loud announcer's voice boomed through the whole arena. Now it would be quite difficult to back off, they would suffer public humiliation, loss to their own face and would bring shame to the clan.

"Brothers, let me handle this! I'll show him how the Zhang Clan warriors fight!"

One of the members from the group stepped out, the youth had sharp sword-shaped eyebrows and looked to be in his twenties. This was a talented youth from the group, even though he wasn't the strongest he wasn't the weakest either. He looked at Huo Kong that was just standing there beckoning them over, looking like he was without any care in the world.

Zhang Liu was the de facto leader of the group, being the strongest and also having the best backing out of the group. Liu remembered the words of the elders of not causing trouble, but he also recalled the bit about not backing down from a fight and not causing any loss to face if it was a manageable opponent.

"Do you feel confident, brother?"

The sharp eyebrow youth smacked his chest which produced quite the loud thumping sound. He then moved over to one of the arena officials to show him his mark and that he was eligible for the fight.

"Oh, think we have a new challenger!"

"Will this young man be able to douse the burning inferno, or will he also get burned by the blaze!"

The announcer was overdoing it a bit with the dramatic introductions and comments, but he was there to pump up the people in the audience. This looked to be working as people cheered, a path was made for the blue robe wearing youth from the Zhang Clan, people shouting out as they got their bets ready.

"Give us a good show, eyebrows!"

"Burn him alive!"

"You can do it, blue robe bushy-eyebrow brother!"

The young man tipped over to the side as he heard people commenting on his eyebrows. This was his most prominent trait though, besides them giving him a sharp look they had quite the volume to them as well.

"Shut up, who you calling bushy-eyebrows!"

He shook his fist at the audience that just laughed at him in response. He then jumped into the arena to face the red-haired youth, his aura getting releases, blue spiritual energy covering his robe. Huo Kong just shrugged and held his fists out in a what looked to be a traditional boxing stance with both his fists up in the air with his forearms blocking the view of his face.

The announcer shouted out which prompted the match to start, the two fighters eyeballed each other from a distance probably trying to get a feel of their opponent.

"Oh, didn't know the Zhang Clan studied the Dao of waiting, such a powerful technique~"

Huo Kong chuckled while taunting his opponent, who in response got red in the face and started showing his inexperience. He shouted out and charged forward, his foundation pillars vibrated and pushed their Qi into his legs. It looked as if a puddle of water formed under him and instead of running forward it looked as if he was sliding on the water that was getting produced on the arena floor. He glided forward like a figure skater just moving his legs slightly while gaining momentum.

The red-haired opponent gathered his Qi into his hands which produced a red glow, some strange patterns started appearing on his forearms that looked like they were made from fire. Huo Kong was going for a similar approach as with his previous opponent, first, rile him up and make him do the first attack, then he would block it and inject his fire type Qi into their body while defending. This was quite the simple battle plan, but worked quite well against easily irritable opponents with a chip on their shoulder.

The moment came soon, the Zhang Clan youth circled around Huo Kong while using his peculiar water gliding movement technique. He was gaining momentum, for his next attack. Soon he took his chance and jumped doing a nicely timed flying kick at his opponent's head and aiming at it from the back. His foot was shrouded in a watery energy that molded itself into a sharp blade, the youth charged forward while shouting.

"Take this Tidal Wave Scythe!"

Suddenly the scythe bubbled and increased in size, the foot was coming in an arch from the side and if Hou Kong didn't dodge his head would be flying into the air and probably killing the haughty youth in one strike.

"Hoho? Not half bad... but!"

Before the kick could slice the red-haired youth's neck he moved back, not to the side but behind. He leaned back while not bending his knees making look as if he was defying gravity and doing a peculiar popular dance move back from earth. The water scythe swung past him while producing quite the strong aftershock, which got dispersed by the shielding formation that the arena was set up with. This was a standard shielding formation that had to be installed to protect the audience members from any stray Qi attacks, that might come their way.

The kick swung past Huo Kong that was now open for a counter, he had quite the good opportunity to deliver a blow. He moved both his hands back as if he was going to do a handstand. While using his momentum from the previous back-dodge he tried landing a kick that was clad in fire energy at his enemy that just missed with the big swing that he did with his foot.

Luckily momentum wasn't only something the Huo clan youth was knowledgeable about, the bushy-eyebrow brother managed to spin around in time to receive the fire kick with his hands dispursing the attack somehow. He didn't go unscathed though, he noticed that the enemy was trying to inject his fire Qi into him to disturb his cultivation. He quickly activated his pillars that worked tirelessly to eject the invading spiritual energy.

"Eh?"

Huo Kong was surprised, he expected to get a clean hit in but only managed to send the other youth flying backward. He knew that his attack was somehow effective as the opponent with the sword eyebrows started sweating from the Qi expenditure.

"So you weren't a total pushover... but this doesn't change anything!"

The raid haired youth went on the offensive, his muscles bulged slightly as some kind of strange runic looking patterns appeared over his body. You could hear an explosion as he flew forward, this was his movement technique that produced small controlled explosions under his feet to produce short bursts of speed.

After the first exchange, the crowd cheered out in unison. the Zhang Clan member that were at the side were hoping that their brother would show this rude cultivator that they shouldn't be trifled with. But gasped out after seeing his water scythe miss the mark and him getting blown back several meters from the counter.

"Oh, that was a nice try but the blazing youth doesn't look impressed!"

The two continued clashing with each other, it looked like they were equally matched at the start but soon enough you could see the water cultivator getting pushed back. His robe started catching fire, his water Qi having trouble in dousing the spirit flames that were far more difficult to deal with than regular flames.

Still Huo Kong was surprised, he had a reason for calling out these Zhang Clan cultivators and it was a personal one. He hoped to show a one-sided massacre against this man in front of him, but his opponent was showing quite a high amount of skill. He was still confident in his victory, but he wanted to show the large gap in their techniques and aptitude. Instead the no-name sword-shaped eyebrow opponent showed everyone that he could keep up with him.

"Don't get cocky, this ends now!"

Suddenly the fire cultivator's power spiked, did he activate some kind of special skill or was he hiding some reserves, no one was sure. The abrupt change of pace surprised the Zhang Clan youth, that received a heavy hit to his stomach. He was unable to see the trajectory of the fist coming for him and was blown back by the strike by several meters.

The red-haired man cocked his fist back, red energy gathered and it looked as many tiny fireflies were quickly getting absorbed into the palm of his hand. The Zhang Clan youth knew that he was about to get hit by something big, so he used a defensive technique that produced a water shield. The previous strike took the wind out of his lungs, so this was the most he could do.

"Take this, Inferno Dragon Strike!"

The moment the fist got thrown forward a surge of fire Qi flew towards the defending cultivator, the fire started taking shape and turned into a dragon. The dragon head gave out a roar that sounded more like an explosion. On the other side, the Zhang Clan member had both his hands stretched out and he was getting surrounded by a thick bubble of water.

*BOOM*

Another explosion occurred, steam and wind getting kicked up while the vision of the audience members got blocked.

"Oh no, is this it? Can the watery youth defend against this strike?"

Everyone scooted closer to the arena trying to see if the fight was over, or if there would be some kind of comeback. After the smoke cleared, they could see the red-haired youth looking at something. At the spot, he was looking at stood the Zhang Clan youth, his bare chest was showing and his hair was in a mess. He was still standing and breathing though, looking as if he managed to power through this attack.

"Huff...huff... huff..."

He was panting hard, one of his eyes closed as he burned through quite a lot of his spiritual energy to defend against this attack. His opponent was clearly annoyed that he couldn't end the fight right there, he even had to push a lot of his spiritual energy into that attack but the annoying opponent was still standing there.

"Oh, he is still standing! What a twist!"

The people cheered out, shouting out the nickname of eyebrows-brother in unison. The youth in question was far too tired to grimace about his stupid nickname.

'That's enough, don't risk injury brother, leave him to me.'

The Zhang Clan youth twitched and then looked to the audience and there his clan members were standing. Zhang Liu sent his voice out next to his brother so that he would hear his message. He was feeling a bit apprehensive but he felt that he wouldn't come out unscathed if he battled this youth further.

Huo Kong looked at his opponent that stood up straight and clasped his hands.

"This is my defeat."

He didn't really wait for his opponent to reply and just turned around to leave, the audience getting a bit rowdy at the surrender but they knew that this water cultivator's spiritual reserves were all used up and he couldn't really continue the fight.

"Hmph!"

Huo Kong spit to the side and looked at the youth leave, then watched as another member from that group stepped forward. The youth was different in the way as his hair was mostly snow-white, with a patch of obsidian in the front.

"Guess it's not so easy to bully our Zhang Clan, now is it?"

"I'll be your next opponent!"

Chapter 132

Huo Kong looked at his next opponent, the youth was staring at him, just standing there. He had to agree that he had miscalculated slightly and that these cultivators weren't pushovers. Still, he didn't feel like he would lose even if each one fought him one after another.

"Oh, the friend of the previous contender wants to avenge him! Let's give him a round of applause!"

Zhang Liu's eyebrows twitched as everyone looked in his direction, he could feel people's eyes on him. This wasn't anything new as he was used to getting watched by his own clan members, still, he didn't like the feeling of getting gawked at.

"What a handsome young man..."

"Think he has a partner? He looks to be quite young too... probably some young master..."

"What beautiful snow-white hair!"

You could hear the women talking, Zhang Liu was quite the handsome young lad. Alas he wasn't concerned with things like that, finding cultivation far more important than a relationship. He tried to ignore the swarm of drooling groupies that he had just earned and looked at Huo Kong.

"Why don't you recover some of your stamina before we fight, you will need it..."

Zhang Liu spoke out while looking at the red-haired youth, who in response scoffed at him.

"What? Do you think I need to recover to fight someone like you? You're being overconfident for a little Zhang Clan whelp!"

Liu wasn't trying to be patronizing, he just wanted a fair fight and was trying to even the odds. On the other hand, Huo Kong thought that he would lose face if he were to take a recovery pill. He only fought a meager opponent and thought that he didn't require any outside help.

"I'll show you your place!"

Zhang Liu's face twitched, finally getting slightly angry. He didn't know why this man was so condescending towards his Zhang Clan, but he would show his opponent that they shouldn't be trifled with.

"Fine... show me my place then..."

He squinted and jumped into the ring while leaving an afterimage behind, the display of speed making Huo Kong back off slightly, startled by the display.

'He's fast...'

He instantly realized that this new opponent was far stronger than the ones he faced in the previous bouts. He wasn't discouraged though, he just gathered his energies. His whole body glowed in a bright red hue as the same runes appeared all over it.

"Oh what's this, the opponent seems to be very fast! Oh, is that lightning? Does the challenger cultivate in the Dao of the storms?"

This was an honest mistake, the Dao of the storms was an actual cultivation method in this world. It was a lesser Dao, lightning was just a side product of it though and not the main component.

Zhang Liu was already in the foundation establishment realm and in its middle stage. While being in the Qi condensation realm he couldn't really utilize the more complex techniques that Zhang Dong was using. Now though, he had quite the repertoire of them, they mostly being the same ones that his Master used. They were just versions that required less spiritual energy to use and were weaker in response to that.

Huo Kong didn't wait for his opponent to make the first move like he did with the previous ones. Instead he jumped in, his fists ready to deliver cultivation shattering blows. At least that's what he was attempting to do, but found himself dodging to the side as some sort of spear of concentrated spiritual energy flew towards him. The attack exploded against the arena floor and delivered a residual static shock to the fire cultivator.

This was a weaker version of Zhang Dong's Lightning Javelin, the skills specs got lowered to accommodate a lower cultivation realm. It packed less of a punch but was still a good earth graded technique. Huo Kong didn't have much time to rest as he felt a shiver run down his spine, he quickly did a 180-degree turn and put up a cross shape guard with his forearms. He made sure to push his fire Qi into this block, soon he received a palm strike that sent him flying backward for about ten meters.

Zhang Liu's hand was crackling with blue lightning energy, his opponent managed to push the invading energies away while a drop of sweat run down his forehead.

"Nice block, wonder if you can block the next one as well..."

The crowd exploded in cheers, the combat prowess of this new challenger was over the charts. They thought that no one could beat this fire youth, but this white-haired one was managing to push him back.

"Oh no, the Challenger's strikes are fast and swift like thunder, is this the end for the master of inferno?"

The commentator started coming up with more silly names while the audience shouted out and cheered on some more.

Zhang Liu wasn't underestimating his opponent, after the first clash he felt the massive amount of spiritual energy that his opponent possessed. It was still this high even after he went through six bouts without much rest, if he made a mistake and got too confident the momentum could quickly shift. That's why he was planning to go all-in and end it fast.

He moved his palm forward and tilted it slightly to the side while pointing it against his opponent. His feet were giving off sparks as he was ready to activate his movement technique. Huo Kong was looking at this display in distress as he knew that this opponent would be a tough cookie to crack.

In response to his opponent's fighting stance and forward movement, Huo Kong put his fists up. His body started glowing red and his muscles bulged, steam coming out of his pores which made him look quite peculiar. His hair started catching on fire and his eyes glowed red, he was apparently charging up some secret skill or ability to try and win this next exchange as he noticed that his opponent was going for the kill.

The two jumped forward, the ground under them cracking slightly as they took off. Both fighters were going for an equal exchange, power against power as they charged towards one another. Before they could do that though, something interrupted them.

"That's enough!"

Both of them felt immense pressure pushing them down to the ground and it also immediately canceled out their own spiritual energy. The two stopped in place a couple of meters from each other and looked to the side, to where the voice came from. There they saw an elder looking gentleman that had a characteristic mutton chop beard and was wearing a standard Huo Clan elder's robe.

"E-elder Qiao, t-this is..."

"Quiet! By your father's orders you were not to start trouble... and here you are offending the juniors from the Zhang Clan that we are allied with!"

The man jumped into the ring and moved while talking, he looked at Zhang Liu and recognized his fighting style to be quite similar to the one Zhang Dong had.

"Oh, what is this? Someone from the senior generation got involved? I must remind you that if you interrupt the fight all the winnings that the young lord battled for will be taken back by the arena staff. Also, there will be a fine for breaking the rules!"

Elder Qiao snorted at the announcer and moved closer to the red-haired youth, giving him a1 good smack on the head. He didn't care about those things, this brat would be paying out of his pocket anyway. He turned to the white-haired youth that looked quite confused, but he somehow remembered this man from the time at the secret ground.

"Ah... junior greets senior."

He did a polite bow towards him, making Huo Qiao nod in response as he didn't feel like he had to explain himself to someone of the junior generation.

"Let's go... your father will decide on your punishment."

"F-father?... wait, why don't we discuss this over some spirit wine..."

The youth rubbed his head while looking distressed, he sounded quite meek now. His bravado was thrown out of the window the moment his father's name was mentioned.

"I just wanted to show the clan's superiority...f-father always talks about the Zhang Patriarch so favorably..."

He trailed off with the last part of his sentence before getting dragged away, Zhang Liu and his companions just looked at the strange display while scratching their heads.

"Due to the unforeseen interruption we will be holding a small break, this bout will be seen as a draw and all the bets will be annulled."

They woke up from their stupor after the announcer's voice was heard. Zhang Liu then left the ring not really wanting to continue with the fighting as he didn't want to make a bigger scene than it already was. Though as he was trying to leave the arena he was surrounded by some ladies. They were all cute young girls that saw his fight and he made a big impact on them.

"Hey big brother you were so cool, why don't you invite us to some tea~"

"No, why don't we go visit some stalls at the market instead!"

"Where are you from, are you from some powerful clan, big brother?"

The girls assaulted him with various questions, they even moved closer and started yanking on his sleeves. They knew that this man was quite strong for his age, probably some kind of rich master as he even had a whole squad of similar-looking cultivators to guard him. The other boys grimaced as this Zhang Liu was stealing all the thunder, they also wanted a piece of that action.

While Zhang Liu was feeling distressed a certain person approached from the back.

'This is the perfect chance!'

The person in question was the girl that Liu bumped into a couple of hours ago. She had followed their group all the way here while hatching her devious plan. This was the best opportunity to pounce on her prey, her pink twintails bounced about in the sea of people as she got closer and closer.

Liu moved his hands upwards as he backed away, the girls looked like predators that saw a tasty snack. They were already seeing themselves rolling in spirit stones if they married a young master of this caliber. He looked to be strong, noble and good looking and by how expensive his robes looked, loaded as well. He was also quite young, below the age of twenty. They all were crafty vixens and knew that at this age it was easy to lure the boys in.

Suddenly Liu felt someone grasp his hand, it was quite the soft and small hand but there was quite the amount of power behind it. He soon felt himself getting yanked behind, the pulling power the person used was quite astonishing. He found himself getting captured by someone with light pink hair, the female was quite small not much over 150 cm. You wouldn't think that a small frame like that could produce so much power, but he found himself flying as he got tugged backward like a ragdoll.

"Follow me if you want to live!"

He wasn't sure what the small girl was talking about, but he wasn't in the position of replying as he got pulled out of the arena. He soon started running with the strange twin-tail girl, he recalled that he bumped into her previously, maybe she lost something during the exchange and wanted to talk to him about it?

The girls that they left behind shouted out something, so did the Zhang Clan members that were together with Zhang Liu but they soon got lost in the crowd of people. The small girl was surprisingly agile, managing to find the best route through the sea of people. So the two youths found themselves outside, Zhang Liu looked down at the woman.

The youth had a growth spurt in the past two years and was now of a similar height as his master and was quite well built as well. This made the short girl look even smaller. Though from what he could see, even though she was quite short she was plump in places that mattered. He wasn't sure what the girl wanted, but she had a strange smirk on her face.

"Um... can I help you with something?"

"Why yes, you can guide this big sister through the city but first... wait here for a second..."

She suddenly run away leaving the bewildered youth with a question mark above his head. He looked around and wondered if he should just leave, but after a minute the pink-haired girl was back.

"S-sorry did you wait long for me~?"

"Um... but you just..."

"No, you just arrived? Well, no use standing then, let's go!"

She grabbed his hand once more and dashed into the city, going for the more area where all the shops with clothes were. Zhang Liu just sighing inwardly as he remembered that his master told him that the Feng clan women were quite peculiar. He had since realized that this girl was one of them, so he didn't want to be rude towards an allied clan. So continued his first day at the new city, the rest would be filled with shopping and eating sweets.

Chapter 133

Zhang Liu wasn't sure what was going on, he got yanked around by the small yet busty girl through the city. They visited various places and he found himself holding a pile of robes while the pink-haired young lass was trying them on. He had a hard time seeing anything past them, by the number of clothes he was holding the shop clerks was even giving him looks of concern.

He wanted to tour the city, but this wasn't the way he imagined it. Every time he tried to speak up the girl butted in and pulled him to another location as if she was in some kind of rush. They visited places like restaurants, tea shops even went over to the area close to the big lake, the view was quite nice but he couldn't even take it in before he was yanked by the ball of energy that was this young lady.

'I don't even know her name...'

In time the young man could see that the sun was setting, this was the time that he was supposed to go back to his hotel. He even received some messages on his communication jade, asking about if he was okay as he just vanished from the arena.

"I think I should go back..."

He looked at the strange girl, that was holding various shopping bags, he himself was carrying quite the mountain of them. He did have a spatial ring of his own, but its size was limited. His mother forced him to cram it full of clothes and food, he had barely any space left for his weapons and pills in there.

When the youth spoke out, the girl looked back at the young male that she was with a big smile on her face.

"Back? we still need to walk around the beach... and go to a hot spring... then you would peek..., tee-hee."

She chuckled to herself as if she had some kind of dubious plan thought out. Though her companion was slowly getting fed up with it, luckily he wouldn't need to put up with the girl's antics for long as a certain old looking grandma that he was familiar with decided to show up.

"There you are, I've been looking all over the city for you!"

The person was an old elderly looking lady that looked like a baked potato that was out in the sun for too long, this was Feng Maling a member of the elder generation of the Feng Clan.

"W-what, h-how did you find me, granny!?"

The pink-haired girl's face sunk, she looked like she was afraid of this old lady that was slowly moving towards her with a cane in her hand. The moment she got closer she delivered a smack with that same cane of hers to the short girl's head, making her drop some of the shopping bags she was holding.

"Stop causing trouble for the clan and the Matriarch, we will be returning this instant!"

Zhang Liu looked from the side, as the old lady grabbed the short yet busty girl by the collar of her robe and started dragging her out. While the two were passing by the bewildered youth, the old woman stopped and looked at him.

"Those robes...Zhang Clan?... if I remember correctly..."

Zhang Liu shook out of his stupor and cupped his fists, giving the old woman a friendly bow, thus dropping all of the clothes and bought goods to the floor. The elder lady rubbed her chin a bit while the pink-haired oddball was squirming on the ground.

"Ah! You're the Zhang Patriarch's disciple, is he in the city perhaps?"

Zhang Liu smiled a bit as he was recognized and when his Master was mentioned, but then sighed out inwardly after the question was asked.

"Regrettably my Master had something important to attend to, so he won't be coming to the festival this year. In his stead my Gran... Grand Elder Jin will be attending..."

The old lady's eyebrows twitched quite a bit when she heard the name Zhang Jin, but she didn't comment on it. She just nodded and said her goodbyes.

"Is that so... the Matriarch will be disappointed if she hears that... Don't worry I'll take this troublemaker with me, send my regards to your Patriarch and.... never mind..."

She broke off the sentence and pulled the girl with the twin-tails along the floor, the girl was adamant about leaving.

"No granny, I'm just following the ancient text of the ancestors... I'm just following the ancestor's wishes!"

The granny's face showed a grimace while she kept yanking on her robe.

"Did you forget what the Matriarch decided on Nuana? You aren't supposed to follow the texts literally, now come you need to get punished!"

"What? I didn't do anything wrong, big sis is the one that's wrong!"

The squirming shorty replied while not being able to resist the core formation elder's might.

"That's Matriarch to you, now come along!"

The two finally vanished into another street leaving Zhang Liu with a bunch of female clothing in his possession. He rubbed his neck slightly and then used the communication jade to call for some people to help him carry all of these possessions.

"What was that?"

He spoke out loud while waiting for a clan member with an empty spatial ring to arrive, he was meaning to return these trinkets that the girl bought when he saw her next time.

Back at Spirit Spring City.

Zhang Dong was looking at his system screen, there he saw the system timer that showed him what time it was. It was only five more minutes until midnight, he was sitting in a lotus position far away from the buildings that were in this small pocket dimension. He was looking at the clock, the seconds ticking down as it was time for the points to arrive.

"Finally... I managed to craft some new pills while waiting for this day to be over..."

He spoke out while sitting down, he was ready to push through to the Nascent Soul realm. Though, by pushing through, he meant pushing the 'yes' button on the upgrade cultivation tree and just letting the magic happen.

'Ah, it sure is nice having a system like this, supposedly it's very difficult to reach the nascent soul level. If you follow the instructions badly or aren't fully at 100% with your cultivation your core might just explode without creating a soul instead.'

The plan was easy, upgrade to the nascent soul then create an item in the heaven grade so that he could absorb it and get his body refining technique to the next level as well. He didn't feel like there should be any problems with it in any way, the place he was in would block his aura from seeping out.No one should notice when he reaches the new realm of power, leaving him secured from his enemies.

'That Dao Festival thing should be over by the time I'm finished here. I told grandpa to invite the other clans for a visit when it ends. I'll tell them my plan, it should work...'

He glanced at his clan building part of the system, the points were there but it had some other uses besides just gathering passive points for his system. This other use was something he was banking on and that would allow him to beat the wall that was the Dark Palm sect.

'I just need some time and soon we'll have Nascent Soul cultivators in the truckloads!'

He grinned, wondering how those overbearing sects would react to a sudden reveal of multiple nascent soul elders.

'They'd probably pee their robes...'

How would he achieve this? The system somehow decided on the area's that he was the 'owner' off. He could put buildings and raise its level for more points, that was just one of the functions. The other one concerned his clan that was in the faction tab.

If he brought up his faction, he could see the whole structure with a little icon of him right at the top. The whole thing looked a bit like a pyramid with him at the top, then the clan members going into the lower parts. He could even click parts of this pyramid to get more in-depth. If a faction member had enough trust in him, he could read their stats without needing to use his analyzing skill or touching them.

This was quite handy, as he was able to tell if someone was shady by just the amount of trust they had in him. Still, they could just not like him without any ulterior motives. The other good part was, that similar to his disciples he could spend his system points on his faction members.

He could actually directly increase their cultivation level with a click of a button. This was the option that was most important, pushing through to the nascent soul level was immensely taxing on the practitioner. The cultivation techniques in this world were also of low quality bringing a lot of random chance into the mix. Matt had figured out, that anything below the immortal grade brought huge risks. Even heaven grade skills weren't all that good and brought risks with them.

'Well, my cultivation method is in the immortal grade so it should be safe even without the systems help, and after I level it up I'll be able to combine it with some other cultivation manuals.'

He was hoping on boosting the other cultivation manuals like the ones the Zhang Clan practitioners used with his new Nascent Soul one. If the combination worked, he could be able to get a cultivation manual at the immortal grade as his own was already in the higher grading of the immortal grade.

'Hm, wonder if it's compatible though... lightning and water? Maybe some kind of Storm Nascent Soul... or would that be more in the wind Dao area...'

'Mixing lower and higher grades mostly produces something just slightly better than the technique that was worse though...'

'I could also try coming up with something myself...'

This was also something the system rewarded him for, he could try to create his own techniques. If it was something that wasn't in his library, the system would give him some crafting points. He had created some variations in his skills like that, mostly weaker ones. He was knowledgeable enough, about his own cultivation method that he could come up with those. The foundation establishment techniques his disciples were using were created by him, without the use of the system.

'It's harder to do it myself, but if I do it my progress in the skill is much faster... but also could be incomplete...'

There were no guidelines that let him move through the proficiency in the technique he created himself. He'd need to test it out by himself and see how good it was before the system gave him a rating.

'But anyway, I should focus on the task at hand, midnight is here!'

He heard a little ding sound, the system could be set up as an alarm clock. His points moved past ten million and he was ready to finally go beyond the threshold. He was stuck at the Great Circle for two years, he wasn't able to get a nascent soul item to push his body refining a stage further either, but now he was going to do both at once and no one could stop him!

He quickly started sliding his finger on his system window, going to his skill tree and clicking on his Divine Golden Lightning Core cultivation method.

Divine Golden Lightning - Updrage to Divine Golden Lightning Soul Yes/No?

His finger hovered above the 'Yes' button as he gulped, he looked around the area he made it sure to be on the edge of the floating island in space as he didn't know if this level up would be an explosive one.

'Here we go!'

He pushed it and saw as his points dropped down to a couple of thousand. He could feel the knowledge of his new skill flowing into his mind, the ways of creating a perfect Divine Golden Lightning Soul lay bare to him. He tossed his head back, his eyes shining with a gold hue as lightning power gathered all around him.

"Here it comes!"

He clenched his fists, energy surging all around him as... nothing happened... absolutely nothing. Matt blinked a bit stupified, he had clearly got the information for the Nascent Soul cultivation method. It got injected into his brain, like it always did when he got new techniques or knowledge. The problem was that the system didn't push him through the threshold.

"Wait... do I need to do it on my own? Or maybe spend more system points...ffffffffffffffffffuuuuuuu...."

Chapter 134

Matt scratched his head and looked out into the void of the small pocket dimension he was staying at. He thought back to the times that he upgraded his cultivation method.

'Each time I did it the change was instantaneous... I could feel my lightning getting reforged along with my body as if I studied the improved version of the skill my entire life... but nothing happened now...'

He crossed his hands while still sitting in the lotus position, his eyes moving up as he thought about what could be the problem.

'Maybe it's because it's a jump in a larger realm and not a small realm?... also could be because of the system change...'

He looked into his system library and could see the technique written down in it, he already absorbed the knowledge from it after pushing the upgrade button. Matt then brought up his status screen, nothing had changed or at least he couldn't see anything out of the ordinary. That was until he clicked his 'Cultivation Base Qi' section of his status.

Cultivation Base Qi : | Core Formation [Great Circle 100%] (Divine Golden Lightning Core) | Upgrade available: 5 000 000

His eyes went bloodshot as he looked at the number of points he had to spend to level up. He needed close to two years to get ten million and now this stupid system wanted even more. Now, even though he had built up a base of power and he was getting a good amount of them through his clan building, he would probably have to wait at least half a year.

'Think I'll have to do it the hard way...no way I'm waiting for that long...I should be able to do it manually...'

He gave off a sigh, this would be somewhat difficult. The technique to push through was quite intricate and didn't allow for mistakes.

'I have to guide the divine energies through my meridians and my dantian like this... then slowly nourish my core till it expands... if I do it too fast it could break crippling me in the process. That is if I'm lucky, a broken core could end up fatal for the practitioner if they don't manage to create even a slither of a nascent soul.'

'If I nourish it too slowly, I could fail and also get crippled though I'd only get stuck a bit past half a step into the nascent soul... but the texts say, that this type of cultivation is unstable and would lower my lifespan dramatically. I'd be stuck in that realm for the rest of my life too...'

He groaned out loud, both of the options were quite bad though the second one was a bit better, he would still be quite strong just stuck with his life depleting.

'If I nourish my core with the divine lightning it should expand and then slowly pulsate and break apart revealing a soul underneath. After that, I should reach the nascent soul stage and have my life span and strength multiply dramatically. '

'At least the manual is quite throughout, it also mentions the fact that a practitioner should only try this if they reach the true Apex of the great circle, which would be the half-step realm I am in right now.'

He recalled what he knew and what he read from all the other cultivation manuals. He had enough to compare too, his own technique got upgraded to the perfect grade of the immortal grade.

'The technique is quite throughout in its explanation there is not much left to chance like with the heaven grade manuals that I got from that library...'

Thanks to how good his cultivation manual was, he didn't really need any outside help to burst through this level. The lesser ones sometimes forced the practitioners to take pills or some magical treasures that could circumvent some inefficiencies.

For instance, one of the fire-based nascent soul manuals that his friend from the Huo clan took. Required him to procure a rare fire lotus, without it his chances of breaking through were slim and he would probably get crippled in the process.

From what he could deduct, only cultivation guidebooks in the immortal grade didn't require outside sources for breaking through. Though you could still aid the process which would lessen the chance of failure even more. There always was a chance of something going wrong, so best to prepare for all necessities.

'I have to think this through, I'm a goner if I make a mistake...though the success rate of this cultivation technique seems to be quite high. I already have the best kind of foundation thanks to the divine core upgrade, my foundation pillars have also changed to perfect divine ones'

Matt decided to write his manual out, he wanted to read it a couple of times and prepare for everything. He wouldn't just wing it, what if he made a blunder and ended up a cripple or dead? The chance of success was high, he was still afraid of failure but he didn't see a problem in giving it a try.

'This will take a while though... maybe I can make some kind of pill to help me out...also there were some formations I could set up to aid me...'

The Dao of crafting was on his side, he already got the forging and treasure creation part to be at the topmost of core formation, even edging it into half a step into the nascent soul. There were various things he could create that would help him keep his spiritual energy from going berserk.

The night passed while Matt made his battle plan and prepared for his ascension into the Nascent Soul. The day of the Dao tournament preliminary round finally arrived and everyone was ready to take their test. The first one would calculate their all-around power, this was done by a large bell treasure. How it worked was, the practitioner would deliver a palm strike with all their might. Depending on the number of chimes the bell struck, their power would be measured.

If you wanted to pass this test, the large bell had to sound at least three times. This was something a practitioner in the foundation early-stage should be able to produce. Though if they had a flawed foundation they would find this test challenging. Four to five chimes would indicate a middle stage degree of strength, six to seven a late one and eight to nine would put you in the great circle. If you managed more than that while being in the foundation stage, it would indicate that you had quite the talent.

The contestants gathered around multiple of those large magical bell treasures, the number of people taking part in this test was staggering and it would probably take the whole day for everyone to get tested, maybe even longer.

There were only five of those bells, each contestant had to stand in a line and wait their turn. People were segregated by their clans and how they registered earlier. Some clans or sects with more pull could pay a bit extra to get a better spot. Some even could outright circumvent the whole testing process, if they had enough prestige or influence.

Zhang Clan was somewhere in the middle, not being considered a really strong clan or a weak one either, just an average, maybe slightly above average one. That was mostly thanks to the personal strength of their Patriarch, which defeated a group of core formation cultivators while defending Spirit Spring City. Also, when he defeated the Demon Hunter about a month ago. Though most people were skeptical about the state of the other clan members, thinking them to be mediocre at best.

'Ding...ding... ding...'

"Three chimes... Passed!"

'Ding....ding....'

"Only two, Failed!"

There wasn't really a limit to how many people a sect or clan could bring here, you could even participate as a solo cultivator. If you could fork up enough spirit stones, the organizers were more than happy to let you give it a shot. They didn't care if you were even illegible for it, they didn't care if you made yourself look like a fool by not being able to sound a bell even once.

But this was still a place where you could show of your aptitude. So, a lot of people were willing to have a go at it. Qualifying past the preliminary round was already seen as a boon. Some clans or sects would take a renegade cultivator into their mids if they managed to get past the tests. Due to this, the number of people increased several folds. Some were participating and some were scouting for prospects.

The participants didn't get an exact time for their test, so they needed to wait in line for hours. Luckily for the Zhang Clan, they were somewhere in the middle prestige wise, so they wouldn't need to wait till the end of the day to take their test.

"Hey, isn't it that person from the Huo Clan..."

One of the Zhang Clan members spoke up, he noticed Huo Kong stepping up to the bell. The fire clan being one of the more established ones, they had the luxury of taking the test a lot sooner than most of the other families and sects. The red-haired youth had a solemn expression on his face, he looked a lot less chipper than how he lucked when he was beating up people in the arena.

He walked up to the bell and looked at it, then just moved his hand backward while standing up straight. He infused his palm with some spiritual energy and propelled it forward, striking the measuring treasure dead center.

"Ding...ding...ding...ding...ding...ding..."

He received six chimes without trying all that much, the last one being a bit faint. The people in the area gasped out, as this indicated a strength level in the late stage. This was of course if you calculated it by average cultivator standards.

"So he was this strong..."

"But it didn't look like he was even trying... maybe he could get seven of those..."

The Zhang Clan people looked from the side, already knowing that this youth was holding back. There wasn't really a reason to go all out against these measuring treasures, unless you were barely eligible for the tournament. It was always better to keep your secrets hidden, then use your best moves when facing a strong opponent.

The testing continued, the Huo clan youths showed a good amount of strength but no one else was able to produce six chimes. The rest was able to make it sound between four and five times, which was still quite good for their age.

The day continued and more sects and clan's kept ringing the bell. The clans that had enough renown were able to make their members pass without any problems. There were some youths that only managed to sound it out twice though, but they quickly left the stage in shame.

Zhang Liu was slowly getting bored of waiting, but soon he noticed another familiar person going up to the stage. The person being the girl that he met in the city and he still had her clothes tucked in a spare spatial ring. It was time for the Feng Clan to make their appearance, it was a female-only one so it made quite the waves. But not in a positive sense, as most men in this world weren't really into the dark skin that the women of that clan had.

You'd mostly see women getting called fairies and approached by horny youths, this time around though, the dark-skinned girls were giving the boys some strange looks. The men gulped while looking at the faces buried under copious amounts of makeup.

"What are you looking at, want this big sister to keep you company?"

"Hey, those guys are kind of cute, we should talk to them after the test..."

"Hey, aren't they from the Zhang Clan, that one with the bushy eyebrows is so my type..."

The puckered up their lips while looking at some men from the crowd that they deemed attractive. The men in question having mixed feelings about the whole thing.

Chapter 135

The Feng Clan, Zhang Clan, and Huo Clan were all in good relations. The gyaru gang saw the male members from the other two clans as potential Daoist partners. While the girls were chatting among themselves, their elders were slowly getting impatient. They didn't come here to find potential partners, but to showcase their clan's power and superiority.

The girls soon got to it, while their elder encouraged them by giving them a smack on the head. The current elder that was responsible for the Feng ladies, wasn't anyone that the Zhang Clan members knew. The Matriarch or the granny elder that everyone was familiar with wasn't here either. Soon the bells started ringing and the girls began passing with flying colors. The clan was mindful enough to not bring anyone with them that wouldn't be able to pass the first strength test.

Zhang Liu looked with interest at the girl that he had a short encounter with, moved up to the stage. He didn't think that she would be participating in the test, but there she was. She walked over slowly, making everyone take in her rather cute facial features. The bouncing of her chest only added to the neck-craning that most of the youths were doing now.

Feng Nuana arrived at the large bell, which made her look even smaller. She looked quite fierce, like an angry puppy. Her eyebrows furrowed and her palm moving closer to her own body as she took a wind up. A gust of wind was produced the moment she smacked the large bell with her small hand, producing quite the amount of dinging sounds. The added wind pressure made her skirt dance around, the boys from the side just gawking.

"Ding...ding...ding...ding...ding...ding...ding..."

The treasure stopped at seven strikes, which caught the attention of many participants as this was the highest number in their age range. This was already a power level of someone at the peak of the late stage of foundation establishment. This girl was twenty-one at most, so this was quite the feat.

"Big sister Nuana is the best!"

"She is the pride of our Feng Clan!"

"Yay sister Nuana!"

The girls cheered out loud while the other clans and sects looked at the tiny girl preforming the feat of strength. The girl in question crossed her hands over her quite voluptuous chest and stuck it out proudly. She moved her head up high and took in the praise that the other clan members were giving her, looking quite satisfied. Before coming down from the stage her eyes met with Zhang Liu's and she gave him a little wink.

'Are all those Feng women like this?'

Zhang Liu looked around the area to the other girls, but he grimaced some more due to the overuse of makeup that made the girls kind of unappealing. The short one at least looked decent enough and her skin wasn't as dark as the rest of the others.

'Master said that jade-like skin wasn't all that great... but I'm not sure about that...'

The female cultivators all made the cut, for now, all of the cultivators from the Huo clan and the Feng clan had made it through the first test. But they were in the minority as shortly after they left the stage, the other participants started failing.

"Get ready, you will be taking the test, don't embarrass the clan!"

The Zhang Clan youths stood at attention as they were the next in line. The clans that followed after the Feng Clan weren't doing all that great. Their members were mostly at the four or three bell range, some of them couldn't even get past two. This was probably due to the lower quality of their cultivation techniques.

"Show them why we from the Zhang Clan are on the rise, young warriors!"

The elder gave the youths some inspiring words. They were still getting underestimated by the other big families in the area, but this would soon change. One of the youths moved on to the stage, but no one was really paying that much attention as people were interested in the more powerful clans that took the test at the beginning. Though even from them, there wasn't a young master that broke past six chimes and Feng Nuana was still holding the top spot.

"I'll go up, first brothers and sisters."

The youth with the sword-shaped eyebrows decided to make his move, he would show that even he a regular member of the clan was quite gifted when compared to the other families. He looked at the person that was standing next to the measuring treasure, it was a man that was wearing quite the long robe and a long hat. The man was old and had a scroll in his hand, on that scroll he had all the names of the Zhang Clan members that would be participating in the test.

"You may proceed."

He noted the name of this clan member while yawning slightly. It was the middle of the day and these workers didn't really have any time off, and there was still a massive line of people after this still waiting. He didn't really care about this average clan, half of these people would probably not make the cut or just barely make it in at three chimes.

"Ding...ding...ding...ding...ding...."

He looked at the bell that started ringing, there were clearly five times that it rung and that would put this youth in the talented bracket. This was quite surprising for an average clan like this. The man with the scroll noted the number of bell sounds next to the youth's name, thinking that they probably had their most notable junior member start it off.

"Five, not bad... next..."

The young man with the sword eyebrows moved down the stage and another one with a similar blue robe moved up. His palm started glowing in blue color before it descended on the measuring apparatus.

"Ding...ding...ding...ding...ding...."

"Oh... five again..."

The elder official wrote down the name and test results again and watched as the blue-robed youth moved down the testing area. The youth looked dejected, making it seem like he was expecting a better score. Five was already quite high in the man's opinion, so why as this youth like that?

The man figured out why the young male looked sad, as following him his other clan members took the stage.

"Ding...ding...ding...ding...ding...."

"Ding...ding...ding...ding..."

"Ding...ding...ding...ding...ding...."

"Ding...ding...ding...ding..."

The youths continued having stellar results apparently they were all above a regular foundation establishment cultivator in the early stage.

"Is the measuring device broken?"

The man was starting to worry, did something happen to the treasure. How could a plain clan like this have youths this strong and below the age of twenty-one? His eyes popped out even more after a certain young lady moved up onto the stage. She was quite the beauty with long white hair a patch of black to the side. A lot of people from the side craned their necks, while whispering to each other.

"Who is that... such beauty!"

"What clan is that... I must get that fairy's name!"

This was Zhang Xue moving up to the stage, her palm already crackling with deep blue lightning energies. It descended on the measuring treasure, a sound of thunder echoing through the whole testing stage.

"Ding...ding...ding...ding...ding....ding"

"Six?... at such an age?..."

The elder that was writing down the results on the scroll gawked, he had the names and the ages of the participants written down here. The age of this young lass was only seventeen and she was already stronger than all of the twenty-year-olds that came before her.

"Only six... I thought I could get seven..."

The cute girl looked a bit glum, she wanted to at least tie for the first place with the girl from the Feng Clan. Still at the age that she was, she was the undisputed champion.

"Good going junior sister."

She went down from the stage while Zhang Tai moved up, he smirked a bit after seeing the reaction of the people around them. It was time to show them that this Zhang Clan was here do make waves. He gathered up his energies and focused, his palm started shining with water-based Qi. This Qi was far purer than the one his brothers utilized, it soon descended on the bell in question and the chiming began.

"Ding...ding...ding...ding...ding....ding...ding...d...."

The last one didn't manage to go through, leaving his result at seven and tying it with the Feng Clan girl. Though, people would put him above her at seven and a half as it almost sounded the last one out.

"Hah, that should do it!"

The other clans and sects started to slowly gather around the area that the Zhang Clan was getting tested. The amount of foundation establishment youths that managed to have at least four chimes was staggering and this last one almost produced eight.

Zhang Tai moved down the stage and smirked while looking at Zhang Liu, signaling him with his gaze that he was challenging him. Liu just looked back at him with a smirk of his own. The two were close to each other in strength, but that was only due to Liu not using Zhang Dong's techniques that gave him stat boosts.

He had learned a lesser version of the technique that Zhang Dong used when he was battling the nascent soul Pride demon. This wasn't the avatar form and the condensation technique stack onto each other though. Matt had combined the two to produce a much more efficient one for himself, that didn't turn him into a ripe tomato after draining him of his stamina. His disciple was handed a lesser but still, it let him increase both his strength and speed by an equal amount.

Matt had to give it a grandiose name, so after much consideration, he ended up with 'Embodiment of the Thunder God'. He added the lesser term to the one his disciple was using as it was weaker and he planned to add a 'Superior' or 'True' prefix if he managed to upgrade it past the core formation level. The safe way of using this skill with no drawbacks was to only have it increase your stats by a half. But you could also double or triple your fighting prowess with harsher drawbacks.

Zhang Liu wanted to use this technique, focusing it only on his palm along with his regular striking form. He gathered up his energies, the lightning started crackling while everyone watched from the sides. His hand started getting coated by a blue aura, electricity crackling around it and it looked as if his hand had turned into lightning energy itself. The youth had similar looking hair to the young woman that was there just a minute ago. The people concluded that the two were probably siblings as this youth was also on the more handsome side.

Before Zhang Liu's palm could descend on the bell that would make it produce eight or more chimes he heard something. This was the sound of his grandfather's voice, getting sent next to his ear.

"Listen Liu, lower your cultivation..."

The youth clicked his tongue at the order, but he wasn't willing to go against his grandfather's word. His palm smacked against the measuring treasure in a similar fashion as his sister did.

"Ding...ding...ding...ding...ding....ding...ding"

He reached quite a high number of seven hits still, it was a bit less than what Zhang Tai had managed. It was quite the result though, putting him and Tai along with Feng Nuana at the top of the charts.

"Hah, I win this time little Liu..."

Zhang Liu scoffed at Tai that was smirking at him, he would have gotten at least eight chimes if his grandpa didn't force him to lower his score. He wasn't sure what it was all about, from his standpoint standing out was a good thing as it would bring glory to the clan and his master. It would show that they are the best and the strongest around.

While the testing continued into the night, a certain youth with a small gem returned to the large pagoda hotel. He cupped his hands in front of another man. This man was Yang Kai and he had an even larger jewel stuck in his forehead.

"Disciple greets Master!"

"En. So, how were they?"

The man was seated in a lotus position and was doing some cultivation exercises. He wasn't even facing his disciple while he was talking to him.

"Just as Master expected, they were quite weak. The best one only reached seven, this disciple managed to attain ten the last time he was tested."

"Mmm..."

The man didn't reply while his disciple just bowed again and left, knowing well that this was the signal for him to leave. He felt a bit apprehensive of taking part in this stupid festival, but his Master's orders were paramount. He didn't have to go through the preliminary round at least, thanks to this being a Dark Palm sect hosted event.

'Guess those country bumpkins must have made Master angry, but those two fairies looked enchanting. Wonder if Master will let me have them if I perform well...'

Chapter 136

The First test came to an end and the day came to a close. The first test was mostly there to get rid of contestants at the lower spectrum. There was no place for people that weren't at a base foundation establishment level. The second trial would test the practitioner's bravery and resilience. The youths would gather in a room with a special treasure. This treasure would give out a menacing killing intent that would be akin to a demonic beast at the middle stage of foundation establishment. The task was quite rudimentary, the contenders would have to receive the killing intent and move forward. If they could move past the placed treasure they would make it into the next round of testing.

This sounded quite easy, even easier than the first test that you had to actually present some bodily strength. In reality, killing intent from demonic beasts was quite invasive. It would cause a person to freeze up and pass out, the demonic aura invading your body and soul. Most early foundation establishment cultivators would find it troublesome. Thus this test was mostly in place to weed out people with a shaky foundation. Badly flawed pillars didn't give a warrior enough protection against this type of mental attack. But there were specialized techniques that blocked killing intent from affecting the practitioner's mind.

"How many of them passed again?"

"All of them passed..."

The person that was responsible for test the earlier day asked about the results of that Zhang Clan. They had made a good impression in the first one, so he was curious about their results which were quite shocking.

"How can they all have passed... resisting such a high amount of demonic killing intent isn't even easy for more battle-hardened warriors!"

There was one standard way that people got used to killing intent. It was quite easy, you just had to face off against many demonic beasts or cultivators, or take part in battles. You would steadily get used to fighting and build up a strong mind that would block things like killing intent from even stronger beings than you. But these were young kids from a middle-sized clan, did they lock them away in some demonic beast infested woods or something, was what this person was thinking.

"Can you tell me how it happened, exactly?"

"Sure brother... it was quite astonishing"

The person responsible for the second test explained everything from his point of view. The rooms that were used for the tests were quite large and could house up to a hundred cultivators at a time. This was mostly due to the treasure that produced the killing intent having a wide range.

The Zhang Clan participants gathered all together. They weren't the only people in the testing chamber though, with them were two other clans that each had twenty-five people. The Zhang Clan had close to fifty participants. The treasure that was giving off the ominous aura was placed at the other side of the chamber, with the cultivators opposite it in a straight line.

The treasure in question looked like a small statue of a demonic beast, inside of it was a demon beast core and it was fashioned in a way to release the killing intent. The man that was responsible for the test didn't think much about the whole thing. The only thing out of the ordinary was the number of people from the Zhang Clan, that were still participating. Normally it would be about half of that, just like the other clans that had twenty-five people with them.

The item was activated and the test started. The juniors were supposed to each the other end of the room where the treasure stood and just walk out of the door behind it. This would indicate that they passed, the whole test also had a time limit of thirty minutes. The man recalled seeing the participants from the other clans. Their faces sunk and they started looking quite pale after getting hit by the demonic aura. They sluggishly moved forward, one step at a time, some of them were even barely dragging their feet forward while resisting the killing intent.

"But those Zhang people were strange... they looked fine but they weren't moving forward... I thought that they had passed out while standing at first. To my surprise, they started walking nonchalantly... they looked fine... like the demonic aura wasn't affecting them at all..."

This was all thanks to Tranquil Mind, which was an already widespread technique around the whole clan. It had zero drawbacks and allowed everyone to think calmly under pressure. It also mitigated killing intent that wasn't over a certain degree, making this test a cakewalk for everyone involved.

"Some of them struggled at the end... but they all made it out within the first ten minutes, the best person from the other clans only managed to leave after a full fifteen minutes!"

The man that asked about the information rubbed his chin, trying to digest the information.

"This Zhang Clan is strange... think we should keep an eye on them. Even people from out Dark Palm sect would have trouble with this test..."

The man was slowly getting curious about this small clan, this wasn't anything serious from his standpoint just yet though. There were more tests after this one, it was still up to debate if more of those Zhang Clan juniors made the cut. The next one would actually test their battle prowess and was also the one that weeded out most of the junior practitioners from the tournament.

The next test was named 'The corridor of puppets' and the name kind of said it all. The participant would walk into the corridor that was quite lengthy and wide. In the said corridor, he or she would find multiple puppets that were similar in power to cultivators in the early and middle stages of foundation establishment. He or she was then supposed to get through this wide passage while being attacked by the angry automatons.

The dolls were quite merciless in their defense, they would quickly surround you delivering punches and kicks. It was quite brutal so the festival organizers had a team of medics on standby. There were numerous of those automatons around which made slipping past them hard. This wasn't all though, there were various traps placed around the area as well. They were mostly there to hinder anyone from just running past the automatons, this wasn't supposed to be just a test of evasion and speed. The participants had to dodge, block and even attack to somehow manage through.

"This should eliminate at least half of those Zhang Clan brats... maybe even more..."

The man smirked, the day of the test had arrived and it was now close to the end. He went inside the building that his companions were grading everyone. He quickly spotted someone that he was familiar with, this man would fill him in on the results of that clan that he was interested in.

"Brother, could I have a moment of your time!"

He went over, giving a standard greeting and then explained everything to the man.

"Hm... the Zhang Clan?... wait... you mean 'that' Zhang Clan?"

The man's tone changed when he was talking about that family in question, the curious man was even more intrigued

"Oh, did something happen? Don't keep me waiting brother, now you got me interested!"

The man responsible for the third test of the aforementioned 'Corridor of Puppets' recounted the events that transpired. The other junior participants were more or less doing the same, the higher-rated clan's had more passing while the lower-rated ones barely managed. Then this Zhang Clan came along, they had the most participants still in the run. Most of the others had from ten to twenty members still in it at most.

This was quite normal as even though each clan helped their junior members out, they mostly focused their resources on a small number of elites. These elite junior members would end up victorious while the lesser ones would stay behind. The Zhang Clan was different in the way, that all of their participants were well rounded. They had their top members with Zhang Tai, Xue and Liu but the rest weren't slouches either. If you compared them to the rest, they were in the elite category and they were many of them.

So, the test started with a bang. A white-haired youth just bulldozed through the corridor without letting any of the puppets even touch him once. He evaded all of the traps and probably set a new record if there was one being kept. Afterward, they continued, no one could match the youth that was first but they still did their best. The later members didn't come out unscathed, leaving with bruises and disheveled hair but all of them managed to power through this test as well. The weaker members had it rough, some of them had to be carried off for healing. Still, all of them made it through, making them have the largest group of people left for the last trial.

This was the second to last testing ground, after this one would come an area that was a mix of all the previous tests. The number of people that the Zhang Clan had put them at quite the advantage though. The last trial was a close of space, a secret ground of sorts. It was a giant maze area where everyone would be put in. It encompassed the entire city and was built right under it.

Every participant would receive a small token. This token represented his life, the purpose of this test was for the junior members to battle it out, with their tokens on the line. You needed at least three of those tokens to pass, if you managed to procure enough you would get marked. The tokens would start giving off a sort of marker aura, that would alert everyone to your location.

The people with enough tokens could then move on to the exit while trying to evade the other participants that would block their way. So even if you lost your token you could still recover everything from another person. Like with the other trials this also had a time limit. You could win by getting three tokens and waiting it out to the end. A reasonable tactic was to wait close to an exit and just steal the tokens from the person that was trying to get out.

"With so many of those Zhang Clan juniors, they have a clear advantage..."

The last test was a battle royale, but people could form groups. Due to the number of practitioners that made it through the previous tests, this clan had a strong advantage over the rest.

"Still, the other clans and sects can also form a bigger group to go against them."

This would probably be the thing that would happen. The names of participants and to what faction they belonged to would be hung out in front of the trial ground. It would open a few days later, leaving enough time for other clans to make some deals. This was also something that was advised and approved by the people that were hosting this tournament. Being able to form alliances was also a measure of strength so it was all fine.

The curious man decided to see how it turned out, but in secret, he went to place a bet on the clan that in his opinion had quite the potential. The number of people that were left after the preliminary rounds at the end, mostly came up to about a hundred. There were close to five hundred participants left, so you'd think that about 160 of them could make it through.

That was a naive way of thinking though. Even though you only needed three tokens, most of the participants would take more than the minimum amount required. There were even times where the contestant count dropped below fifty, when some strong clans with a couple of geniuses made a pact. The next trial would be beginning soon, the ones that made it out, in the end, would be hailed as the big winners and the future elite. The rest only to be forgotten and used as stepping stones for the new wave of young masters.

Chapter 137

The day before the last test a group of cultivators was sitting together. There were various faces, young and old but they came here for one reason, to make a deal. One man, in particular, stepped out to the center stage. He looked like any ordinary old cultivator uncle with a beard and dressed in your standard cultivator robe.

"I am glad that you have chosen to participate, brothers and sisters."

The man spoke in a relaxed tone while looking at the people in the room, one of them quickly replying to his statement.

"Not like we have much choice in this, those three other clans will be a problem..."

"En, you speak the truth, not sure where that Zhang Clan came from, but even the Feng and Huo clan are supporting them..."

"Yes, they clearly want to steal all the top spots for themselves!"

The other people in the room chimed in, this was a hastily organized meeting with a couple of the more influential clans that were still in the competition.

"Together we have about two hundred juniors, this should be enough of a fighting force to take care of them!"

There were about twenty clans here, together they had a bit over two hundred junior members that were still participating in the preliminary round.

"If we join hands we can defeat the others, easily."

"Yes, the only problem is that there might not be enough tokens for everyone, how do we go about this problem?"

Everyone nodded, there were close to five hundred people taking the whole test. The person participating had to have three tokens to pass the stage, but there were only five hundred of those tokens to pass around. They needed close to six hundred for all of their people, so someone would need to stay behind.

"Well, my friends how about we do it like this. Everyone picks out one or two juniors from their group, that you think aren't up to par... and they will just give up the tokens, to their more superior brothers and sisters. How does that sound?"

The people started murmuring, which sounded like a good strategy that wouldn't cause much internal strife.

"The other option would be to get rid of the other clans and then have the juniors compete against each other normally..."

The group started rubbing their chins and whispering among each other. The second option sounded worse but would be seen as a lesser evil against their junior members. Their young members would probably hold grudges against their elders, if they were told to just drop out of the competition. But if they went with the second option, the number of contestants would drop even further. Also, injuries could happen rendering more of their juniors out of commission.

The people inside the room debated the pros and cons of both options. In the end, it was decided that the first one allowed for the maximal number of members. The clans would rather try their luck in the main tournament, with more juniors participating than gamble in this last test. Already being able to take center stage with all the other sects and clans watching, was a grand achievement of its own.

While those clans were having their meeting, three other families were doing the same thing. They didn't hide though and were right in the pagoda hotel. Zhang Jin was on one side with a couple of senior members from his clan, sitting down with a teacup in his hand. Opposite of him sat a Huo Clan elder with mutton chops for a beard, his name was Huo Qiao. The third member was a granny that looked like she spent her whole life farming in the sun, her name was Feng Maling.

They had gathered here for the same reason as the other clans that were plotting against them. The three seniors were crafty old foxes and had foreseen the other families going against them.

"I guess we have no other choice, I wished that we could have had a regular competition for out juniors without us old seniors getting involved."

Zhang Jin spoke out while setting the empty cup of tea on the table.

"Well, you have to see them from their perspective brother Jin."

Huo Qiao replied while leaning back in his chair.

"Yes, your Zhang Clan has gathered quite the number of promising youths... maybe you can talk your Patriarch into giving our juniors some pointers. Think you owe me a bit of face since the last time we met..."

The granny spoke out while squinting her eyes at Zhang Jin, the two had some history the old man having claimed this old lady as one of his targets back in the day.

"Oh...ho...ho... senior brings up old tales from my younger days, I was just young and curious..."

The man coughed into his hand while looking to the side, he didn't think that his old love interest would be in this city. The woman didn't age well compared to him, he was a bit younger as well. Back in the day, she was quite the beautiful older sister, he met her on one of his travels. Zhang Jin had quite the silver tongue and managed to court favor with the woman. He also left without saying a word after having his fun. Thanks to his high standing and the two clans not really wanting any trouble with each other the whole thing was forgotten, but the old woman still held a grudge.

"Yes... but I heard you didn't learn much after that, how many poor women have you devoured. Well, I guess Patriarch wouldn't be here if you weren't like this..."

She already knew that Zhang Dong was someone from a side family, that came to be due to Zhang Jin's fooling around. The old lady wasn't letting up, Huo Qiao was to the side just scratching his neck not sure what to do with these two. He was slowly getting worried that the old woman would jump at the Zhang Clan senior and claw his eyes out or something. He coughed into his palm and tried to get their attention as he spoke up.

"Ahh... let's focus on the junior members and on the competition, its not the time for these personal squabbles, you two..."

The two looked to the man, he had the highest cultivation base here, and even though Zhang Jin had improved with the help of Zhang Dong. He was still nowhere near this senior in terms of power and strength.

"Ah yes... the competition, think we can all agree on a truce and to have our juniors work together."

Zhang Jin was quick to jump back to the conversation about the Dao Festival, not really wanting to talk about his love life.

"Well, that's obvious we can't let those idiots take the spots from our juniors, not sure what they are thinking. Guess they don't know how strong our clans have gotten since that time..."

The granny grumbled and also chimed in, during these two years the three clans had leveled up. This was all thanks to the share of cultivation resources.

"Mhm, who could have known that your Patriarch has such a useful skill! That would explain his behavior back in the library."

Huo Qiao thought back to that time two years ago and how Zhang Dong was rushing all over the place poking and touching books. He thought that he was just looking for something, but he was actually remembering them with some kind of bizarre technique. They found out later after he had sent some of the techniques from the library for their personal use.

There were various manuals handed over to them, for which the whole Huo clan was grateful. Their Patriarch was flabbergast and immediately formed an alliance with the Zhang Clan. The techniques that they received were by far the best ones that they had ever seen. They also went along with the Dao of the flames that they practiced. The same thing happened to the Feng Clan, though their Matriarch didn't really need them to form a similar alliance with the Zhang Clan. She already held Zhang Dong in high regard and would have done it if he just asked.

"Though your Patriarch has a peculiar naming sense."

Huo Qiao laughed.

"Oh, think the 'Triforce alliance' has a nice ring to it..."

Zhang Jin replied while also chuckling slightly. The scroll that they all signed that day also had a three triangle pattern. This was, of course, a symbol from a popular game that Matt had played back in the day.

"Well, I see that we all agree. I'll have some of my clan members pass the plan to the junior members, you should do the same."

Zhang Jin said while leaning forward slightly, but as he was about to stand up from his seat to excuse himself a person walked in from the side room. This person was quite the beautiful lady with light pink hair, the hair was styled in a ponytail. Some of that hair was still bouncing up from the front and slightly covering the woman's eyes.

"Grandpa Jin, grandpa Jin... why didn't Zhang Dong come... I wanted to show him how much I have progressed..."

This was Feng Liena, the woman hadn't aged a day and was still of a nice caramel complexion.

"Yeah, I wanted to spar with Brother too..."

A large muscular red-haired man walked out as well. This was Huo Qiang, Zhang Dong's self-proclaimed brother. He treated Zhang Dong as a senior brother, but he was actually older by about ten years.

The two looked dejected while looking at Zhang Jin, the old man not sure what to say as it was due to him that his grandson wasn't here. He was still adamant about letting him know about the whole Dao Festival, not wanting to bring him into the area where he could offend some Dark Palm sect members.

"Ah, Dong'er was in secluded cultivation so I didn't want to bother him with the small stuff... it's better if this old man takes care of the junior members from time to time, ho ho ho."

He laughed out loud while standing up and giving the two that walked in a bow with cupped fists.

"I'll be sure to mention you two when I see my grandson, he had been quite busy since we started reclaiming our old territory."

"If you say so..."

Feng Liena replied while trying not to pout. The woman was quite interested in this Zhang clan Patriarch that had offered her own family various cultivation manuals. But this wasn't all, she was quite fond of his rather unorthodox ways. He was quite the peculiar man that didn't really act as others acted. He was in a rather high position, but he seemed quite innocent on the inside.

'Haven't really seen him much since those two years, he is always away or cultivating...hope he isn't evading me on purpose...'

The woman's head dropped down. Matt didn't really visit any of his new friends all that much, still having his introvert ways of not trying to intrude on people without having to. If left alone without any responsibilities he would probably lock himself in his crafting abode. He didn't really have the urge to meet people, the responsibilities of being a Patriarch mostly being the ones that made him go out.

"Ahh... didn't he send you a new battle fan recently though?"

Feng Maling interrupted as she saw where her young Matriarch's thoughts were wondering. The new pinnacle earth weapon arrived just a couple of months ago.

"Ahh! Yes!"

Liena pulled out a fan, it was quite beautiful and looked like the tail of a peacock. It shined brightly and looked like it was made from green jade. This was a lot stronger than any weapon that she possessed, Matt managed to produce it with an advanced grade of A+. Making it something that was at the top of perfect graded earth weapons.

Feng Liena waved it around proudly while her grandma and Zhang Jin smiled, seeing that the lady was cheering up once more. But the happy mood didn't last long as Huo Qiang spoke up.

"Oh, he made one for you too? Look at these babies!"

The man pulled out a set of red gauntlets that looked as if they were made from red rubies. He struck a battle pose showing them off while Huo Qiao tried not to facepalm from the side.

'How can a man with so many wives have so little tact...'

The three elders in the room squinted at the red-haired man while Feng Liena's expression sunk once again.

Chapter 138

The elder members from the three clans dispersed after a small commotion. The Matriarch of the Feng clan almost got into a scuffle with the Huo clan young lord. Luckily the others managed to quell her anger, the man in question not really sure why the lady was mad at him. He even offered her the spot as his 100th wife again. Telling her that if things with Zhang Dong didn't work out, she could join his harem. This, of course, didn't go well ending in the Feng Matriarch trying to deliver a strike to the Huo lords nether regions.

While this was happening, down in the pagoda hotel the Zhang Clan juniors were getting ready for the last trial. After the 'misunderstanding ' was cleared up, their Grand Elder Zhang Jin went over to tell them about the plan and the alliance.

"So it's like this, young ones..."

Zhang Jin laid it bare, telling everyone to work with the Feng Clan and the Huo Clan if they came across them. He didn't beat around the bush too much as he didn't have the spare time. Still having important business to take care of later on.

"Remember, when the final trial opens you will be randomly spread out throughout the testing grounds. If you are lucky you will have your brothers and sisters with you, but if not. You might find yourself against multiple opponents."

"The Feng and Huo Clans have agreed to aid us, the other families will band against us so if you see anyone from our allies, aid them."

The trial area had a teleportation formation implemented in it. It would put the juniors at random locations in a maze-like area. There were many traps and even some of those dolls were waiting to give the contestants a trashing. This wasn't all though, in the area were hidden treasures like spiritual herbs. This was placed inside the area to give the participants some incentive to fight, the resources were limited and you could keep everything that you managed to find.

The short briefing ended and the juniors bowed, they weren't against working together with other clans. They weren't so sure if they could trust the other clans that well. They didn't know the other party well enough for that. The Feng women were strange and hard to approach, the Huo cultivators overbearing and haughty. Still, this was the order of the grand elder, so the juniors would try to follow it as well as they could.

"Liu'er, Xue'er join your grandpa for a talk..."

Before Zhang Jin left the juniors, he made sure to get his grandson and grandaughter for a little talk. The two just looked at each other and nodded, not really thinking much off it. They all gathered in a separate room that was prepared for the highest-ranking member from their clan. It looked quite nice, but compared to the penthouse one it looked quite shabby.

"Sit down, have some tea."

They got offered some snacks and tea, their grandpa just trying to create a nice enough atmosphere. What he would say would probably not fly well with these two youngsters that had progressed at an amazing pace. But he had to at least try to convince them to see things his way, if not he would have to go with plan B.

"Liu...Xue... it would be wise if you dropped out of the competition after the next trial..."

Zhang Liu coughed out as he was sipping on the tea, his sister had a similar reaction as she choked on a cookie that she was nibbling on. The two were quite shocked not understanding the meaning of their grandpa's words, why would he want them to drop out now.

"Grandpa Jin, what is the meaning of this? How can we show the other clan's our superiority if we don't participate?"

Zhang Liu slammed his palms down on the table in protest, the table rattling due to the force. His sister covered her mouth with the sleeve of her robe as she didn't want to show the crumbs on her mouth while also replying.

"Yes dear grandpa, I would like to hear an explanation too...how could we, as the Patriarch's disciples do such a thing?"

The old man looked at the two youths, the two looked a lot different now than they did two years ago. They looked a lot more mature, those white locks only added to their mystical appearance. He didn't think it would be possible for anyone below the age of twenty to be at their power level. That Master of theirs really did bring in all the best techniques to the table and in that lay the problem.

"Now calm down you two, let your grandpa explain... the thing is..."

"You might bring unwanted attention to your Master and the clan if you continue like this..."

The two twitched slightly as they heard their Master getting mentioned, Zhang Liu sat back down after he stood up to smack the table and continued to listen.

"You might think that spreading the glory of the clan is a good thing, but in reality, it might bring it to ruin if we aren't careful..."

"Your master is a powerful man, but he isn't strong enough to shoulder this burden... not yet at least."

"I have seen his cultivation manual... I've seen yours and it's far more immeasurable than you might think. If the powerful sects realize what we are holding and it's true worth, we might face annihilation..."

The two youths gasped in shock, not really sure if their grandpa was serious or if he was being a bit too melodramatic. Would the sects really attack if they found their Master's cultivation method to be of a high quality?

"So that's why grandfather stopped me back then..."

Liu said while moving his head down and thinking.

"You could have easily attained first place, but you would have attracted a lot of unwanted attention."

"Still... I don't agree! It would be shameful to not fight at our best!"

Liu retorted, not wanting to throw a fight as his pride didn't allow him. Xue was also of the same mind, thinking their grandfather was over exaggerating. Though she also understood where her family member was coming from, but if they hid some of that strength things should work out.

"Well, I'm not telling you two to lie down and take it, at least try not to use the more powerful techniques like the Embodiment of the Thunder God. But your grandpa would be glad if you thought about what is good for the clan... Luckily the inside of the trial is sealed off so no one will be able to see you fight. But after the main tournament starts all eyes will be on you."

What continued was an attempt of the old man on getting the two youths to see it from his standpoint. Bringing honor to your clan or yourself was fine and all, but it wasn't worth your life. The two weren't all that convinced, from their experience things seemed to work out in the end but they would take their grandpa's words into consideration.

"So, you're not convinced... well at least try to not stand out, your opponents shouldn't be strong enough for you to go all out..."

The man gave off a large sigh, he could force the two to drop out but he also wanted them to make their own mistakes. The probability of something going wrong wasn't all that high, there were only a couple of people that could contend with his young grandson at an equal level. One of them was even from their own clan, the other was the Huo clan young master. It should be fine if Zhang Liu doesn't use the more overpowering techniques that gave off that strong lightning Dao.

He also tried making Zhang Xue wear a veil or something to cover her face, his men were telling him that the girl was garnering quite the following due to her looks.

'I will probably be receiving a lot of marriage requests if this continued, but now like that's a bad thing...'

Forming bonds with other clans was something positive, but from this elder's standpoint not a lot of clans could actually bring much to the table. Their Patriarch was already a cultivation technique encyclopedia, the only thing they really lacked were more materialistic resources, like spirit stones or spirit herbs.

'It would be nice if she fancied someone rich, but she doesn't look that interested in the young men around her...'

"Well, you two should think it through... don't worry if something happens, your grandpa will save you!"

The two youths looked at each other and chuckled a bit, Zhang Xue being the one to reply this time around.

"Ara? I only thought that grandpa saved fair maidens from other clans~"

Zhang Jin got taken aback by the retort, his womanizing ways having reached even his two grandchildren.

"Don't make fun of your grandpa, you two rascals!"

The three family members chatted for a bit more before parting ways, the two youths returned to their quarters while contemplating about their grandfather's words. They knew where he was coming from, but even then they didn't feel like they should give up and throw the fights. Why did they have to stain their honor by acting in this way, this would bring a loss to their Master's face if they lost a battle that they could have easily won.

Zhang Jin was left in the room alone, contemplating on what he should do.

'Should I force them to forfeit... no, that could impend their progress later on and leave some demons in their hearts. They cherish their master too much and won't allow a loss to his face by quitting...'

The old man looked into his spatial ring and pulled out a magical treasure, that looked like some kind of shield-shaped talisman.

'Might have to use this if trouble arises, hope that there won't be a need for it though. The probability of things going badly is low.'

The man huffed and looked out into the scenery, the window from his room letting him see the well-lit city in the night. His face going more solemn as a certain person entered his room.

"Are you ready?"

The man asked while Zhang Jin nodded, his eyes sharp as he rose from his seat to head out.

"Who do you think I am youngster? I was born ready!"

He replied with vigor while the other person rubbed his palms together.

"Good... let us venture forth into the unknown!"

The two men looked at each other, their expressions resolute as they headed out of the room and then out of the pagoda hotel.

................

"Now this is what I call, a secret ground!"

Zhang Jin proclaimed while holding a small bottle of alcohol in his hand and taking a sip out of it.

"See, I told you that I know where the good stuff is,Senior Jin!"

Next to him was Huo Qiang, his muscular arm wrapped around a thin waist of a serving girl that looked like she was enjoying herself.

"He he he, senior brother where are you touching me~"

The young woman replied in a coquettish tone, not really moving from the spot she was sitting on as she let the young master from the Huo clan have his way.

The two hornballs had decided to check out what the red light district had to offer in this jade city. The two were prominent members of their clans so they had a lot of gold and spirit stones saved up for occasions like this.

"Let the young generation have their fun at the tournament, while we of the older generation face these ferocious foes!"

Said Zhang Jin while plopping his head between a rather busty girl's bosom, his face was all red from drinking too much alcohol already.

............

On the next day, everyone from the three clans that were in the triforce alliance gathered together. The elders wanted the younger members to at least be able to recognize their allies before they headed to that closed of trial. The tension was in the air and everyone was ready to do battle, the juniors were taking everything very seriously. Unbeknownst to them, the Zhang grand elder and future Patriarch of the Huo clan were deep asleep. Having fought a ferocious battle throughout the night, tired and bruised.

Chapter 139

While Zhang Jin was trying to soothe his hangover, the youths and some other clan elders were gathering at the last trial area. There would be close to five hundred participants. The entrance to the last trial was in a large building, the large doors had a phoenix and a dragon pattern on it, the two beasts seemed to be entangled in battle. The large door was still closed as it was an hour before the competition, the people would use this time to make their battle plan.

The three families that would be working together gathered at one spot. Everyone had characteristic robes, the Zhang clan members had blue ones, the Huo clan had red ones and the Feng clan girls were mostly in green. Though the women that looked as if they stayed in the sun for too long, were hard to miss. So the other two clans wouldn't really have a problem with discerning them from the other practitioners that were participating.

First came the supporting elders that exchanged greetings, the group of Juniors was facing each other in a triangle, curious gazes coming from all directions. The Feng girls started whispering with each other while sneaking in glances at the boys from the two other clans. In response the youths gulped, the young ladies had strange expressions on their faces as if they wanted to gobble them all up. First to speak out was a Huo clan elder, that people weren't particularly familiar with.

"Listen up, remember each other's faces, if you find your brothers and sisters in distress help them out."

"The other sects and clans will be working against our group, so don't forget to work together and after passing the trial you will be able to test yourselves against each other!"

The elder was an experienced person and knew how youths like these thought. Their competitive spirit would surely soar in a situation like this. He wanted these kids to at least work together in this trial, letting their ambitions dormant for the time being. Some of them might already be antagonistic against each other. Closed of trials like this brought out the beast in some of the cultivators, as it was the perfect chance to let old grudges unfold.

"Don't be arrogant enough to think that you are strong enough to succeed on your own... just look..."

The man pointed to the other participants in the area. There was one thing that stuck out, just like them they were gathering in groups. Some bigger than the other, one being at least twice the size than their own. This looked like the main enemy camp, the youths there were already giving them the stink eye.

"I guess they are taking us very seriously..."

Zhang Liu chimed in while standing next to his sister, his senior brother that fancied his sister was also there probably being there due to that.

"Well, we probably gave them quite the scare during the other tests."

Zhang Xue chuckled while smiling at her brother, the Zhang family members not that worried as they took this in a positive way. From their perspective, the other clans and smaller sects saw them as a powerful enemy. Was there anything better than being seen as a power to be feared in this world?

"Do we really need the help from these other clans, think our Zhang Clan can manage on its own!"

Zhang Tai voiced his opinion from the side while looking at the cultivators from the other clans. Not really convinced that he or his clan members that were quite strong needed to team up with other people.

"The more allies we have the better senior Brother Tai. Also, these two families have close ties to our Patriarch, so it would be rude to deny them help."

Zhang Xue replied while moving, the moment Tai heard the Patriarch get mentioned he quieted down. He recalled that their Patriarch had some dealings with the Feng Matriarch and the man that was next in line for the Patriarch position in the Huo clan. It would be disastrous if the juniors went against plans that their elders had, for various reasons.

"Is that so..."

Tai said while looking at Zhang Xue that was slowly walking towards the Feng Clan side. None of the three factions had yet mingled with each other, even after their elders stopped talking.

"Greetings from the Zhang Clan fellow sisters."

Zhang Xue smiled at the dark-skinned ladies. The girls looked at each other and moved forward, the girl that approached them looked to be quite the beauty. Some of the gyarus moved forward, they looked friendly enough. Before they could reply though, a tiny blur rapidly squeezed from within the group and arrived right opposite Zhang Xue.

"Who do we have here?"

The person that came out made the other Feng women move to the side, it being their elder sister. Zhang Liu blinked rapidly as he recognized the short girl that took him for a tour of the city. Though he was mostly used as a serving boy that carried her clothes for the whole day.

"Ah, greetings little sister, Zhang Xue sends her greetings!"

Xue tried to be civil in her reply, but she was getting strange vibes from this small girl.

"Little sister?... who you calling little, you pipsqueak!"

The small girl puffed out her cheeks and stood up straight, her voluptuous chest pointing forward as if she was presenting it against Xue's. The two girls started staring at each other, one was hostile while the other was bewildered not knowing where the animosity was coming from.

"E-excuse me, senior sister?"

The small girl crossed her hands over one another and nodded, she looked satisfied after getting called a senior sister.

"That's better!"

While this was transpiring the other youths started with curiosity, Zhang Liu moved over to his sister as he tried to pull her away, knowing well that this pink-haired midget was a strange one.

"Xue... I think we should..."

Before he could finish the sentence the small girl pointed her finger at him while shouting out. She then rapidly pointed it at Xue and then back to Liu again.

"You two, what's your relationship!

The siblings looked at each other before eyeing the strange girl again.

"Liu is my older brother..."

Zhang Xue replies, getting the strange suspicion that this small girl was interested in her brother. The girl in question dropped her pointing finger, it looked like she was thinking about something. But just as soon as the finger was dropped, it was put up once again and pointed at the Zhang clan young lady.

"E-enemy!"

The small girl proclaimed, her eyes moving into tiny slits as she glared at Zhang Xue that took one step back.

"E-excuse me?"

"Younger sisters are always the enemy!"

Feng Nuana glared more as her eyes went up and then down. The smaller girl analyzed the looks of this so-called new enemy, not liking that striking appearance at all.

"Such a ferocious foe... but mark my words, I'll never surrender! You will be a fitting rival for this senior sister!"

While the small girl was shouting out, the other junior members from the group moved closer. The other Feng clan ladies moved in and bowed in an apologetic fashion as they tried to diffuse the situation.

"Oh ho ho, senior sister is really energetic... don't mind her..."

"Yes yes, she is just glad that so many handsome brothers and beautiful sisters had gathered together..."

"Yes, you there little brother, do you want to have a chat with this big sister?"

One of the Feng ladies took the chance to move next to one of the Zhang clan men that were to the side and just looking. The man looked at the dark-skinned 'big sis', her looks were quite exotic but she had a certain charm to her. Soon, the young women from the wind tribe were mingling with the other clans, even pulling the Huo clan into the mix.

Zhang Xue moved back feeling like it would be better to not get associated with the angry-looking little girl. Her brother moved in front to shield her, Feng Nuana seeming in a better mood after her so-called enemy started backing away.

"Did something happen between you and my sister..."

Liu asked wondering what this was all about, the girl in question just smirked and moved closer. She looked up to him with a smile on her face and before the youth could react, she wrapped her hands around his. The youth jumped slightly as he felt something soft pressing into his arm.

"Hey, what are you doing? Let go!"

"No!"

He was quickly shut down while the small girl rubbed her bosom into his arm, the inexperienced youth going red in the face instantly after getting assaulted by the Feng girl. The girl in question smirked and made sure to eye Zhang Xue that was backing away, her nose moving upwards as if she was looking at a bug.

'What's that strange girl doing with big brother... does she really fancy him?'

She thought to herself while backing away, but when she did that she bumped into some.

"Hey, who dares!"

She bumped into this person's back without realizing as she was preoccupied. The voice was quite manly and the back that she bumped into was quite wide, so the person behind her had to have a large physique. After turning around her eyes met with a set of red hues that looked like small embers. The youth's face contorted, his frown turned into a gaping mouth as he started.

"Ah, excuse me, I wasn't paying attention."

The girl made a little bow in front of the youth, not wanting to seem rude. She was afraid that this could turn to something more as the man in front of her sounded quite annoyed. But instead of that, the man continued to stare for a second or two before snapping back a hand moving to his head as he scratched it.

"Ahhh... don't mind... everyone makes mistakes..."

The man tossed his head back and started laughing out loud, Xue remembered him from the first test as he had scored the same number of chimes as she did.

This was, of course, Huo Kong that was panicking on the inside. This was the first time he had seen such a beautiful girl in his life, none of the women in his clan or the fiances that his clan tried pushing on him compared to this young maiden.

"N-nice weather we are having today? Haha..."

'What do I do!'

He thought while panicking, he was a person focused on personal might and had no knowledge or experience in talking to girls. Luckily the response that he got was a cute sounding laugh, followed by the girl's lovely voice.

"Yes, it's quite nice. Brother is from the Huo clan?"

Huo Kong nodded quickly replying to the question.

"Yes! I am Huo Kong the fiercest from our clan!"

"Ara? The fiercest? Quite the title you got there."

The girl laughed some more, thinking that this older brother was quite funny. This was mostly due to how the youth looked, on the outside he seemed to be a seasoned warrior with a large physique. But there he was panicking as if Xue was someone to be feared. The girl kind of knew why he was acting like this, attributing it to him being inexperienced with girls.

Suddenly everyone was mingling with each other. Zhang Tai got surrounded by quite a lot of people, being the person with the best score on the first test. He also scored quite well on the other ones and was well known by now. Quite a few Feng maidens were trying to chat it up with him, but some from the Huo clan were there too.

Zhang Liu was trying to wrestle away from the busty midget but wasn't having any luck as the girl was surprisingly strong. For some reason, she had it in for him and the youth wasn't sure why. Time passed and soon the doors from the last trial were opened, a couple of older looking people walked out that belonged to the testing crew.

Everyone was guided inside, the last test would be starting soon it would probably take a couple of days till it finished.

Chapter 140

The five hundred or so people were led to a large hall where they stood and waited. Everyone was keeping to themselves in the previously created groups, only a couple of people could be seen alone without any factions backing them up. This hall was mostly empty with torches lined up on the walls that shone brightly.

The trial participants had walked down into the unknown for quite some time before arriving here. The place they were led to was apparently deep underground under the city. The hall was quite immense and the ceiling was at least twenty meters tall. There were large square pillars holding it up with bright-lit torches that seemed to be burning without the need for oil.

There were several men standing on the other end of this hall, they wore a familiar set of robes that these junior participants were already familiar with as they belonged to the people responsible for the testing process. Everyone looked to them as it was time for the last test to start, a lot of the youths feeling those butterflies in their stomachs.

"Welcome, you have managed to best your peers but now the real trial begins!"

There was something like a large gate close to where the testing personnel was standing at. The strange thing about this gate was that it wasn't leading anywhere. There were wide stairs leading up to it but nothing behind it, not a tunnel or anything of the sort. The youths looked at each other while the people that worked for the dark palm sect chuckled on the inside, laughing at these backwater cultivator's lack of knowledge.

Suddenly the large circular shaped gate that was embedded into the wall started vibrating. Everyone could feel massive spiritual energy radiation coming off of it. Some Chinese symbols started appearing on the rocky surface of that gate, a burst of energy making the whole thing light up in one go. Suddenly something that looked like water exploded forward startling the young contestants.

"W-what is that..."

"It looks like a pond of water but on the wall..."

This was what some people called a 'portal' it was shining with deep blue light, the surface looked like a pound which was waving around. While the young people were gazing at the strange phenomenon the people in the room spoke out.

"This is what we call a transfer gate, you will walk through this treasure and be placed inside the last trial ground. As you might have heard, the place you will be transported to will be unknown, if you're lucky you might even appear near a treasure!"

The youths looked at the strange-looking treasure that looked like a teleportation gate. It looked a lot different than the teleportation array that was located in the secret ground. The senior member picked up a rock for a presentation and threw it inside the watery like surface. The item that was thrown vanish inside and the surface just rippled like it was made from water.

"As you can see, you just need to go through it, so don't be afraid."

The man laughed a bit after seeing how these young cultivators reacted, most of them never having seen a teleportation treasure like this. Something like this was a well-kept secret among powerful clans, being able to teleport was a big advantage if it came to battle. Mostly due to logistics, you could easily transport resources to your warriors and army without having to leave your well-protected fortress. You didn't need to worry about enemy attacks hitting your transport line either.

This wasn't something widely spread though, even this place only allowed people to teleport within the trial grounds and at a random fashion to boot. The dark palm sect possessed the knowledge to build teleportation gates like this, but there were very few of them around as they just used up way too many resources. This one was only valid for the trial period as it couldn't be used for long-range teleportation between cities. The sect only had the teleportation treasures situated in their core cities and strongholds.

"Please proceed to the gate in an orderly fashion, but don't go in, all at once."

A line was formed and the youths started vanishing while the teleportation gate rippled as if something splashed inside of it. In time everyone found themselves alone in various sections of the large trial ground, it consisted mostly of wide corridors with faint light but some were pitch dark. The less fortunate people ended up in the middle of traps or around automated dolls that started chasing them the moment they got a glimpse of the enemy.

One of those unlucky people was the Zhang Clan prodigy, Zhang Tai. At first, he thought he hit the jackpot, ending up close to some spiritual herbs that were just growing to the side. The herb that he spotted was giving off some strong spiritual energies and had a nice mint smell to it. Was this the fabled seven-star sage? he thought before moving up to it, hoping to pocket it with him. Spatial rings were forbidden in this area, the cultivators could only bring as much as they could carry with them.

But just as he was about to pluck the herb from the ground, he noticed something staring at him. After he pushed some spiritual energy into his eyes to get a better look he saw quite the army of wooden dolls. They weren't the humanoid looking ones that were at the corridor though. Those didn't have sickles for arms and swords for legs, these here were clearly enhanced to kill. He quickly grabbed the herb and bolted away, not really keen on finding out if he was able to handle these automatons on his own. The moment he snatched the treasure though, the group of battle puppets chased after him.

Zhang Liu, on the other hand, was dropped off in an unsuspecting corridor with nothing in particular around him. After traveling for some minutes, hoping to find something he noticed some strange fluctuations right above him. Before he could react to the strange phenomenon he saw a large posterior right in front of his face. Bewildered by the display he didn't react in time and got hit by it and tumbled to the ground. He started wiggling around and could hear the person on top of him gasp, with a rather cute voice.

The person on top of him quickly jumped off his face, he groaned as he felt a foot hitting his stomach as the female to who the posterior belonged to jumped away. He gasped yet again, the moment he saw who the person was that landed on him.

"Mmmmm...pervert!..."

This was the small Feng Nuana, that was blushing slightly while holding her short skirt from her robe down. She had apparently been teleported in the same place that Zhang Liu did, as her clan was the one next in line right after the Zhang clan.

This place was quite large as it covered the underground area under the whole city that housed millions of people in it. There were many corridors and the chances off meeting at the start were slim. The whole test had a time limit of a week, so the contestants had the incentive to find others and strip them of their tokens. After this, they could either wait out the whole extent of the trial or try to find one of the exit teleportation gates that were scattered around the large maze-like area. But you wouldn't find more than a handful of those, so waiting it out was quite a valid strategy.

The test finally started, the young adults inside started looking for their allies and enemies alike. They all had some baggage in the form of food and weapons with them. This would be a true test of their survival skills. While everything was unfolding a certain white-haired man was sitting with his legs crossed, staring at a scroll.

"Well... think I got all that I need now... let me just got through this one last time..."

This was, of course, the glorious Zhang Clan Patriarch, Zhang Dong. He had written down the whole cultivation process on the paper, with pointers on how to go through into the Nascent soul. He had managed to fashion a small formation to help him with controlling the spiritual energy in his own body. He also produced a helpful pill that would boost his vitality and concentration during the task. There wasn't really more that he could do, being already a step through the door he just needed to take the next one further in.

"Okay, this is it... time to become one with the world and one with myself..."

This would be quite the quality change for him as he would be gaining something called a nascent soul. This would fully awaken something called the Spiritual Sense. At first, he thought this was something similar to the aura detection technique that he used before, but it wasn't quite that. If he understood it correctly, it would push him towards being one with himself and one with the world around him. Making him able to sense other energies and truths that the world of cultivation had to offer, and not just other cultivators.

"Here goes nothing... wonder what gramps will say when he finds out..."

He chuckled to himself, he knew that no one expected him to reach this level so soon. If he succeeded he would be the youngest Nascent soul practitioner in the world. From what he knew, the world record wasn't even under the hundred-year mark. People at the great circle of core formation would prepare for years before attempting a breakthrough.

'Guess maxing out your cultivation level wasn't all that easy... But I guess the techniques they use are also faulty and have more restrictions than mine.'

He smacked both his cheeks with his palms to pump himself up and sat down in a traditional lotus position. Golden lightning crackled around him and his body started radiating a massive amount of spiritual energy. The space around him warped and he slowly started floating off the ground.

The lightning that was coming of his body collided with the ground, some strange patterns emerging from under his floating form. The area shined brightly as the electricity was absorbed and then redistributed back into the man floating above. This was the formation that was working to help with Matt's spiritual energy usage, pushing it back into him so that not much of it was wasted on the surroundings.

His cultivation was fully utilized as he felt his power rising and rising. He could feel his golden lightning core shaking as it got bathed in his divine lightning energies. His foundation pillars also reacted, humming together as they resonated with his cultivation core that began expanding in size. His core took in his divine lightning energies while his whole body surged with power.

Matt could feel his body changing, his core got bigger and bigger and he knew that the moment it shattered it would unearth a soul underneath. He wasn't hasty though, making sure to follow his battle plan and slowly perform this procedure like a surgeon doing and operation. The time for action came soon enough, the man opened up his eyes which were noting more than golden saucers filled with lightning energy.

"Now... shatter!"

He tossed his head upwards and shouted out, the last surge of Qi ventured forth through his meridians and invaded his core shattering it into pieces in one go. The process wasn't painful but it wasn't anything enjoyable either as sweat run down his forehead. He could suddenly feel it, there was something deep inside of him. He tried looking at the thing that was now there, the 'soul' that was formed looked at him back and he felt like he was looking at himself from withing.

"So... this is my nascent soul..."

The soul looked like a tiny person, a small version of himself. The odd thing about the tiny person living inside of him was, that he wasn't one hundred percent similar to his current appearance. From what Matt could tell, the soul living inside of him had features that he possessed in his old life, like his eye color. It was as if his old persona had mixed with his current one to form this strange-looking nascent soul. Still, he had broken through, power was surging through his entire body, power like he had never felt before.

He grasped his hand, the surrounding space contorted to his might as his golden lightning energies burst forth. Massive winds were produced by this simple hand gesture that didn't really have his full force behind it. He was feeling rather peculiar, he could feel it... he could feel everything around him, it was as if he was one with the world.

Chapter 141

The whole small floating island rumbled due to the energies that were emanated, the source being a floating Zhang Dong who had his eyes closed. He was moving further up into the air going out of the range of his formation. The golden arcs of lightning energies started flying in all directions, scorching the ground underneath.

The man was too occupied with his ascension to the higher realm, not knowing that he was destroying the spirit herb fields that were painstakingly planted by his fellow clan members. Though a strange phenomenon took place. After the herbs turned to ash, new ones started sprouting as if the roots absorbed the divine lightning energies. This allowed them to regrow themselves with an added boon.

Matt had just reached this realm and he was still in the process of reinforcing his cultivation. Just as expected the immortal grade dimensional regalia treasure contained all of his energies as the people outside the pocket dimension had no clue that their Patriarch reached a new height. If they knew what was happening, they would probably pass out from excitement.

He stopped looking inside of his body, moving his attention to the world around him. He could feel the plants, it was as if they were breathing. His senses all got enhanced, he felt that he could hear a water drop fall from many kilometers away if he really concentrated. He was now floating up in the air, without the need of his sword or the aid of his technique just sitting with his legs crossed.

"Huh... well... that was neat..."

He rubbed his head, not really sure what to say or think. He looked at the charred earth below him and the strange golden herbs that were growing here and there.

"I'll have to take a look at those...but first..."

He stood up while floating in the air, he was now in the higher realm the fabled Nascent Soul was in his grasp. There was one thing that he needed to do first though and this was the perfect place to do it. He looked side to side, making sure that no one was watching. After making sure that he was alone, he stuck out his hands right above his head. It looked as if he was trying to do an overhead press with his hands stretched out.

Then he closed his fists together and flew upwards, yes he was just testing out his new flying technique. He zoomed up high and then right down both his hands in front of him while the wind pressure made his hair shake about. This soon subsided as a golden aura surrounded his body, shielding him from the wind pressure.

"Weeeeeeeeeee........."

He was just like a little kid now, it was as if one of his childhood dreams had just come true. It was one thing to fly on a sword that was more of a stationary platform, and it was another to do it on your own without outside help. He rocketed around the small floating island, he couldn't really utilize his new flight as the area that he could fly around was small. If he tried going into the void he would quickly feel the lack of air and the drop in spiritual energies.

He tried various positions, the first one was just the default one that was probably the most popular one. The next one he tried was with one of his arms stretched out and with the other arm bent backward. He then tried bending one of his legs during that position, then he tried holding out his hands to the sides with his palms outstretched. He even tried flying with his feet in the forward position and then while standing out straight with his hands behind his back in his serious senior pose position.

He finally decided that he had enough and landed on the ground, this wasn't any old landing though. No this was the fabled superhero landing, his palm smashed into the ground producing a thumping sound and cracking the earth under him. Both his legs bent as if he was doing some type of crawl, a blush appearing on his face after he did it.

"Well... that was equally epic and equally silly... also I think if I wasn't so sturdy I could have broken something."

This type of landing was quite cool to look at, but it seemed quite dangerous, he hoped none of his clan juniors would try to imitate it if they saw him do it. He stood up and dusted his white robe off, he had a new one at this time. It was different in the way that it had armor integrated into it.

It was a new design that went more for functionality than looks. He ditched the flowy robe parts, trying not to imitate the popular robes in this world. To this day he didn't understand how those people could fight with those wide sleeves and robes that were longer than their own legs.

This was something added to his first robe, it had two modes now. The first one was just his regular white robe, while the other one made him look like a lightly armored knight of sorts. It left him a lot of wiggle room with his legs but kept his torso well protected. He didn't want it to be too bulky, otherwise, they would impede his movements during combat. He turned the second mode on while he was going past his realm, as it offered some nice bonuses to his stats like more energy and more resilience.

He turned off his battle mode and went over to one of the spiritual herbs, analyzing it to see what was the deal with it. He got its name which was 'Radiant Spiritual Sage', which was a rare variation of the Sage herb that his clan was cultivating for pill making.

"Hm, this... I should test it with some pills and see what it does if I exchange the regular ones..."

He looked at the destroyed herb fields, not many of those 'radiant' variants were there, most of the old greenery was just destroyed in the process. Maybe if he did some research he would be able to copy this creating process of this rare herb variant. He pocketed the herbs and then thought back to his flying experience, still not sure about the best pose.

"How do those other Nascent Soul guys fly around, haven't really seen any besides that one guy by the secret ground and he only floated a bit with his hands behind his back...."

He rubbed his chin and contemplated the best pose to take, he couldn't make a fool out of himself. Thinking that his regular hands behind back pose was good for slow floating, it looked the most honorable and menacing at the same time.

"Well, I guess I could fly with my hands behind my back while looking stoic... but that will be probably a bit uncomfortable in the long run."

After having his fun with his new flying skill, that was several times faster than his old sword flight. He decided to see how much his power increased. He took out a pinnacle graded earth treasure that looked like a large tower shield. This thing was made with defense in mind so it would act as a good test item.

He propped it up against a log that he inserted into the ground close to the edge of the pocket dimension. He then walked back a couple of steps so he was standing about ten meters away from the tower shield. He then clenched his fist tightly and took on a fighting stance.

"Okay, let's see..."

He pushed some of his spiritual energy into his fist and cocked it back, quickly punching forward. His punch produced immense wind pressure along with golden lightning energies, the sound of thunder reverberating throughout the area. He thought that he would probably put a dent in the shield, as it was quite a crafty. Instead, he watched on in surprise as the thing broke into small pieces along with the area around it, exploding in the process.

He whistled and looked at the big chunk of earth missing, thanks to standing next to the edge of the pocket dimension not much of the area was destroyed but he could see some of the shield chunks floating in the distance of the void.

"This will take some time to get used to..."

He fired off a couple of more ranged attacks, the lightning dragon that he could create now was several times larger than what he was able to produce previously. Same thing with his avatar form that made him at least as tall as a popular kaiju from the movies. He felt full of vigor and power. If he faced the demon from that secret ground this time around he could probably defeat him with one well-placed hit.

He was still fresh and had to reinforce his cultivation level, it was a miracle that he was actually able to do everything according to plan. No one was attacking the city or knew that he pushed himself into the new realm. Everything seemed to be working out.

"Okay, let me work on some of those heaven grade techniques a bit, then I'll craft that heaven graded weapon and get my body refining up... think a dagger should be fine and don't really have the resources for anything big..."

Getting to the nascent soul level was one thing, being both a body refiner and a Qi cultivator at that level was another one. He felt like he would be undefeatable if he got both of them up to at least the late-stage. He wasn't sure how long that would take, but with his increased life spawn now he had a lot of time on his hands.

"No need to rush things, I got all the time in the world. As long as we stay hidden that Dark Palm sect shouldn't notice anything and it will be too late for them after I get stronger. If I manage to help Liena and Qiang to reach this realm, even if that sect finds out, we should be able to defend ourselves."

"Well, time to get to work, this is going to take a while..."

He had many things to do, upgrading his techniques was one thing. Crafting a new set of weapons and treasures was another thing. He was even planning to use some black market connections in some more shady areas to get more nascent soul level resources later. He could always change his appearance and no one would actually believe that he was thirty-two. Only old monsters above the age of hundred were in the nascent soul. It shouldn't be traced back to him, even if someone noticed something off with his disguise.

While Zhang Dong vanished into his crafting abode the last trial back in Jade Grass City was in full swing. There was a lot of fighting happening among the junior members as quite a lot of them had gathered into large groups. The larger camp that was created by the more powerful clans was the one on top, managing to sweep past the more unorganized factions.

The Triforce Alliance wasn't far behind, but some of their members had already fallen in the process of trying to gather together with their allies. Not everyone was with the main group though, the trial ground was way too large for them to find each other in just a couple of days of time. The people also had to fend for themselves against the other contestants. There was no magic teleportation formation that brought people out if they were critically injured, so deaths could happen.

At this time Zhang Liu and Zhang Tai along with a couple other clan members from the other two factions were chatting.

"Still no word?"

"No, brother Kong and sister Xue still haven't been spotted... we were separated from them during a fight..."

One of the Zhang Clan youths replied while talking to his clan brother, one of their main powerhouses in the form of Hou Kong was missing and Zhang Xue that wasn't a slouch wasn't there either. This was troubling as they didn't think that the two could take on that large clan alliance on their own.

"Okay, let's move out... let us form two large teams and let's search the area for more of our brothers and sisters. If you find anyone, be sure to alert the other people from our alliance."

Zhang Liu and Tai were the two defacto leaders, they tried to mix the teams up in a similar fashion to the platoons that they were in at the secret ground. Some fighters along with ranged support and healers, Feng Nuana was sure to stick to Liu like glue so they headed in a different direction than Zhang Tai did, the older brother concerned about his sister that was probably alone.

'Don't worry Xue, big brother is coming.'

Chapter 142

"Hold still..."

A female voice could be heard accompanied by some groaning.

"Ugh...t-that feels strange"

The man groaned out while panting.

"Quite the cute sound there, for such a strong senior brother~"

The woman chuckled while some rustling could be heard.

"Hey, stop teasing... I'm trying my best here..."

The man replied in a shaky voice.

"Don't worry senior brother, I'll be as gentle as I can... just stay still for a moment...but you sure are quite large down here..."

The cute female voice proclaimed while more rustling was heard.

These two people were Zhang Xue and Huo Kong. The girl in question had her hands outstretched and a sphere of water was surrounding the man's abdomen. The youth had a sword wound on the side of his stomach that was slowly getting closed down thanks to Zhang Xue's healing arts. She couldn't use the holy element as her master, so she had to use the water arts from her clan. They weren't bad either, they just worked in a different fashion.

"Yes, those are quite the nice abdominal muscles there, you must have worked on them diligently."

The girl was apparently impressed by the man's physique. The girl was around muscular men, in the form of her own master and her big brother, that due to his body refining was turning into quite the beefcake himself. So she was now quite fond of the wider types, finding the manly ones superior to the more feminine dandy looking ones.

"I'm just glad that we got away from that group, we were lucky that those things started chasing after them instead of us."

The two ran into each other a day after the trial started, they formed a team but soon were discovered by a large troop that was gunning for their tokens. They were lucky enough to run through an area with a hidden treasure. It looked to be a sword surrounded by circular rocks, but when the people that were chasing after them tried touching it the rocks started shaking about.

They turned out to be humanoid looking golems, at least three meters tall and with heavy hammer-like fists. While the large band of monsters was trying to protect the weapon, Zhang Xue and Huo Kong made a run for it. Some of the enemies were indisposed so they decided to force their way through one side, the young man taking some hits as he pushed through the other participants that were blocking their way. He ended up injuring himself, getting a couple of cuts here and there but nothing that Zhang Xue couldn't heal.

"I'm feeling a lot better now, my thanks junior sister Xue."

The young man smiled awkwardly while looking at the white-haired beauty. He was quite enamored by the young girl's beauty and even more after he continued interacting with her. She wasn't haughty like some women with this type of beauty, she didn't seem too impressed in him being from a powerful clan either. She felt genuine and just all-around friendly, he didn't feel like she had an ulterior motive like some of the women that were after the prestige that his clan had going for it.

"No problem senior brother Kong, the elders told us to work together and I think they were right in doing so. There are really a lot of enemies in this trial."

Zhang Xue stood up after healing the red-haired man. She thought he was quite funny as he was always trying to evade her gaze and was blushing furiously whenever she touched him. He felt like a little puppy for some reason, she was used to getting stared at by the opposite gender. The gazes were quite different, mostly ones of attraction or possession.

It made her feel like the men saw her as some kind of trophy and not like a real person. This man, on the other hand, seemed too pure to even put her in that bracket. Which was quite funny from her point of view, the man's demeanor didn't fit his fiery appearance. He was quite the beast while fighting, she already saw that but the moment the two were alone he looked like a scared kitten.

"Senior brother, I don't think we should remain in this spot for too long. I bet those other people will try catching us again, we have to find out clan members there are too many of them for us to handle on our own."

Zhang Xue proclaimed while looking to the corridor that they came from, there were two other paths they could take. Xue could use her Master's detection technique, so she could somewhat spot people at the distance. But it wasn't as if this place was laced with traps and high levels of danger, like in the secret ground they were in. So she couldn't pick the right path, as well as the elder members, did back then.

"Um... think we should go with the left one..."

Zhang Xue said while focusing her senses on the two paths, the right one looked to be more dangerous.

"Yes junior sister, we should move... but don't worry, I'll protect you with my life if anything bad happens!"

The man proclaimed while smacking his chest with his palm. Xue just chuckled into her robe sleeve and nodded.

"Well, that's quite reassuring, senior brother Kong."

The man just smiled awkwardly at the girl and moved in front of her, he would be the vanguard as he was better in close range combat than the girl. The two had spent some time together, and this junior sister was quite the talented spear user. She even had some powerful range spear attack that could wreak havoc from the backlines.

The two both already had two tokens each as they had battled some other participants here and there. Most of their time was spent on running away though, the two knew that they couldn't really battle twenty cultivators at once. While the two moved through the similar-looking corridors they started chatting, not really having anything better to do.

"So, you are the son of that Huo Qiang... did he ever mention anything about a senior called Zhang Dong?"

The man had introduced himself as a young master from the Huo clan while shouting at the attackers so this much she knew. She knew that name as he was a close friend of her Master, he even made a pair of beautiful ruby gauntlets for the man.

"Did you s-say Z-Zhang Dong?"

Xue looked at the man, she could tell from his body language that something was wrong, he even twitched a bit the moment he heard her Master's name be mentioned.

"Yes, I'm sure they should be good brothers to each other... am I wrong?"

"Zhang Dong... brothers..."

The man mumbled something under his breath while spacing out slightly, then turned his head to the side to see Zhang Xue behind him.

"Could I ask what your relationship is with this... senior Dong?"

The girl didn't really know why the man seamed down after her Master's name was mentioned. She was now curious about the reason.

"Zhang Dong is our clan's Patriarch, but you probably already know that."

The man nodded, thinking that it would be hard to forget that man's name after what happened back home.

"Well... he is also my Master!"

The girl stopped, quite proud that she could call that man her Master. Her current disposition was all thanks to his superior techniques. Even though he was a bit distant, he was still a great Master that both she and her brother looked up to. She would defend Zhang Dong's honor if she had to, so she squinted a bit as the man in front of her started acting strangely.

"Is there some kind of problem, senior brother Kong?"

The red-haired youth stopped and looked back, his lower lip was trembling a bit. The man started thinking, the girl that he was fancing was part of that Zhang Clan, that was a problem of its own. Now it was even worse, as she was a disciple of the man he learned to despise. There was a reason for that, it started after his father returned from the secret ground.

He was the oldest son of Huo Qiang, also the son of the official wife and not a concubine. He had the highest status, but he still knew that his place wasn't set in stone. He tirelessly worked himself, training like a madman to be the strongest cultivator possible. He knew that his father was in line for the Patriarch spot, but he still wasn't the only one.

There were many clansmen going for that spot, he had uncles and aunts that could replace his father at a moment's notice. The expedition to the secret ground was one such thing. He didn't have any proof but he was sure that one of his family members that were next in line, probably set things in motion. It was lucky that his father made it out alive from that death trap.

Normally he would be proud of his father that proved himself to be one of the strongest. But his father changed, the moment he returned he couldn't shut up about the Zhang Clan or this Zhang Dong that was now apparently his sworn brother. Every day it was Zhang Dong this, Zhang Dong that. His father wouldn't stop, he even coerced the Patriarch to form a binding pact that would last for many years. Apparently he used some techniques that this so-called Zhang Patriarch gave them.

Huo Kong was highly skeptical about this, he thought that the Zhang Clan was of lower status and that this man probably tricked his father in some way. He wanted to even offer his older sister up as a bride, Kong protested this but got trashed by his own dad after saying some hateful words about Zhang Dong in a fit of rage. Due to this, he had a chip on his shoulder and a dislike towards this Zhang Clan and its Patriarch. Thanks to Xue, he had just recalled why he disliked them once more, he had almost forgotten it due to his hormones.

Huo Kong wasn't one to hold back though, he didn't like the whole cloak and dagger approach that other people used. In his opinion, only weak and cowardly people sneaked around, the truly strong let their fist talk instead.

"Problem... yes there is one...to be totally honest..."

Zhang Xue looked at the red-haired man, he looked as if he was going to say something that she didn't like. But before that could happen she felt a disturbance, someone was coming their way.

"Brother Kong, we will have to postpone our talk, I can sense other cultivators coming and I don't think they are friendly!"

The man stopped, he wanted to ask a couple of questions about this girl's Master. But apparently this would have to wait, he put up his guard and got moved forward, Zhang Xue run next to him as the two bolted further into the corridor some shouts heard behind them as the enemies were closing in.

"Here they are!"

"Quick before they can escape!"

"Halt, there is no use running just accept your fate and give us your tokens and you can leave!"

The two could hear the people shouting at them, but they didn't trust them to leave them be after giving up the tokens. Huo Kong wanted to stop and fight, but there was a large group behind him. Even though he felt that he could take on multiple opponents at once, he wasn't sure if he could take on ten of them.

"Go to hell you cowards, the only thing you can do is ganging up!"

He called out while gnashing his teeth. His lovely companion grimaced as she could feel the enemies closing in on them from multiple corridors. Were they being led into a trap like pigs to slaughter? She was sure that if they continued on their path they would run into another group of those cultivators.

There was nowhere else to go but forward though, would they have to fight it out in the end? Suddenly she felt a familiar aura signature, it was behind a wall quite close to where they were at. She took this opportunity, hoping for the best as she shouted out to her red-haired partner.

"Senior brother, help me destroy this wall, there should be something good on the other side!"

The man just looked at the spot that the woman was pointing out. He didn't really mind but he wasn't sure that they could destroy the wall or how thick it was. He also couldn't detect people behind it, the walls were quite good at blocking their senses.

"That wall?... Fine!"

The man's muscles bulged, and some strange patterns covered his muscular frame that made him look as if he was on fire. He then took off, charging at the spot that the junior sister pointed with a shoulder tackle. He looked like a mad bull covered in a blanket of flames, hoping that the spot that he was going for wasn't too thick otherwise his shoulder would be in a dire state.

Chapter 143

Zhang Liu was together with a couple of his clan members, Zhang Tai had gone in a different direction as they were still looking for more of their clansmen. Liu had gone through a couple of small skirmishes with other practitioners so he already had an additional token, only needing one more now.

His group was resting at the moment, they were at one of those spiritual herb gardens and they had just taken care of a trap formation that was previously here.

"These herbs aren't of good quality though, we can get better ones back at spirit spring city...still, it's not good to waste resources. "

Zhang Liu and his clan brothers examined this so-called spirit herb garden. They were from a pill making faction, so this wasn't anything out of the ordinary for them. Zhang Dong had also nabbed scriptures and books that described a way of producing rare variants of certain herbs. So these ordinary spiritual herbs weren't valued that highly by these youths. The few members from the Feng clan and the Huo clan saw it differently as they pocketed as much as they could get their hands on.

While this was happening, Liu felt something or someone coming. There was a familiar aura coming their way, but it looked to be behind a near by wall.

"Wait is that... Hey, look out get away from that wall!"

The youth shouted out, trying to get the attention of the people that were standing closest to the wall. The two people that were standing there, quickly jumped back. They knew that something was wrong and trusted Zhang Liu enough to heed his warning. Just in the nick of time as an angry-looking Huo Kong busted through that chunk of rocks.

"It's that guy?"

Zhang Liu noted while seeing the man covered in red energy, but soon after he could see his white-haired sister following after him. This wasn't the end though as many other angry-looking youths, with drawn weapons charged through after them while shouting various things.

"Don't let them escape!"

"Get them, brothers!"

The group poured through the hole that was slightly larger than a human. At least they tried to, the hole wasn't that wide and some of them ended up getting stuck. Zhang Liu used this chance to move towards his sister and the red-haired man that he fought previously.

"Hah, I knew you were alright Xue... oh and you brought a friend..."

He looked at the burning man that canceled his skill after charging through the wall. His hair was slightly scuffed and he had rock debris all over his body, that looked like scorching coals. Huo Kong just eyed Zhang Liu, he already knew that the two were siblings due to the similar features like the robes and their white hair.

"Hmph!"

He justs scoffed at Liu, still not happy about the things that transpired back at the betting arena. The two youths looked at each other, the shouts of the charging enemy cultivators making them postpone their argument.

"We'll settle the things between us after this trial is over, for now..."

Huo Kong turned around, his fists surging with red Qi.

"Let's take care of these trashes!"

Zhang Liu just smirked and nodded, letting his fist crackle with blue lightning Qi as if he was imitating what Huo Kong was doing. Zhang Xue just looked between the two boys while chuckling. She herself pulled out her brand new spear that her master made and brandished it against her foes. The mix of clan members that was on their side, also charged in.

"Don't let them get through that hole, we can pick them off one by one!"

The hole that the group was coming through was quite small, so they only had room for one person at a time. This could be used to their advantage. Soon a barrage of ranged Qi attacks rained at the group that was pouring through the wall, forcing the group into a defensive stance while the rest of them remained stuck behind it.

"Quickly, charge through... agh!"

An enemy cultivator was sent flying by a well-placed lesser lightning javelin. Zhang Liu's group had the element of surprise on their end as the enemies didn't expect to find anyone on the other side of the wall. They were still outnumbered though and the hole in the wall would just act as a temporary deterrent.

The enemies on the other side could do two things, either risk it all and try to battle it out right here right now, or pull back and reorganize. Being the haughty youths that they were, they went with the former and decided to blast the path open so more of them could fit through.

"Ack, w-what are you doing?"

The problematic thing about that was that they had some of their people crowding at the small opening. The rocky wall was quite robust, made from hard to breakthrough materials. This resulted in some collateral damage in the form of some lesser clan cultivators getting hurt. The youths from the other side belonged to the more powerful group, so they didn't care that much about the well being of the lesser clans that were temporarily helping them out.

Zhang Liu looked at the spectacle and smirked.

'Those guys have no teamwork what so ever... compared to us..."

He glanced to the side, Zhang Tai and the rest of their group were charging through one of the corridors. This looked to be it, the two largest factions against each other. The so-called triforce alliance was outnumbered but not outgunned. From the fifty so Zhang Clan members thirty or so remained.

"Brothers and Sisters... let us show them what the Zhang Clan is made of!"

Everyone shouted in unison and two groups with fifteen people each were formed. This was one of this clan's specialties, the Spirit Serpent Formation that everyone was required to train from this point on. This was one of the formations that was utilized in the secret ground, that this clan had ventured forth. This along with the Floodarmor Formation was now becoming a staple of their training regiment. The two formations could be switched between and grew in strength with the number of cultivators in it.

Zhang Liu was used as the core of one of the formations, while Zhang Tai was in the other. The larger group of cultivators could see two water serpents entangling with each other and then releasing a deep blue beam of condensed Qi in their direction. They were quick to react, putting up various defensive treasures and techniques to block the incoming attack but after one hit they already knew that this wasn't something they could take on easily.

The energy beam made everyone scatter to the sides, the place everyone run was in was a more wide-open area. Still, the two blue serpents had barely enough space to maneuver around here. This was also the reason why the Zhang Clan didn't combine into one large formation.

The other two clans were keeping busy as well. Their teamwork wasn't as grand but you could see various wind-based attacks getting thrown by the Feng ladies. The Huo clan rained down on their enemies with their scorching fists, quickly turning up the heat. The whole area turned into a battlefield, anyone not involved in the two alliances was quick to escape.

"W-what's with these bastards... how are they so strong..."

"How did that little Zhang clan become this strong?... are they getting backed by some sect?"

"Stop yapping and fight, we are getting pushed back...attack them you fools!"

The trial ground rumbled and massive amounts of foundation establishment techniques collided against each other. Small craters riddled the ground and walls, showing just how much power these youths were already able to wield.

After a couple of exchanges, an expert would notice which side was the favored one. The larger alliance started to slowly falter, the stronger clans were using the weaker ones as cannon fodder. This was a massive hit to morale and resulted in the breach of their defenses.

What followed was a domino effect in which their offense collapsed. They were then pushed back by the overwhelming might of the trio of clans.

"D-do you know who I am?...m-my uncle is the....Arghh...."

A small palm landed on an enemy youth's abdomen that propelled him far into the distance. The man slammed into the wall out cold and with foam coming out of his mouth. The small palm belonged to a certain pink-haired lady that just smirked after defeating one of the main young masters from the opposition.

"Hah, serves you right!"

The girl hopped up to the twitching body of the opponent that she defeated and pulled out his token. She could see that the fighting was almost over as her clan members and allies were doing the exact same thing that she was. She looked to the side, spotting a certain white-haired youth.

"Hey....HEY!"

She shouted out in a loud voice towards him as she bounced forward in his direction. Zhang Liu twitched a bit and turned to see the small girl rushing towards him. She came to an abrupt stop, this produced quite the enchanting 'bounce'.

"Ah y-yes, can I help you with something sister Nuana?"

He asked while not being sure what to do about this bundle of energy, or where to look to not seem rude.

"This is my fourth token, this big sister is magnanimous enough to share it with you! Don't be shy and take it!"

She held out the token in front of him, her nose sticking up high as she presented it.

"Ahh... I'm fine, I already have enough of those... maybe one of the other brothers or sisters from our clans can use it..."

Zhang Liu had the pleasure of wandering around this place with this strange girl. From his perspective, she was quite the oddball. The girl was nothing like the people that he knew, she was different from his sister or mother. The other girls that he came across were also more refined and reserved compared to this one, but this gave her a certain amount of charm.

"Ah, I only have two tokens, I could use that one..."

A certain Zhang clan member came over, he had unusually large sword-shaped eyebrows that were quite voluminous too boot. Feng Nuana just gave the youth a death glare and threw the token to the side while tapping her foot on the ground furiously.

On the other side, Zhang Xue and Huo Kong were finishing up as well. They weren't alone though, they were in the company of Zhang Tai that was in the process of glaring daggers at the red haired man.

"Who is thi..."

Before he could ask his question he was assaulted from the side. A girl wrapped her arm around his from one side and another did the same from the other side. These were quite the tanned Feng clan girls, the man they were holding was quite the looker and was also the strongest person beside Zhang Liu.

"Senior brother Tai... why don't we go look for some treasures together~"

"Nooo... Senior brother, wouldn't you rather do it with this junior sister instead?"

The Feng clan women weren't ones to beat around the bush, the man that was deemed worthy of their time would be chased after. The poor guy was surrounded by young women while Zhang Xue and Huo Kong excused themselves. Tai's clan brothers weren't sure if they should be feeling envious of their senior brother or pitty him instead.

"N-noooooo...w-where are you touching... t-that spot it...Ahhhhhhhhhhhh..."

His shouts reverberated around the trial ground as he got pulled away by a group of gyarus. The next time he was seen, he looked quite drained, his hair disheveled and his robe torn.

The last trial's major battle came to a close but it was still not over. There were still people that managed to get away, people from other factions that were hiding in the shadows. The treasure troves were also open for exploration, but the major obstacle for this trio of clans was vanquished. What remained for them was to either wait it out till the time run out, or to find the exit and end it early.

Chapter 144

The Zhang, Huo, and Feng clan members that were still in the trial made sure to search through the area. The places like that one with the embedded sword could be still visited as the threat of getting ambushed was lowered now. Going through it once more and collecting the treasures was now a possibility, the only problem was the lack of spatial rings to carry things around.

The army of puppets that were guarding the more lucrative areas was the only problem now. This would be their last test, but after battling with the combined forces of the other clans and coming up on top the triforce alliance's spirits were at an all-time high. Everyone gave out a battle cry, those automatons were the last obstacle between them and a fat payout.

While the last trial was coming to an end the people organizing the festival were keeping tabs on the results. The tokens had some weak tracking capabilities and every contestant was marked before entering. Thanks to that the judges had an idea of what was happening inside. The incapacitated contestants would be removed by the puppets inside the trial ground. This also gave them added info to what was happening inside even without being there themselves.

"Looks like that Zhang Clan is going to be the big winner this time..."

One of the judges said to one of his co-workers while noting down something on a scroll.

"Who would have thought that such a small clan could achieve this... we must get more info on them..."

The Zhang Clan was slowly attracting more attention, this was equally a good thing and a bad thing. From one side, the increase in renown would let them expand their influence, forge alliances, and make better trade deals. On the other side, it would alert the more powerful forces to their existence.

The Zhang clan was like a carp swimming upstream against a strong current as they tried leaving the small pond they were stuck in. Would they succeed in jumping over the waterfall that was blocking the way and transform into a ferocious dragon? This was still to be seen, but the probability of success wasn't low, the problem were the other dragons on the other side lurking to strike.

While the kids were wrapping up the last trial, a certain youth with a small gem in his forehead was walking down the streets. He was wearing an expensive-looking robe and was accompanied by quite the scary-looking cultivators. He had long flowing charcoal colored hair, and his face looked as if it was sculptured by the gods themselves. Still, the lofty disposition that he was carrying himself with kept the ladies at bay. The moment anyone noticed the man they could only shiver in astonishment or fear. Everyone dropped their heads, trying not to look at anyone from that group. They could tell from the insignia of the dark palm, that this was some kind of powerful young master.

"Young lord Cai, the restaurant that was reserved for you should be just around the corner!"

One of the old looking cultivators proclaimed while walking in front, his eyes scanning the area while scaring off anyone that dared to look in his young master's direction. The young man just nodded and moved forward, hands behind his back looking as if he owned the place.

It was still the middle of the day and people were in a cheerful mood, the Dao Festival was something that even the residents looked forward to. This was mostly due to the fact that they got a lot of tourists that were all big spenders. All the various rich families gathered in this one spot and everyone wanted to give a good impression. This was mostly achieved by spending a lot of money and spirit stones.

Someone like this young master was at the very top of the totem pole though, he didn't really need to show off as the dark palm symbol on his robe already made everyone drop down to their knees. Still, sometimes accidents tended to happen. A group of kids was playing around with some sticks, fighting it out while pretending to be powerful cultivators.

Kids being kids, they didn't really know about the rules of this world quite yet. One of them ended up tripping right in front of the dark palm group, the stick that he was holding on to flying forward and hitting one of the bodyguards on the foot. This wasn't something that could actually cause pain to the man, but that wasn't the problem. The real problem was, that they interfered making their young master stop in his tracks. If a certain Patriarch was here, he would probably be astonished by another child running into a haughty young master.

"How dare you!"

The bodyguard shouted out, the child shrunk back his friends too afraid to go forward as they saw many angry uncles staring at them. The mother of the children was nearby, but that wouldn't really help in this situation.

"Please appease your anger my lord, he is only a silly child..."

The bodyguard wasn't hearing any of it, his life depended on this as well. He could not let people offend his master, he needed to punish this child. He pulled out a whip, cracking it against the ground ready to deliver a sound beating to the peasants in front.

"Stop~"

The man stopped himself, his whip moving to the side while he looked behind himself to his young lord that had spoken up. His tone was cheery as if he saw something interesting.

"You'll have to excuse my men, they are quite overprotective."

"Young lord Cai?"

The man asked a bit confused, but stepped to the side. His young lord walked forward to the mother and child. He reached out with his hand and gave the boy a pat on the head a smile on his face.

"It's fine, the bad man won't do anything to you or your beautiful mother."

The youth with the gem in his forehead pulled out something that looked like candy from his spatial ring and handed it to the child. The mother received a bewitching wink that made her face turn into a red tomato.

"Here have this, give some to your friends too."

The people around the area sighted out in relief. This young lord looked to be on the milder side, the child and his mother left with the rest of the children that were now munching on the treats. The group then went back to their route and towards the restaurant that they were heading towards leaving these commoners to themselves.

"What a nice young man... you wouldn't think he would be from that dark palm sect..."

"This is quite the scoop, such a benevolent young master, a good fit for my daughter!"

"Dream on, he wouldn't want her even as a concubine."

Some people bickered, some laughed while others were a bit skeptical but they couldn't deny the act of mercy. They dispersed after a while leaving the area a newfound admiration for the dark palm master awakening in some of them.

The young master that was called Deng Cai headed to the most luxurious restaurant in the city. It was a large building that looked more like a small castle than a place you would go to eat. The top floor was bought out for this young master's needs, this being one of the boons of being a direct disciple of a powerful Master. He knew that his Master would reward him further if he did well in the coming tournament, but he wasn't worried. The people participating were way below him, he could take them out with his pinky.

"Please follow me, young lord, we have everything prepared for you upstairs!"

A butler looking fellow that didn't look like he belonged to this era guided the small group of people. They used an elevator like treasure to arrive at the top floor. The people were greeted to a group of scantly clad beauties that were swimming around a large swimming pool.

"Please enjoy yourself young lord... everything on this level is specially prepared..."

The butler grinned a bit while looking at the women on the level, some were dancing some were already coming over to guide the clients to a more relaxing part of the restaurant. The man just nodded and headed out, two voluptuous women at each side. They were treating him like a king, feeding him special spirit grapes and letting him grope the ladies all over.

The guard that was close to punishing the child not long ago just looked at the youth. He was still a bit new to this group so he didn't know what to make of this. He was smart enough to not bring it up at least, he wasn't here to party. Still, the way this young man was getting treated was quite envious. This was also a stark contrast to the way he acted previously, gone was the look of a virtuous person, it was now replaced by a lecherous grin.

'Ah, this is the life... as long as I remain Master's disciple, women, wine and power I can have it all... maybe even...'

The man thought to the most powerful member of the sect, shaking his head in disappointment.

'That old fart is a monster... better to wait till his life runs out before even trying to make a move...'

He took a swig from his wine glass while a busty dancer lady offered him some food, feeding him mouth to mouth. While this was happening the youth suddenly felt something, another smirk appearing on his face.

'Here comes the harvest...'

A little ball of light flew through the window, the people in the area oblivious to its existence. It was followed by two more, even the dark palm disciple couldn't really 'see' those balls of light, but he could feel them moving closer. They came to a stop in front of his head, just hovering there as if their purpose was to be there.

Deng Cai closed his eyes for a moment, not paying attention to the scantily clad women around him for the time being. He was focused on the orbs of radiating energy in front of him. They in response moved in closer and finally entered into that gem on his forehead. The gem gave off a faint sheen which soon subsided after the light orbs were absorbed.

'Ah, the young pure ones always taste the best... sadly they were just plain commoners with minimal spiritual energy.'

The man licked his lips and laughed out loud in a rather creepy fashion. This startled the dancing ladies, that took a moment to gather themselves. The sound of zither music drowned out the cackling man while another scene was playing out elsewhere.

"Little Tei... what's wrong, are you feeling unwell?"

The mother from the previous encounter was shaking her son a bit. He looked a bit out of it his eyes glossed over, his hands slumped forward. The boy didn't react, his arms and legs flailing as if he was a ragdoll without any life in him. He was obviously still breathing and was warm to the touch but something was wrong.

"Why won't you answer?"

The woman started shouting, this wasn't the first child the others were all doing the same thing. It was as if something sucked out the very being out of them and left them just a shell of their former self. It didn't look like anything was wrong with them on the outside, but the kids seemed vacant and unresponsive.

The woman had no idea what could be wrong with her children, they were just fine a moment ago but suddenly dropped to their knees. They weren't responding to her, she wasn't a doctor and her husband was still out working. The only thing the woman could do was to gather up her children and place them in bed.

This wasn't the first or last case like this, soon the clinics in the jade city were getting filled up with unresponsive children and people. The doctors were baffled by the strange symptoms by they all came to one consensus, all of these people were missing parts of their soul. The longer they stayed in this state the worse it would get, the only cure was either to return the stolen soul fragment or using a soul treasure that would allow the soul to repair itself. Such treasures were far too rare, the only thing these people could do was to slowly watch as their loved ones drifted away.

Chapter 145

The time was up and the last trial was over. The participants that were still inside the testing area, were forcefully removed by the teleportation formation that was embedded into the trial area. Even though some of the young cultivators were able to last till the end, not all of them were left with the three tokens. Some of them somehow managed to scrape by while hiding from the stronger participants, hoping to nab a token in the end, but to no avail.

A group of youths was slowly appearing in the large auditorium like room. This was the same room through which they entered into the trial through the large teleportation gate. The number of people that were in this room was a lot smaller than previously. The people that were removed during the trial had already gone back to their hotel or clan members by this point.

The youths from the three clan alliance were there as well, with them all together they finished with about fifty members. This would be considered about half of the contestants in the final tournament. The rest was a hodgepodge of other clans and sects, the people that remained were either very lucky to evade the overbearing three clans, or somewhat capable.

Zhang Xue was standing, just looking around. After the big battle, the youths didn't really have many problems in the trial. They run into some of those puppets and traps while traveling, but it wasn't anything that they couldn't manage. She was walking along with her brother that was getting bothered by the short, tanned girl. This self-proclaimed 'big sister' was quite the oddball.

She looked to the sides trying to find her sibling but spotted her red-haired male friend. Huo Kong looked back at her as everyone was teleported into this area but into random locations. This man had proven to be a good ally to this Zhang Xue so she just smiled at him as he was looking in her direction. The man opened his eyes wider and the young girl could see his cheeks turning into a redder shade.

'For such a big lug, he sure is quite innocent...'

Zhang Xue thought to herself while trying not to laugh. She then spotted her white-haired brother that was inching away from something. This 'something' was a busty looking pink-haired girl, she was shouting something at him while the youth looked like he wasn't sure what to do.

'That girl is sure peculiar... but big brother should take care of that himself... I'll tease him about her later.'

She thought that this Feng Nuana was quite an interesting person. She didn't act as anything that Xue had ever seen, she was one of those eccentric people that she heard about. The small girl was a bundle of energy and apparently had it in for her big brother. She was the strongest member of the Feng Clan so the other girls didn't bother her older sibling. She also scared away any other girls that tried approaching him. Liu's younger sister could only look on from the side and giggle, even if her older brother gave her pleading looks she wouldn't help him out.

Xue moved her eyes to the side, she saw another peculiar thing. It was her senior brother Zhang Tai. He was covered in lipstick marks and his robes looked to be torn. Apparently he had spent the rest of his time in the trial ground running away from a gang of gyarus. The girls were relentless but he managed to safeguard his chastity. The number of girls was probably this large due to not being able to bother Zhang Liu that was occupied by the Feng Clan strongest junior member.

'Senior brother sure is popular...'

Xue wasn't really interested in him that much. She knew that the man was vying for her attention, but she wasn't all that interested. There were a couple of reasons for this, mostly she didn't like his double-sided nature. He was nice to her and all, but when it came to others he quickly transformed into a haughty young master type. He also didn't have the body type that this little sister admired, being more on the toned lanky side.

'Think I just need to wait for one of those Feng sisters to nab him, he looks to be very popular with them.'

Everyone that made it through the lat trial rejoiced, they had made it till the end of the road only about a hundred participants remained now. The people responsible for the last test came out, one elder stepped out as he started talking.

"Any fighting past this point is forbidden, please head through this corridor if you have managed to acquire the three tokens."

The man pointed at a door, if they went through it their tokens would be counted and their names would be recorded.

"If you didn't please use the other passageway, also relinquish any tokens you might have on you. Sharing tokens among yourselves from this point forth, is forbidden. Anyone not adhering to this will be forcefully removed!"

If allies wanted to share tokens with each other the judges wouldn't mind if it happened during the trial. For instance, if three people had one token each, they could hand them over to one person to pass the trial. This was also how some of the contestants made it through, either by making deals or threats which were still approved.

The tired group of youths nodded, the winners went to the corridor to get their names recorder and tokens counted. The losers returned theirs to the judges and left in shame. Everyone that made it through would have a number assigned to them, the tournament was an elimination one. This meant that by winning a fight you would move up in the brackets. This was a different method than what Zhang Dong used to test his fighters before moving on to the secret ground. He mostly did that as he thought that an elimination tournament would have a large luck component to itself.

"Zhang Liu... number 42... Zhang Clan... tokens check out... please take your number and move along."

Liu was handed a number and moved along, from what he knew the actual pairings would be given on the day of the Dao Festival. Papers with the numbers would be put into a closed container with an opening on the top. Someone would then pull them out, making the pairings be random and also give the audience something to look forward to.

"Feng Nuana... number 43... Feng Clan..."

He snapped to his senses, the little girl was still sticking close to him and he wasn't sure what to do with her. He didn't have it in himself to get angry at her and whenever he tried hiding or running, she always managed to sniff him out. In the trial area, he always managed to bump into her whenever he tried to ditch her.

'Think she is sticking to me so closely, so that I don't try to run away... what is up with this girl..."

He was getting concerned, but he only needed to power through this tournament and then he could return back to his clan. The girl was from an allied clan but he didn't think that she should be able to bother him at his home turf. The girl had violent tendencies but he didn't think that she would do anything stupid. While he was thinking the girl in question wrapped her hands around his once again, the familiar feeling of something soft against his arm was felt again.

"Gah!"

"Mmm, what is it? No need being shy, I know you like when Big Sis does this, you always get red in the face!"

Feng Nuana proclaimed while tightening her grip on Zhang Liu's arm. The young man went red in the face, while furiously denying this preposterous claim.

"W-who is shy? Who gets red in the face? Let me go this instant!"

He tried shaking her off but the more he moved the more he could see those peaks jiggle. He was still a young man and was quickly subdued by the cute girl's advances. While this was happening he heard a cackle from the side, turning his head he saw a smirking Huo Kong.

"Well, isn't the mighty Zhang Liu quite the ladies' man. Think you and my father would get along."

Huo Kong laughed, his rival looked troubled which instantly made him feel refreshed.

"Just don't forget about the festival tomorrow you two love birds!"

Feng Nuana looked to be happy about being called that, Liu, on the other hand, was fuming from the side.

"Senior brother Huo, should you be saying such things, yourself?"

Huo Kong looked to the side while still smirking, only to catch Zhang Xue's face dangerously close to his when he turned. He instantly backed away while stuttering, the white-haired girl just covered her face with a sleeve and snickered.

"Oh my, the mighty senior is so bashful~"

Kong's face contorted while Liu laughed out from the side, soon everyone left towards the exit with all of their numbers assigned. Zhang Tai was the only one that quickly bolted into the distance, followed by some Feng sisters the girls were apparently still on him.

"Senior Brother Tai sure is popular..."

Liu said while rubbing his head, the shorty that was stuck to his arm was now getting pulled back by the old lady he met in that shop. He was finally free and could stretch out, his arm had quite the girl smell to it now. His sister moved over to him and inhaled, she then poked her own nose.

"Hm... cherries?"

Zhang Liu grimaced and backed off, his sister was looking at him funny and he knew that she wanted to tease him. The two and the rest of their clan members headed back to their hotel to rest. They had limited free time, they had to recover their used up spiritual energy and heal any injuries they had.

Nothing out of the ordinary happened, the elders escorted their juniors back to their quarters. The real festival would be starting soon and the possibility of getting attacked wasn't nill. There were also rumors about some people having their souls drained, there could be demonic cultivators in this city somewhere. So, they had to be more vigilant than ever.

At the headquarters of the Dark Palm outer sect building, an elder with a crooked nose was standing up straight. Opposite him there was a man with a gem in his forehead, it was glistering with an eery light that was giving the crooked nosed elder the creeps.

"Young lord Kai, the festival will be starting in two days, your disciple already had his number assigned and everything has been prepared for his arrival."

This was the governor as well as the man in the highest position from this Dark Palm outer sect. He was still trying to make a good impression on the young lord, but the man that was standing a bit further back was even more important. Even though Yang Kai had a high position, he was still only a core formation cultivator. The man that was standing in the back was the actual VVIP, even though the man with the gem had a strong backing, the elder behind him was an actual Nascent Soul powerhouse.

"Elder Ming, the auction house is still gathering the items for auction, it will open up in three days..."

The man was worried as he couldn't hasten the auction. That establishment had a strong backing and took a neutral stance. Thanks to this the quality of the items that were put up for sale was quite high. Masers even at the nascent soul could procure worthwhile items for themselves, but this was quite rare.

Even though the Dark Palm sect had a zero-tolerance policy for letting others have heaven grade treasures, it had to allow some powers to sell them. This auction house was a large chain store and was owned by a rather strong clan with their own nascent soul monsters. Even the Dark Palm sect couldn't strongman them around. Still, the auction house was only interested in profit. They didn't care what happened to the item after they sold it. If the Dark Palm sect wanted to chase the buyer down afterward it was up to them. Thus it was rare for people without a backing to go for items of that quality. If you tried it, you'd find yourself on this sect's hit list rather quickly.

"Is that so..."

The man just nodded while leaving the area, the atmosphere got lighter when he left even the man with the gem gave out a sigh of relief.

'Elder Ming is always so calm on the outside... hope everything goes well at the auction'

Yang Kai looked at the elder member from his sect leaving, a glint in his eye.

'Well, if not... then I bet there will be an interesting spectacle to watch...'

Chapter 146

The door shut behind the Nascent Soul elder. The man with the crooked nose didn't give away his emotions but he was glad that that man left. He noticed that the young lord Kai gave out a visible sigh, making him think that he was feeling the same way as he did. This man was someone that liked to gossip and gather information on various things, so he spoke up and tried to probe this young lord a bit.

"Elder Ming is such a composed man, isn't he? Heard that among the grand peak elders he is one of the more virtuous!"

He smiled while looking at Yang Kai that looked to be taken aback by what this crooked nosed man just said.

"Composed? Hah, that's a nice joke there. Elder Ming makes my old man look like a docile little puppy in comparison."

The cultivator looked to be amused, the man that asked the question was bewildered by the answer. The elder that just left was quite stoic, he never talked much or complained either. But apparently he was a lot more ferocious than even Yang Kai's father, just the mention of that person made this outer sect elder shiver in his boots.

"Young Master must be joking, how could Elder Ming be that fierce?"

Yang Kai's eyes twinkled a bit and a smirk appeared on his face. He leaned back in his seat and got more comfortable. He would tell this ignorant outer sect elder what was really going on.

"Well, you might not know it as you're not part of the inner sect... but let me tell you something... never go against Elder Ming in any way... don't even meet his eyes if you aren't willing to lose your life!"

The outer sect elder was taken aback as he gasped. Was this elder Ming so vicious that he would give you a good thrashing for looking at him the wrong way?

"What, you think that I'm lying?"

The man moved his hands in front of his face and waved them around in protest while replying to that question.

"My young lord, how could I presume such a thing!"

Yang Kai just smirked while taking a swig from some spirit alcohol that one of his bodyguards handed him.

"I don't blame you, If I didn't see it with my own eyes I would probably have a hard time believing some of the stories concerning him..."

The young lord started relaxing and drinking, he got a lot more chatty as well. He started recounting some of Elder Ming's misdeeds and they were quite ghastly. The man even wiped a whole middle-sized clan from the face of the planet, just for a trivial-sounding offense. From the stories, the outer sect elder found out that the man was awfully pedantic. Everything had to go by the book, so if someone of lower status offended him in any way he wouldn't just let it slide. Either they apologized right away in the appropriate fashion or they were in for a bad time.

"You'd better tell your people to keep things nice and tidy around Elder Ming, or he might blame you if someone offends him."

The crooked nosed elder shivered and started sweating profoundly. He soon excused himself from the room that they were talking about and alerted his most trusted aides. He heard some tales about this nascent soul monster, but he thought they were highly exaggerated. But apparently most of those grim stories were the truth, he needed to put more people on the job and keep anyone that might cause trouble away from this overbearing elder.

'What if he blames me if someone steps on his foot? Then decides to chop my head off along with the rest of my bloodline...'

The man went pale and headed out, he wouldn't be sleeping much for the duration of this auction. He had to make sure that no one offended this merciless sect elder.

At the break of dawn in Jade Grass City, you could hear people shuffling around. Everyone was putting up various stands with all sorts of items. Food, trinkets, and even low-level magical treasures could be seen everywhere. This was the true beginning of the Dao Festival, the residents were ready to earn some cold hard cash. Milking the tourists was one of the main reasons that this event was set up. The clans would have a stick measuring competition and the residents along with the Dark Palm sect would profit.

The tournament would start before noon and depending on how long the participants fought, it could take more than one day to finish. Everyone knew the rules before going inside the ring. There would be a main judge at the side of the ring that was of core formation strength.

His or her job would be to determine if the opponent couldn't participate and to point out the winner. There were no life-saving formations that would prevent death, only a shield that blocked any outcoming attacks going into the audience's stance. The judge was required to jump in if the fight got too spicy.

The juniors that were participating were considered the best of the best at this point, so no one wanted their future leaders to get hurt. Still, accidents did happen, anyone could lose their life in a nerve-racking bout like this. The youngsters mostly weren't that good at holding back and if you tried, you might be the one to die instead.

The place that the tournament took place looked similar to an old Roman colosseum. It was just much, much larger than the old earthen structure. The center stage was the size of a soccer field and it was circular in shape. There was a body of water separating the battle stage and the audience area.

There were a couple of two-meter wide bridges leading to the stage through which the contestants were guided into it. The audience stands were layered and could fit thousands of people. The more elite members like from the Dark Palm sect had their own VIP area that had the best spot to overlook the battles.

The participants would face each other on that large stage, due to the size of it they had enough space to maneuver and use their foundation establishment techniques to their heart's content. Even though the distance from the battle stage was far, the eyes of cultivators above a certain level allowed most people to see just fine.

"Is everything ready?"

Zhang Jin asked while standing opposite another older looking fellow from his clan.

"Yes, Grand Elder. Thanks to the Huo Clan's young master's help you will be able to enjoy the VIP seats. The young Matriarch from the Feng Clan will be joining us as well."

The man proclaimed as the triforce alliance had managed to pull some strings. They had to pay quite the hefty price in spirit stones but they had one of the better seats in the arena.

"Good, We'll be able to see the youngsters taking all the glory in style."

Zhang Jin smirked, knowing well that his junior members were the top batch in this tournament. He was still a bit worried about kicking up too much of a fuss, but some good advertisements would also be very profitable.

"What about the other thing?"

The old man asked while walking forward, ready to head out to the festival ground.

"Ah yes, various clans and sects from the area wanted to have a word with you. They probably want to garner some favor with us after their members lost to our junior members in the trials."

Zhang Jin nodded, he agreed thinking that it was probably the main motive.

"Yes... but be careful, some of them might have some ulterior motives. Be sure to check their background, be careful who you invite."

There was still a possibility of some snakes trying to slip their way into their graces along the way. Even though the junior members were doing great, that didn't mean that their elders were powerful. The other clans could try prodding them to see if they have enough power to defend themselves. The Patriarch wasn't here to show off his strength so Zhang Jin would have to cover for him if something happened.

"They should know that we are allied with two prominent clans, so I don't think they will cause trouble. But stay vigilant and report to me immediately if something happens."

Zhang Jin didn't really worry about the lower sects and clans. He was powerful enough to defend himself now and had a couple tricks up his sleeve. The problem would be if the Dark Palm sect got involved. But he was an old cultivator. He was confident enough in being able to maneuver in this sea of schemes and politics. This was the reason he didn't want his grandson Zhang Dong around, he knew that the Zhang Patriarch wasn't so good with people of a higher status than him.

"Don't forget to stay in contact with the main house though, you never know..."

He didn't want Zhang Dong to come here, but he knew that if something went down that the Patriarch was the only one powerful enough to do something about it. He already knew that the boy was edging towards the nascent soul level. He almost passed out when he showed him the full extent of his power, that finger attack that he demonstrated was something that he wouldn't forget till he died.

There weren't many opportunities to meet Nascent Soul cultivators. So Zhang Jin wasn't sure how his grandson compared to an established master at that realm. Zhang Dong told him that he should be able to last a couple of minutes against someone at the early stage. This was already a shocking discovery, how could someone in the core formation stage and slightly above the age of thirty accomplish something like that?

In Zhang Jin's opinion, Zhang Dong was quite the monster himself. Who in the world heard of a person below the age of hundred with such power? He didn't know that it would be wise to reveal him to the world just yet, so he would have to consider his options before calling his grandson for any help.

The old man sighed out while looking up into the sky. The day was nice and warm, the sky was a nice shade of blue and there were almost no clouds around. This tournament would be over within a couple of days. He really didn't want to consider choosing between his young clan juniors and his grandson. But in reality, there would mostly be one right move he could take and he didn't like the thought of that.

In front of the large colosseum looking structure were many vibrant festival stands. People were shouting and trying to get people's attention to sell their wares. The youths from the three clans were heading through the street altogether. After the last trial, they had gotten closer to each other even though only slightly.

Zhang Xue was covering her face with a veil that only let people see her charming eyes. This didn't stop anyone from staring though as they could tell from the way she conducted herself that she was a beauty. She was walking next to some of her clan sisters, not many remained after the three trials.

Huo Kong had his own entourage but he was sneaking glances at the junior sister that he met in the trial. For some reason, he had suddenly seen the light and wasn't thinking about vengeance against this Zhang Clan. His reasoning being, that no clan with such a gentle beauty could actually be evil. The things that his father said must have been true in the end.

Zhang Liu was stuck with Feng Nuana, he had a concerned look on his face. His arm was already a designated boobrest for the short girl, this making the young man have mixed feelings. He also wanted to know who taught this fiendish arm lock technique to this small girl, was she a demonic cultivator in disguise? Only someone like that could have came up with a ghastly technique like this!

Zhang Tai was surrounded from all sides by the Feng gang. The tanned girls were giving any other women that glanced at their 'target' the stink eye, successfully keeping any other potential contenders at bay.

Soon everyone arrived, the Dao Festival would be officially beginning!

Chapter 147

People poured in like water and quickly filled up the seats. This world didn't have much entertainment with the lack of the internet or TV. So things like fighting tournaments were all the rage. It was very popular among men that were attracted to the contest between two warriors. It was less popular with the women, but they did enjoy seeing the good looking young men participating.

The contestants were led to a side hall while the people in charge were preparing the drawing. The numbers would be announced out loud and a person would write the names of the fighters on a large board. The fighters in question wouldn't be there for the process as they were ordered to wait. If their turn came they would be guided to another room to wait for their turn. This was a long process so most of the people weren't really paying attention.

At the time of the drawing, Zhang Jin was sitting in the VIP booth that he and some of the other elders occupied. He could see Huo Qiang along with his most trusted retainer and bodyguard Huo Qiao, his beard looking pristine as always. The two were sitting together while looking at the stage wondering when Qiang's son's number would be pulled.

On the other side was the Feng Clan elders, Feng Liena and Feng Maling were there together paying attention to the number 43 that belonged to their family members. There were some less important elder members from all the three clans sitting in the back and chatting as well.

"That little rascal has taken a liking to the Zhang boy, even though we told her to not follow the old teachings anymore..."

The old lady shook her head a couple of times before looking to the young Matriarch. The tanned lady was wearing a jade green robe that went well with the green motive of her clan and this city. This was a more modest robe than what she normally wore, and there was a reason for that.

After the explanation Zhang Dong gave her, she started pondering her life choices. One of them was wearing revealing clothes that showed off her peaks, that the old scriptures showed as being the proper attire for their clan members. She didn't abandon the old teachings altogether, picking and choosing as the man said that there were some truths in there. She just needed to find the real ones herself.

The tanned appearance of the Feng clan had nothing to do with makeup or tanning though, it was a side effect of their body refining technique. This was also why Feng Liena's complexion was a lot lighter than the skin tone of the other Feng clan ladies. Her technique was of a higher quality and she didn't suffer such a big side-effect as the others. The same could be said for her younger sister who was using the improved version as well.

"Don't see anything wrong with that... that Zhang Junior seems to be quite the virtuous fellow..."

Feng Liena proclaimed while fanning herself a bit with one of her fans that she received from Zhang Dong as a present.

"Oh? Did you look into him already... or is it because he is the Disciple of that man."

Feng Maling sniggered while looking at her Matriarch whose face twitched.

"If your little sister gets closer to his disciple you'll probably see him a lot more as a result, which wouldn't be bad... But wouldn't it be better to just send that marriage request?"

The old lady probed as she already had attempted to send one of those requests but was stopped by the Matriarch each time. If they followed the old teachings the Matriarch would aggressively go after her 'love target'.

"I... "

Feng Liena moved her face down and blushed slightly. After deliberating about the old texts and that they weren't all that cracked up to be, she just felt slightly silly about the things that she did back in the secret ground. She also felt like the man in question should do some pushing of his own accord, but besides a couple of techniques and items that Zhang Dong had gifted her, she didn't see him all that much.

She was well aware of the way cultivators lived. They spent most of their days cultivating and trying to get stronger either to better themselves or help out their family. She was also scared of getting rejected by the man she was interested in. Thus she was left with waiting it out, but this approach was proving its ineffectiveness.

"Well how about after the festival finishes we head to Spirit Spring City together young lady Feng?"

Zhang Jin butted into the conversation that the two women were having. He was quite proficient in things like this and also felt that it was high time for his grandson to have some kids himself.

"I'm sure the Patriarch will gladly accommodate the whole Feng Clan and the Matriarch, just leave everything to this old man!"

He smiled at the two women, Feng Maling raised her brow a bit but then nodded as this wasn't such a bad idea.

"So it's decided then, we will stop at the Zhang Clan for a week after the tournament is over."

The two elders were agreeing with each other, the young Matriarch in question just sat there quietly while deliberating some more.

"W-well... I don't see a problem with that..."

She covered her face with her fan and smiled slightly, thinking that checking out the Zhang Clan's city wasn't such a bad idea. Though while she was smiling to herself thinking about the robes that she should wear while meeting with the Zhang Patriarch, someone from the side butted in.

"Oh? What are you talking about? Are you heading over to Senior Brother after this? That's a great idea, I'll be able to have a glorious battle with him!"

Huo Qiang slipped into the conversation, which made his retainer grimace from the side while turning his head away in shame. Maling and Liena just glared at him, Zhang Jin just nodded while chuckling.

"Hah, sure thing lord Qiang, just don't destroy our little clan during that 'glorious battle' "

He laughed out loud while moving his attention back to the tournament. The contestant numbers were still being drawn, the process was going slowly. The names of most of the members from his clan weren't yet drawn. He didn't know why but he was getting a bad feeling, like something could go wrong at a moment's notice.

'Must be my imagination... this is a sanctioned and well-protected place... the boy shouldn't have any problems of coming up on top in this tournament. Just hope he doesn't give away too much on the way there though. Xue will be wearing a veil so it should be fine.'

The old man leaned back, hoping that his bad premonition was just him being overprotective in his older years. While the triforce alliance members were talking and bickering with each other, someone was looking at them. Right opposite them was another closed-off booth for very important members, it was a lot more exquisite than theirs though. This was the room that Yang Kai was occupying, there was a special tinted glass blocking anyone from viewing inside of it.

'There you are...'

The man thought to himself, he was alone in this luxury room just sipping on some spirit wine while enjoying the view. His eyes were in the direction of the two Feng clan members that were talking with each other about something.

'Should I just go there... no, it's too soon. I'll let my disciple play with some of those brats first...or should we make it more interesting...'

The man leaned back in his high-quality chair his gaze plastered to someone in that other VIP booth. His face showing a grin as he thought about something interesting.

'Hm, who would she be inclined to help the most...'

The man had a list of participants of the Dao Festival tournament with him. He glanced at the ones coming from a certain wing clan, his eyes stopped at one name in particular.

"Feng Nuana... this one is from her family... perfect..."

He quickly called a Dark Palm sect retainer and sent him out with a plan. He just leaned back and relaxed waiting for the show to start, the tournament would probably not be done correctly due to his interference but he didn't care. Who could go against this young master?

'Elder Ming won't mind, this place belongs to the Dark Palm sect. I can do whatever I want, he just cares about the things in the auction house.'

The papers were getting pulled and the names on the large blackboard were getting filled out. Suddenly a person run-up to one of the members that were scribbling the names on the board. The worker looked at the messenger and quickly nodded. He looked up at the names that were already there as if looking for someone. After a moment he found the name he was looking for, it was already there but there was no one written in yet as an opponent. This was quickly changed as he wrote one peculiar name into that bracket.

In the main resting area where all the participants were standing about nothing, in particular, was happening. Most of the people were keeping to themselves while sitting in a lotus position. Everyone was circulating their Qi through their body to relax and put themselves in the best possible condition. Even Zhang Tai was left alone by the gang of tanned girls as he convinced them that he might suffer in the coming bouts if he doesn't get some space and time to relax.

After some time passed, the first two contestants were pulled to the sides, they moved to the two waiting rooms. They were ordered to wait there and go out after the door opened up.

Zhang Liu and the rest finally heard people cheering from afar, the first bout was on its way. It took about ten minutes for it to end, one of the contestants was carried off on a stretcher to anther room while a cultivator that they weren't familiar with sat back in the waiting room. He looked a bit beaten up but still had a smile on his face, he managed to win it n front of so many people and was proud.

'I wonder when my turn will be...'

Liu wondered if he should take a peek at the fights before his name got called. They were ordered to wait here, but they still were a couple of large windows that allowed them to see and hear what was happening. Not like they were trapped in here and if they were someone that won a match they could just go out before the next round altogether.

Luckily he was one of the people that got called out sooner than later. He quickly moved to the inner waiting room and soon heard his name getting called out. After walking through the large doors he heard a massive amount of cheers and could see a large number of people just shouting.

"Coming from the East gate we have Zhang Liu from the Zhang clan! Give him a round of applause for our young warrior!"

Liu blinked as the voice sounded quite familiar, this was true as the announcer was the exact same man that was doing the commenting during his bout against Huo Kong. His opponent was already out and standing, luckily it wasn't someone from his clan or from the two other allied clans. His opponent looked to be a youth with short brown hair, just a regular looking young cultivator.

Zhang Liu could tell that his opponent wasn't up to par and it didn't take him long to deliver a strong blow to his opponent's abdomen. The adversary quickly passed out while spitting out his lunch, the audience gasped as it was a one-hit KO.

'Did I go too hard?'

He shrugged while leaving, the people cheered while the announcer praised his strength.

'I can leave now till the next round starts, no use waiting here..and Nuana is still in the waiting room...'

Zhang Liu used this chance to slip away while Feng Nuana was stuck in the waiting room. He joined some other people that won their fights. The people gave him odd looks as they were shocked due to the man's one-hit win. Time passed and more and more bouts happened, Liu saw people ripping up some small papers constantly. Those were the betting slips that didn't pan out for the gamblers, the ground was littered with them and it was only going to get worse.

'Should I got bet on myself...'

While thinking to himself he heard a familiar name getting called out.

"Fellow Daoists, from the East gate we have the lovely Feng Nuana!"

He craned his neck back to the stage, the shorty was going to fight with someone. Her opponent wasn't out yet, and people were drooling at the stacked girl that walked out onto the stage.

'She shouldn't have problems with the regular juniors from any clan... don't think that anyone besides Tai or that red-head can beat her.'

He waited for the announcer to give the name of the opponent while looking at the stage. Liu's arms were crossed over one another as he waited.

"From the west gate... the glorious, the gallant, the magnanimous and the brilliant young master Deng Cai. He has graced us with his presence and is a warrior from the inner Dark Palm Sect, please give him a round of applause! "

Zhang Liu's raised a brow slightly as that introduction was slightly overdone. He didn't know who this opponent was, but apparently the announcer had a favorable opinion of him.

Chapter 148

The people in the audience went quiet instantly after the name of the next participant was announced. The uncomfortable silence was then replaced by faint whispering.

"Wait... d-did he say, inner Dark Palm sect?... what is a person like that doing here..."

One person asked.

"Why would someone of that status be here... are they here to cause trouble?"

Another person asked.

"How should I know, this was supposed to be an event for the clans and not for the main sect..."

"This looks fishy... probably something big is going to happen!"

People continued speculating while Deng Cai slowly went over the bridge, the shield flickering on as he entered the stage. He had a faint smirk on his face, hands behind his back while not paying attention to what these commoners were whispering about. He looked at the opponent that he was facing, it was one of the two girls that he was slightly interested in.

'So it's that one...so Master wants me to play around with her?...'

Deng Cai sighed inwardly, his plans were slightly different. He wanted to show off during the tournament against the so-called 'best' of the warriors that those clans had to offer. He would let the fair ladies see how awesome and strong he is, garnering their affection in response.

But now things were different, his master had ordered him to 'play' with this busty yet short girl. He knew Yang Kai's character and what this actually meant in reality.

'Hope I don't break her too much... oh well there still is the second one, and she is more my type than this one.'

The young man looked to the audience, there were a lot of gazes on him. He was someone that liked to appear magnanimous on the outside even though he was quite rotten on the inside in reality. But if his master ordered him to be violent he would follow the order with decisiveness.

The two combatants were now facing each other, the mood was tense as the people that were watching didn't know who to cheer for. They kind of had to go with the young Dark Palm sect master, otherwise, they feared that the sect would think they weren't respecting them enough or giving them enough face.

The young lord smiled at the short lady opposite him, he was quite the handsome young man even the girls in the audience had their hearts skip a beat after getting a load of that hunk.

"What a beautiful fairy I have as an opponent, but don't you worry this lord Cai is quite benevolent when fighting against such beautiful opponents!"

He gave her a slight coquettish grin while still standing with his hands behind his back. Feng Nuana's eyebrows twitched as she had her hands out in a more traditional battle position. She as well as her big sister was someone that used combat fans as a weapon. This tournament allowed the use of personal weapons, the only thing that was forbidden was having spatial rings or pills that boosted your battle strength.

She was kind of mad as she noticed that her opponent wasn't taking her seriously at all. Which made the small girl fume in anger, which was shown in the form of a giant pout on her face. The girl moved her hand out and pointed at the yang man she was going to fight, rage in her eyes.

"Who are you calling a beautiful fairy you idiot, you think this big sis would go for shallow compliments like that, huh?"

She gave the man a malicious glare, her battle fans getting moved in front of her face as she got ready for a fight. She didn't know why, but this guy was pissing her off. He was way too smug and if she remembered correctly, smug and overconfident males weren't good partners. You were supposed to go for the awkward boys, the more troubled they looked the better match they would be.

Deng Cai was taken aback, he was giving the girl his best young master smile and he even blew his bangs upwards for an enchanting effect while talking. How could this woman not be affected by his charms, there must be something wrong with her. Was what this man was thinking to himself.

"No need to be shy lovely fairy, how about we play a little game?"

The man proposed still standing there with his hands behind his back while the people in the audience continued whispering among each other.

"I'll give you five minutes, if you manage to strike me even once, I'll admit defeat."

The man stuck his chest out while posing proudly and swished his sleeve to add to the effect, thinking that this made him look really gallant and charming.

"Huh? Stop spouting nonsense you dandy bastard!"

The small girl fumed with anger as her face got red. She really didn't like how this guy was running his mouth, making it seem like she wasn't even worth his time. She was still part of the young master template, so this was quite the hit to her face. She was oblivious to the Dark Palm Sect behind this man and didn't really worry about things like that.

Feng Nuana gripped her two battle fans tightly and swung them forward. Her mortal grade weapon shone with a green light and produced a blade of wind in the shape of a scythe. The ranged attack flew with astonishing speed at Deng Cai that was still standing there without a care in the world.

"Die you bastard!"

The short girl had quite the potty mouth and continued shouting at the man while producing more razor shape wind blade attacks. The young master with the gem on the forehead on the other hand just dodged. He made it look easy as he dodged the wind scythes, each one of them missed and sliced into the rocky ground leaving deep scratches on it.

"My, my... you're quite the interesting girl... but this is child's-play for this young lord!"

The man continued bouncing side to side while using some strange movement technique that Feng Nuana couldn't get a read on. The girl just as the rest of her clan members was a ranged specialist. She continued pelting her opponent with wind blades, the sheer amount of them was astonishing. The number would leave a normal opponent bleeding and defeated by this point. This man, on the other hand, looked to be enjoying himself as he just soared through the battle stage.

The crowd gasped, they weren't expecting such a one-sided battle. The girl was ranked in the top ten of the current young generation that was taking part in this tournament. But compared to this man she was like a tame little kitten, he wasn't even retaliating, just dodging everything with ease.

Up in the VIP booth where the members of the triforce alliance were sitting, the elders were sweating bullets. They didn't know where this dark palm sect disciple came from, but everyone here knew well who he was.

"What is the disciple of that bastard doing here..."

Feng Liena moved forward and stared at the center stage. Her younger sister was assaulting her opponent with various techniques, but they didn't look to be effective at all. The granny next to her rubbed her chin and also chimed in.

"Could it be a coincidence..."

"I don't think so, this youth wasn't there during the trials. His name wasn't called out during the draws either."

Zhang Jin replied while also standing up from his seat. He didn't like this one bit, this situation was strange. He didn't know what this was about, but it was probably something relating to the Feng clan. The disciple of that Yang Kai was probably moved to fight this young Matriarch's sister for a reason, but what could that be?

"Do you have any ideas about the purpose of this? Did you offend this disciple or his master in any way?"

Feng Liena moved her face to the side and went a bit pale. She remembered one person from the Dark Palm Sect, she didn't give him much face and stormed out the moment he made a marriage proposal out of nowhere.

"The Matriarch did refuse him, I was there with her that time."

Feng Maling replied while following the rest to the edge of the VIP booth as everyone was trying to look at the fight.

"Think this might have been the reason we were sent to that blasted secret ground two years ago. Though we haven't heard anything from him since then..."

The old lady vaguely remembered the Dark Palm young master, he had a strange look in his face. She was the one to apologize after the whole predicament happened for her Matriarch. The man had a weird smile that gave her the chills that time though.

"Maybe you should tell the young one to give up, that young man is clearly just toying with her at this point..."

The old man spoke up while rubbing his chin. He started measuring the young man's strength and was quite surprised that such a young lad existed. He was clearly in the late stage of foundation establishment, even edging on the great circle realm.

'Is this boy really below the age of twenty-one?'

Zhang Liu and Xue were already progressing fast, but even those two might not be at that realm in just a couple of years. Was this youth lying about his age? Even if his age was a lie, he was from the inner sect. The same sect that owned this whole town, they would probably not care or be too afraid to punish him for it.

"Tell her to give up?"

The busty Matriarch looked to the granny next to her, the older woman grimaced and then shrugged.

"I think it would be easier to find a phoenix feather than to convince that sister of mine to surrender..."

Feng Liena was getting worried, it would be great if the battle just ended. Her silly sister didn't look as if she had any chance of winning. At least not if she used the regular Feng Clan techniques that were widespread. But would her pride allow her to go down without a fight?

"Oh, that's a nice breeze my little cute fairy."

Deng Cai chuckled to himself while doing a somersault backward and landing on his two feet. The audience bursting out in cheers at the nice performance.

'Master didn't really give me any specific instructions, so I'll just embarrass her this way... best to not damage her before I have my fun.'

He licked his lips, which gave his opponent the shivers. Feng Nuana narrowed her eyes and stopped showering the man with the wind scythes. She moved her hand backward, her legs bent while she leaned forward. She looked now like someone that was intending to throw a discus from ancient Greece.

The man noticed that she was gathering some spiritual energy into the fan she was holding and just whistled. He was just going to dodge and then deliver a small attack of his own as the five minutes were almost up.

Nuana gritted her teeth and she felt a drastic decrease in her spiritual energy. The moment she 'threw' her fan forward without releasing it you could see a phantom of an emerald hawk behind her. Deng Cai felt like something was off as the greenish looking ranged attack flew forward him. The bolt of energy transformed into a hawk-like bird that charged towards the young man, the speed of this attack was several times faster than of the wind scythes.

Cai's eyes bulged as he dodged to the side, evading the speeding bird just in the nick of time. This was far from over as the green hawk flew upwards and quickly changed its trajectory. It was chasing after its enemy and gaining more speed with each passing moment.

'This one is a bit tricky...'

The man thought while constantly dodging the energy bird, the attack radiating a strong Dao of the winds. But enough was enough, it was apparent that he couldn't evade this thing forever. He moved both his palms forward and chanted something. People could see a faint phantom of a giant mountain behind him.

A giant slab of rock appeared in front of Deng Cai just a few moments afterward. It looked like some kind of mystical wall with some strange runes and patterns etched into it. The green spirit bird collided with the slab of spirit rock producing quite the loud booming sound. After the smoke cleared people saw some cracks on the defensive technique but it was still there, they couldn't say the same thing for the energy animal that was now gone.

"Nice try little fairy but..."

The man couldn't finish his sentence as he felt something off. While he was defending himself he had lost sight of his opponent, this was something that Feng Nuana was counting on. The small girl was already following her previous attack with a close-range one, her battle fan moving towards her opponent.

"Go to hell you bastard!"

"Why you little!"

The man kicked the ground making it quake from the sheer amount of power. He was slightly late on the uptake as the battle fan that was covered by a layer of green spiritual energy sliced right next to his face. The two finally jumped back after the exchange, the small girl clicking her tongue as she didn't manage to get a clean hit on her opponent.

Deng Cai, on the other hand, was seeing red, as the spot between his eyebrow and nose got sliced and he was bleeding. He moved his finger to the wound, it was a shallow cut but he could feel a stinging sensation. His hand shivered and his eyes trembled as he looked at the blood that was now on his fingers. He looked away from the blood and to the person that managed to injure him, his face going red with anger.

"You dare? You fucking bitch!"

Chapter 149

The red liquid dribbled to the ground, there wasn't much of it but this was enough to make this Deng Cai break out into a fit of rage.

"M-my face...m-my beautiful face...this is inexcusable..."

Feng Nuana was still ready to go, she was dejected that the hit didn't go fully through but she still managed to land a hit. She didn't know what that guy was mumbling about, but someone that lost their cool during a fight was mostly an easier opponent.

"Stop whining you dweeb, this is only the start!"

She proclaimed while charging forward, the momentum was on her side and she would use this chance to tip the scales in her favor. Her opponent was still stunned from the bloody gash that was on his face and looked to be enraged. Making someone lose their cool during combat was one way to win and Feng Nuana wanted to use this opportunity.

She wasn't that bad at close quarters combat as some people thought. Her clan was known for their long-range repertoire, but that didn't mean that they were defenseless at close range. The girl already managed to get one shot in from a close attack, so she would try for another one.

The energy from the tips of her fans expanded upwards, turning them into a dangerous slicing weapon. Before her opponent could turn to counter he saw a green light right next to his eyes.

"You dare?"

He managed to evade the small girl's next attack, his long hair bouncing into the attack as it got severed in the process. The man coursed out, his seemingly weak opponent was now giving him a hard time. His feet started shuffling and a brown aura started surrounding his frame. The man's elemental Dao was closer to earth as he was using the Dao of the mountains.

Feng Nuana was ferocious with her attacks but soon enough Deng Cai regained his composure. She managed to slice up his hair and parts of his robe, but the youth surrounded himself with a layer of rock that was indistinguishable from his own skin. Even if she delivered a hit to his body, she could only see cracks instead of blood, as if she struck a massive boulder without managing to crack it.

The man was clearly above her in cultivation and skill. She used her movement technique to quickly jump back, it making her look like she was gliding on the winds.

"I have no idea what a dweeb is, but you will regret what you did!"

The man dusted himself off, the cracks on his rocky skin vanished as if he was regenerating.

'Thump!'

Deng Cai stepped forward, the ground cracked underneath his foot and you could see spiderweb-like fissures forming on the floor. Feng Nuana moved into a defensive position and moved backward as she knew that he was coming. The young man blasted forward, every step he took cracked ground with his footprint was left. The more steps that he took, the deeper the holes in the ground were and the faster he was moving.

This was also a type of movement technique, but instead of evasion, it was used for offense. The practitioner would build-up spiritual force with each step they took, while building up momentum that allowed them to move faster. The longer they used this movement technique they faster they would become and the more damage they would deliver to their target if they managed to strike.

At the time Feng Nuana was skipping backward while using her soaring wing step technique. This technique allowed her to just skip along the ground, each little step propelling her far away from her adversary. This was a graceful technique that conserved a lot of energy while allowing her to dodge with minimal movement.

The audience gasped and cheered. They were now seeing a game of cat and mouse. The young lady was jumping back and to the sides evading the man rushing at her with all his might. He was like a locomotive, that couldn't be stopped. Any spiritual techniques that the girl tried throwing at him just bounced off without doing any damage. The man was clearly proficient at defense, but his speed wasn't anything to scoff at as he was slowly gaining on the poor girl.

Zhang Liu was also looking at from the side, he could see that the annoying girl was in trouble.

'If she can't deliver any damage then she is done for...'

He looked at her opponent, the young man's eyes were glowing red and the gem on his forehead was also looking eerie. Due to the nature of his movement technique, he was gaining speed fast. Soon enough he was upon her, his hand moving out to strike.

'Peng'

Feng Nuana moved both her fans in front of her chest to defend herself. The palm strike that was thrown by her opponent, struck right at her weapons. The mortal grade weapons cracked a bit while she herself got thrown to the side by the pressure of the hit. This wasn't over though, as before she had time to recover another strike in the form of a kick was thrown her way.

"Ack!"

She defended herself yet again with her battle fans, but the one closest to the foot just fractured and its pieces flew everywhere. She was even infusing them with her spiritual energy but that didn't do anything to lessen the blow. Her arm felt numb but she wasn't defeated yet, her second fan was still there and could be used for a counter-attack.

Feng Nuana gave it a shot, while her opponent was in a blind rage she spun her whole body around. She was using the momentum that she gained from her enemies kick while making her body spin to receive less damage. It looked flashy and now her remaining fan was getting swung right at Deng Cai's face.

The girl's green wind energy collided against the young man's brownish earth energy kicking up a storm. The people stood up from her seats, their eyes glued to the large tournament stage.

"Was that all?"

Feng Nuana gulped as her enemy just grasped her wrist before she could fully swing down with her battle fan. The energy from her attack got lowered and didn't manage to go through the dark palm sect members' defenses. She was now stuck, she couldn't move her arm so she tried delivering a kick to the opponent's face while she was still slightly above the ground.

"Hmph!"

"Ack..."

Before her kick could go through she felt a sharp pain in her abdomen. Her mouth opened wide and she gasped out in pain, the hit propelling her back. She didn't fly much though as the man was still grasping her slim wrist and wasn't intending to let go any time soon.

"You're not going anywhere, you harlot!"

The short girl didn't have time to even reply as she felt a sharp pain on her face, her cheek in particular. A metallic taste filled her mouth after the slap, her eyes going wide as she protested. She wanted to retaliate, her legs and hands squirming around but to no avail as the man's defenses proved themselves too tough to break.

"Not so chatty now, are you?"

The sounds of slapping resound around the stage. The people in the large colosseum structure could only gulp as they saw the overbearing young master hit the poor young girl's face over and over again. The person with the biggest shock was Feng Liena, her hands were grasping the balustrade. It was made from hard steel, but even it was bending in odd ways as this woman mangled it in fury.

"How dare he...to my little sister..."

The people to her side looked to the one-sided battle, then back to the woman that was watching the whole thing in fury. They knew well what she felt, but this youth had a large backing behind him and this was a sanctioned battle. It wouldn't look good on their part if they got involved. The other danger was offending the man that was standing behind this disciple, his master who was someone with powerful connections.

"Lady Liena please calm down, things like this happen. The boy was just stronger than her, he might be overdoing it slightly... but if he doesn't target her life than its not our place to intervene..."

Zhang Jin said while moving closer to the woman that was close to jumping down from the VIP booth. She was even getting held back by her grandma that was sweating bullets and not sure herself, of what to do.

"Y-yes listen to the elder from the Zhang Clan... wounds and pride can be healed, but we can not offend the Dark Palm sect!"

Feng Liena was still mad, but the threat of the Dark Palm Sect that was looming over her head was a good enough deterrent to make her stop. There was also another option that they could go with, that was milder even though they would take a hit to their face. While the Feng Matriarch was contemplating her choices, her little sister was tossed to the side.

"Ugh..."

Her face was all red from all the slaps she received, it was even swollen. Her battle spirit wasn't broken just yet though, her eyes were still staring daggers at the haughty young master.

"Oh, still defiant?"

Deng Cai said while smirking, he moved two of his fingers up to his face. The previous gash that was there was covered up by his rock armor now so it couldn't be seen, but he still could feel the wound throbbing.

"You think this is over... you damaged my face... so I'll do the same to you!"

He moved closer while outstretching his hand, his palm visible as something formed on it. It was a small rock that quickly expanded and got thinner, soon it changed into an impromptu dagger with a razor-sharp edge.

"After I'm through with you, your own mother won't recognize you!"

The man got nearer while Feng Nuana tried standing up to defend herself. Her legs were shaky though, the slaps weren't just regular hits they were boosted by the man's spiritual energy. Her own Qi got dispersed while the enemies spiritual energy invaded her body and caused chaos inside. But before Deng Cai could go through with his dastardly deed, Feng Liena finally shouted out her cultivation base of the great circle of core formation blasting out.

"Halt, that's enough! This battle ends now, the Feng Clan admits that Feng Nuana has lost this bout and we request for it to end!"

She shouted out so that everyone here could hear her. The judge that was overlooking the whole thing looked at the VIP booth from where the voice was coming from and could see the woman that roared out. This wasn't anything out of the ordinary but didn't happen too often, an elder member of the participant could announce their defeat if they felt that their junior was in danger. Most of the time this didn't happen as everyone took the matter of pride and face even more seriously than the life of a junior.

The judge didn't really have a reason to refuse the request. He was about to stand up and give his verdict, even though Deng Cai was an inner sect member he still was only a junior so he would have to follow the judge's order here.

"I announce this match..."

"HALT, THIS MATCH WILL NOT END!"

An even more dastardly aura filled the area, this one blasting out from another VIP booth that was right opposite the one the Triforce alliance was residing in. The People in the audience were feeling dizzy, they were lower-level cultivators so when people at the pinnacle of core formation bombarded them with their aura, they felt like puking.

The judge looked up to the other person, his eye twitched a bit. He soon cupped his fists and bowed, he sat back down in his seat as if nothing happened.

"Continue the match, both of the participants are still able..."

He murmured a bit, not being able to go against Yang Kai that was a high ranking Dark Palm Sect elder and from the direct line of the sect Patriarch.

Feng Liena and her grandmother starred at the man that spoke up, recognizing his smug face from the time two years ago. This was the same man that tried proposing to the young Matriarch. Both of them were present at the time, but due to their ancestral teachings, they refused his advances. Now their decision came back to bite them yet again.

Chapter 150

Yang Kai waited for the right time to speak out. His disciple was now giving that Feng Clan girl a good beating, his master was quite okay with the tough handling of the lady. He didn't see anything wrong with it as he only cared about things related to him, other people that got in the way could be used and abused.

"There they go..."

The Feng Matriarch finally got involved in the fight, throwing in the towel to stop it her aura filling the whole colosseum. The guards that were keeping watch were alerted to the spike in spiritual Qi, and it was a lot of it. The woman was already at the great circle of core formation, so even the people from the Dark Palm sect would have some troubles of handling her without someone at the nascent soul to totally overpower her.

"It's time..."

The man smirked and moved his finger out. His spatial ring glowing faintly as a mirror appeared in front of him. He moved his face to one side and then to the other. He grinned widely so that he could see those pearly whites of his, and he made sure not to have any pieces of food stuck there. Yes, he was mostly just checking if he looked presentable.

"Mmm, no woman could resist this smile!"

He nodded to his reflection in the mirror and put it back into his spatial ring. His VIP room had a window that blocked prying eyes from seeing inside. This one-way glass started slowly sliding down as it revealed the Dark Palm lord inside the VIP room. The people didn't notice it yet as this room was positioned above the audience. Yang Kai then cleared his throat and took in a good amount of air before shouting out.

"HALT, THIS MATCH WILL NOT END!"

His intentions were made clear and the Feng Matriarch's eyes went bloodshot. The judge that was overseeing the whole thing just bowed and returned to his seat, not wanting to get involved in this young master's scheme.

"It would be rude to stop a match between two youths just yet, look at that girl she is still standing, she has yet to show us her true potential."

The man said in a calm voice, but it was backed by his cultivation so everyone in the area could clearly hear him. Feng Liena and the rest of the people that were in her VIP booth were taken aback. The man clearly had way more pull here than they could ever have, this was his home turf and they were just some country bumpkins. Still, the young Matriarch couldn't just let her sister be brutally mutilated or maybe even worse, die.

She bowed slightly while cupping her fists and bowing towards the man that shouted out. She might be able to get out of this predicament if the man called Yang Kai could be reasoned with.

"The Matriarch from the Fang Clan greets senior from the Dark Palm Sect."

The man just nodded while trying not to grin too much. This was more or less a signal as he allowed the woman to speak.

"My foolish sister is beneath the junior she is fighting and has clearly lost, please allow us to end this match senior..."

The man looked at his disciple that was holding on to the girl's hair, he had the impromptu rock blade in his hand and was ready to start cutting. He had stopped for the time being as the aura that Feng Liena released had caught him off guard. He was still only in the foundation establishment so he could handle someone at the core formation level.

The shield that was protecting the ring only partially held the aura attack at bay. Now he was just watching the show, his rage had subsided slightly but he would still like to carve out something on this girl's face. His cover of a wholesome young master was already out of the window, so he didn't care anymore.

"Yes indeed, she was a foolish child... but she managed to injure my cute disciple and I'm not sure he is willing to let things go that easily..."

He looked at Deng Cai that just nodded and moved his blade to the girl's face, inching it closer and closer.

"P-please wait... I'm sure we could work something out, show mercy oh great senior!"

This time Feng Maling moved in, bowing her head while almost hitting the railing in the process. To Cai's surprise, he saw his Master moving his hand upwards that indicated him to stop before he could touch the girl's skin.

"Hmm... work something out you say... yes we could do that... how about..."

The man paused for a moment, making it look as if he was contemplating this matter very seriously. His eyes were closed and he was even rubbing his chin with his own thumb for a dramatic effect. His eyes then shot up and he did a little clap, indicating that he had some kind of idea.

"How about we have a small wager? If you win my disciple will leave your clan member be and the match will be over."

He then licked his lips and continued to talk, no one brave enough to interrupt his speech.

"But if you lose, you'll have to give me something ... something substantively more valuable than that little girl's life..."

The Feng Matriarch went quiet. She didn't know what the wager would be or what the thing that this man wanted was, but she had a hunch about what it was.

"How would we go about this wager..."

She asked, quite curious. The man swished his long robe sleeve and just looked back with a sneer.

"Oh, nothing too serious. This whole thing started as a squabble between the junior generation, so it would be best if they handled it."

The woman still didn't know where this man was going with it, so she just stayed quiet and listened to the explanation.

"What I mean is, have another from your members fight my disciple. They just need to win against my disciple, anyone is fine if you can get them to fight for you."

The man moved his hand outward making it look as if he was trying to hug someone as he finished talking. The gist of it was that he wanted the Feng Clan to get someone to face his disciple in battle, if that person won they would all be free to go. He didn't think that anyone from these clans could actually beat his disciple, so in his eyes, this was a sure-fire win.

"How about I give you an incense stick of time to make your arrangements? "

The man grinned once more, not really caring if the other side could coax someone to fight for them. The Feng Clan didn't possess anyone stronger than Feng Nuana, so they would have to seek help elsewhere.

The old Feng Maling looked to her Matriarch and then to the other two elders from the triforce alliance. Zhang Jin and Huo Qiang were the only two people that could help them out. The problem was if they would offer their help and potentially get themselves in trouble with the Dark Palm Sect master.

They didn't know how strong the juniors from their allies camps were and even if they won, would that Yang Kai keep his promise? The two men were being quiet as they were thinking about what to do. They heard the whole conversation and both of them had an able fighter for this task.

The Huo Clan had the young master that was also the son of Huo Qiang. The man wasn't really too eager to exchange his son's life for this Feng Nuana that he didn't know too well. The Zhang Clan had both Zhang Tai and Zhang Liu that would probably be the only ones capable of giving the Dark Palm Sect young master a good fight.

The problem was the same for the Zhang Clan though, were they willing to potentially give up the life of one of their promising youths. If you thought about it rationally there wasn't. The Feng Clan was weaker than the Huo clan and had fewer resources, the Zhang Clan was on the rise and would probably overtake both of these clans in no time. The only thing stopping them from growing, would be a strong sect like this one that Master belonged too.

Still, these three clans had an alliance. This would probably doom their contract to fail and soil their future relationships if they didn't do anything at all. Before any of the two men could voice their worries, the Feng Matriarch spoke out.

"You two don't need to trouble yourselves, this is something that the Feng Clan has to resolve."

The two men looked at each other and then back to the young woman. She might have sounded resolute, but the two knew that she was shaken. She couldn't hide that quivering lip and her saddened tone from these two. The woman turned to face the grinning man and asked.

"What would the senior want to exchange for the wager, the Feng Clan doesn't really have many things to offer to someone from a distinguished sect like yours."

The two Feng elders kind of knew what the man wanted, but was he really that kind of person to still demand it?

Yang Kai stopped smiling, the question was asked and people were looking at him with curious gazes. Everyone was wondering what this man wanted, why was he bothering someone from a weak clan out in the open and making a huge scene. Were people at high positions just strange and eccentric like this?

"The thing that I want is..."

The man cleared his throat and pointed at the Feng Clan women, he was quite far away but everyone knew at who he was pointing out as his sentence ended.

"You!"

Feng Liena didn't move back, as the finger was pointing right at her. Her granny just shook her head side to side while thinking back to that strange marriage proposal the man made two years ago.

"Well, the time is up let me hear your decision... I also might be willing to forget about the whole thing if you just offer yourself up to me..."

"I..."

"I will face him!"

Before Feng Liena could reply she heard a voice from the audience. The person that the voice belonged to sounded resolute and young. Everyone looked to the person shouting out, it was a certain youth with mostly white hair and a patch of black strands in the front. Yes this was Zhang Liu that was calling out to the VIP booth.

"Let me fight elders, I'll be sure to win this wager for you! I bet my Master would agree with me if he was here!"

Zhang Jin almost got a heart attack as the thing that he wanted to avoid was now out in the open. His young grandson was probably the only one from the bunch that had a realistic chance to win this fight. The problem was not the winning part, but the actions that strange Yang Kai would take if his disciple actually lost.

The Dark Palm Master in question just looked at the youth with a raised brow. Zhang Liu shivered as he could feel the man's oppressive aura wash over him. He was getting probed by the man, Yang Kai just smiled after noticing the low level that this youth was at.

"Well, well. I see that we have someone that is willing, think we can get this over with now."

The man was quick to react as things were going his way. His disciple would defeat this wannabe white knight and he would go home with the prize. He wouldn't take no for an answer now and was hoping for a good show from his disciple.

"P-please wait, this..."

Feng Liena panicked, this was Zhang Dong's disciple. She couldn't let him get harmed while she was around, this wasn't going her way at all.

"I-I'll go with you... let us just stop this..."

The woman trembled and was ready to give up, she didn't want to get any more people involved in her private matters. She felt that it was more important to get these juniors home safely now, than her own life. She didn't feel like the man would harm her, at most she would have to become his concubine. This was something she was willing to do, her sister's life was more important.

"You?... I think you are misunderstanding something here..."

Yang Kai spoke out while sighing. This making Liena and the people around here even more confused.

"But you said that you wanted me?"

The woman pointed to herself while question marks appeared over her head.

"No... I was clearly pointing to that lovely lady... why would I want someone like you?"

The people in the audience went silent, the same thing happened to the elders in the VIP booth. Everyone looked to the person that was standing next to the Feng Matriarch. She was the only other woman there and was standing next to Feng Liena when Yang Kai was pointing out with his finger. The only person that wasn't surprised was Deng Cai, he knew his Master's 'tastes' quite well now. Yes, he was a man that liked his women a bit older...

Chapter 151

Some people whispered, some were silent and others just baffled. The VIP booth that Feng Maling was in was above ground and people couldn't really see her well. The people that couldn't see craned their necks, wondering if there was another beauty in there that this Dark Palm Sect master was aiming for. Though, the moment they saw who was standing next to the Feng Matriarch they went slackjawed.

"Is that a human-sized raisin?"

"My god... why would he want that old crow..."

"That wrinkled up potato is the 'lovely lady' ?"

The people in the audience whispered among each other, holding their hands over their mouths while trying not to stand out. This development was far too shocking for the commoners, not knowing how they should react. This also prompted them to gossip and murmur with each other.

Luckily Yang Kai was far too focused on the person that he wanted to take home, the granny in question far too taken aback to react. She looked at the baffled people around her, Zhang Jin was just scratching his head while Huo Qiang and his retainer were sweating in the back not sure what to do about this situation.

"The young lord must be joking..."

Feng Maling spoke out, not sure if she should feel flattered that a handsome young man like that was interested in her or is she should feel disgusted. The man might look like a nice catch on the outside, but she knew well that he was rotten on the inside. There were warning signals firing off in her mind, there must have been a deeper reason why he wanted her and not the younger Feng Matriarch instead.

"Young lord, you shouldn't be making fun of old ladies like me."

She tried laughing the whole thing off, attributing it to being a badly timed joke.

"You shouldn't be acting so bashful, don't worry this young lord can see your true inner beauty~."

Yang Kai's eyes were sparkling as if he saw some kind of divine being. The people next to the old lady that were from the triforce alliance noticed this and visually cringed. It as if the man was looking at some once in a lifetime beauty, he became more animated his expression become less stern and he was even slightly blushing.

'Is this guy serious, what kind of situation is this?'

Zhang Jin was to the side looking at the whole thing. He knew his way around the ladies, but he still couldn't see what the man was seeing.

'Maybe if she was two hundred years younger...'

The old granny was quite the looked back in the day, he still remembered those good old days. Though have barely survived the aftermath of his fooling around.

'But wait... this might be a good thing...'

Zhang Jin rubbed his chin and nodded, then he sent his voice next to the Feng elder ear so that others couldn't hear them.

"Hey, you old bat, why don't you agree to his offer?"

Feng Maling just twitched and moved her gaze to the side to the old fox that was sitting slightly to the side.

"What do you mean you old fart?"

She replied to him while using the same technique.

"Think about it, the young lass will be saved and your Matriarch won't be taken either."

The old man started talking, from his perspective the whole situation was already too dire. If they made any mistakes everyone in here along with their clans could end up dead or enslaved.

"He isn't so bad looking and below the age of a hundred. He is quite a good catch for you!"

Feng Maling trembled even more and tried not to show any facial expressions while the two talked. While this was happening Yang Kai was throwing praises and sweet words towards her, so it was quite hard to concentrate. Zhang Jin, on the other hand, was running his mouth like he was trying to sell her off. This made it look like he was some father trying to convince his daughter to an arranged marriage.

"See... it's the best choice in the situation... maybe he will give you a good rejuvenation pill... you'll just pop him out a couple of kids and it will all be fine in the end!"

"You'll be laughing about it in a couple of years, think about how the clan will prosper... it's a small price to pay!"

The old woman wanted to vomit. Why was an old granny like her getting sold off to a powerful sect master as a bride now, this just didn't make any sense. Still, if she thought about it, this was the lesser of two evils. This would be better for the Feng clan and her granddaughters, the younger one was still on that battle stage.

Deng Cai had moved away from his target at the moment, waiting for his master to be done with the arrangements. He was still mad about the wound, but if his master ordered him, he would let the girl go. Zhang Liu was still standing on the side while glaring daggers at the Dark Palm youth. Zhang Jin, on the other hand, was trying to prevent the fight at all costs. He didn't want his grandson to face that youth, not due to fear of him losing but more of the fear of him actually winning.

'That Yang Kai's word isn't worth shit, if Liu trashes that brat of his I'm sure he will intervene...'

Is what he thought to himself. If push came to shove he would protect his family to the bitter end, he was still on the fence about alerting his youthful Patriarch that was still back at Spirit Spring City. He was sure that Zhang Dong would quickly rush here with all his might if he sent him a message with a communication jade.

He knew that his grandson would act rashly, fighting would be unavoidable. Offering up Feng Maling might be cruel, but it was the better option. Everything could be resolved and everyone here could still go home to their loved ones. He was also sure that the old lady was thinking along these lines as well.

"And that is why fairy Maling should..."

Yang Kai was still at it, but his face suddenly contorted. He was a master at a certain level and he could tell that the old woman that he was talking to was very absent-minded. At first, he thought that she was just being shy and overwhelmed with his forward approach. Who wouldn't be bashful if such a young lord as him showed him so much affection?

But then he noticed another suspicious elder sitting in the VIP booth. The old man had gray hair and he had a large scar ruing through his face. It looked like someone tried slicing his face with a sword, but just managed to get part of his eyebrow along with his cheek while missing the eye by a millimeter as it was still there.

Kai could tell that the man was quite intimate with the woman he was going for. The two were apparently exchanging information with each other. You could feel the faint spiritual fluctuations that they were using to communicate if you concentrated hard enough. His heart rate increased and he clenched his jaw tightly while slamming his fist down on the edge of his VIP booth.

"You! what is your relationship with Fairy Maling! Tell me this instant!"

The people's faces contorted in a strange way as soon as they heard the man attributed the word 'fairy' to the old burned potato looking grandma.

"Y-you see..."

Zhang Jin jumped back slightly, he could feel the man's overbearing aura moving his way as if he was trying to make him back off.

"I am just a humble cultivator from the Zhang Clan..."

He had to at least introduce himself to the man, he probably was thinking it was rude that the two were talking with each other while he was doing his monologue. The old man decided to remove himself from the equation, just bowing his head down hoping that Yang Kai would just attribute it to his old age.

"You two clearly know each other..."

The man squinted with his eyes. The person named Zhang Jin was close to the age of the person he was trying to pull to his side. They were also clearly very familiar with each other and were even in the same VIP booth, there had to be a reason for it. What if this old man was also someone striving for the affections of this lovely old lady. He must have also noticed the peculiar qualities that this Feng Maling possessed and he wanted to snatch them for himself.

'Hah, I'm on to you old man... that woman will be mine...Zhang, Hm?'

The man looked at the youth that declared that he would fight to save that Feng junior. He could just take the old woman and that would be it, but that would be too easy.

"Hm, well I think we had talked for far too long. That youth was willing to face my disciple, so let the battle start."

Yang Kai smirked, he would show that old fart his place by letting his disciple massacre that junior of his. He was on the winning end in every situation, his disciple losing to some backwater cultivator wasn't possible. Deng Cai just stepped away from Feng Nuana, the girl slowly limping away while trying to get as much distance from her enemy as possible.

"My lord, please wait...we don't have to..."

Zhang Jin's stomach churned and his palms got sweaty as things were moving in a direction that he wanted to avoid. He could see that Dark Palm Disciple moving away, the energy shield that covered the ring got removed as well. Zhang Liu didn't care much for what those elders were talking about, he just didn't want the girl to get beaten and bruised any more than this.

"That's enough from you, sit down!"

Yang Kai held his palm out and looked at Zhang Jin in a stern fashion. His stare got quite intense which forced this elder to shut up and follow the order. This wasn't over though, many other core formation experts started gathering around the colosseum and even close to the VIP booth that the triforce alliance was in.

These were the various bodyguards that the Dark Palm Sect master possessed. They were mostly in the late stage of core formation and there were ten of them. They had gathered there to keep everyone in check, their young lord didn't want any of those people to flee. The atmosphere in the area got quite stuffy, but suddenly the familiar voice of the peppy announcer boomed out to lower the tension.

"What a twist! Our young Lord Cai has a new opponent and it's Zhang Liu, let us give a round of applause for our contenders!"

The people could only sneer to themselves while clapping, knowing well that the poor Zhang junior would be trashed by this Dark Palm junior. While this was happening Feng Nuana was limping off stage, Zhang Liu was next to her and the two were passing each other. The short girl looked at the boy with mixed feelings.

"P-please be careful..."

She sounded meeker than before, her eyes were darting around as she wasn't sure what to look at. Then the youth did something strange, he held his hand out to the side his palm open. He then glanced at the girl and waited.

"W-what?"

She wasn't sure what to do but the youth just waited while indicating that she was supposed to do something. The girl then thought back to the ancient texts, there was something in there like this, but how did this youth know about it. It took her a bit to react but she gently tapped her palm against Liu's, the youth then finally moved on while saying.

"Tag in!"

Chapter 152

The girl looked at her hand and then at the back of the young man that moved past her. She kind of knew what this act meant, having the old 'texts' to go back to. Zhang Liu had learned it from his Master on one occasion.

It was one of the rare days that he and his sister were allowed to spar with Zhang Dong. Their Master wasn't really taking them seriously and only dodging their attacks while the two tired themselves out, he then gave them some pointers. The 'tag in' came to be whenever he or his sister switched out, their Master told them that it was an old custom. You were supposed to slap the hand of the person you were exchanging before going into battle in their stead.

Back at the center stage Zhang Liu continued walking while staring daggers at his new opponent. He wasn't all that close to the girl that he was exchanging, but he couldn't just stand there and watch this continue. Deng Cai on the other side was just standing there with his hands behind his back. His face went back to being calm and collected, you couldn't see the rage-filled expression that it once had.

The audience tried cheering, it didn't feel right though. The atmosphere in this colosseum was stifling, the Dark Palm cultivators were now out and about. People were even trying to leave but the paths of escape were blocked. Apparently, Yang Kai wanted everyone to watch this show, even if he had to force them to do so.

Zhang Jin could only sit himself back while looking down at the large football-sized battle stage below him. It was too late to call for help at this point, he had missed his chance. There were now many core formation experts around him, if he tried sending a message with his communication jade they would notice it.

He scanned his surroundings, the only people that would be willing to help him if something happened were sitting in the booth together with him. Even then, they only had five core formation fighters with him on their side. The strongest from them being the young master from the Huo clan.

He was the only one that wasn't yet involved in this fiasco, the Dark Palm master didn't interact with him and also didn't seem to want anything from their side. Realistically speaking, there was no reason besides his friendship towards Zhang Dong to help them. Zhang Jin didn't know if he would jump in to help them, their relationship was still kind of vague. They were friendly with each other, but the old man had seen enough paper-thin bonds breaking off at critical junctures.

There were two core formation experts in the room with them now, both in the late stage. Zhang Jin was in the middle stage himself the same as the old Feng grandma. The Feng Matriarch was already at the Great circle along with Huo Qiang, so they could handle themselves. The problem were all the experts that were spread around the area, there were far too many of them. While the old man racked his brain about the way to get out of this situation, his great-grandson was ready to fight.

"Without further adieu, let us start the bout!"

Deng Cai strutted forward slowly while tossing his head backward and shaking his head.

"First I get to face a weak little girl and now a brat."

Cai's words were followed by an arrogant laugh, his nose raised high in the air as if he was mocking his opponent.

Zhang Liu narrowed his eyes while tapping his foot on the ground. His opponent wasn't taking him seriously at all, which made this youth clench his fist tightly. He didn't take the bate and just took on his fighting posture, he would show him his superiority with his actions and not with his words.

"Hah, silent type? How about this... I'll let you make ten moves before I retaliate. You should be glad that this lord is giving you such an opportunity!"

Deng Cai chuckled more and just stood there, his hands running through his long hair as he made sure to strike a valiant pose for the young ladies on the side. Liu just clenched his teeth in response, holding himself back while the other person continued to mock him during this life and death situation.

'Calm down... this is not an opponent I can take lightly.'

The white-haired boy lowered his posture and started pushing his spiritual energy into his legs. He was trying to make the whole process as inconspicuous as possible. If the enemy noticed and predicted where the attack was coming from, it wouldn't bode well for Liu. Luckily his techniques were all of superior quality, his Dao and Qi as pure as humanly possible.

He took his chance, while the older youth was busy with trying to look good he charged forward. A faint afterimage was left behind in his wake, lightning crackled and thunder boomed the moment the young man took off. The abrupt movement startled his opponent, this was what he was aiming for. His lightning charged fist flew forward, most of the people weren't able to see what was happening as it all happened in a matter of seconds.

THOOoooM!

Sparks flew and the aftershock made the ground vibrate. After the smoke cleared the people could see the result of the white-haired youths attack.

"You surprised me there..."

Deng Cai spoke out, his hand raised to cover his face. Zhang Liu didn't expect this, his fist connected with his opponent, but not with his face. He was stopped by his opponent's forearm that was showing cracks due to the heavy hit it took. Still, this wasn't enough to get through the rocky defenses of this man.

"What happened to giving me ten moves, senior?"

Zhang Liu replied while pushing his hand forward. The opponent promised to give him ten moves, which meant that he wouldn't counterattack or defend himself but just dodge. He had already broken that promise, which was a hit to his pride.

"Shut up!"

Liu jumped back, evading a kick by a hair's width. His surprise attack had failed, his foe would probably be fully alert now and not give him a second chance. His follow up attack was a hastily created lesser lightning javelin. The technique that looked like a bolt of lightning flew forward only to get slapped to the side by Deng Cai. The earth elemental defensive technique proving quite sturdy and effective in blocking the lightning Qi attacks that this youth was proficient in.

"It looks like the young lord isn't impressed, the attacks of the challenger are proving to be ineffective!"

The Dark Palm Sect young master just sneered, shaking his hand that he smacked the lightning bolt away, the rocky armor quickly reforming around it.

"That tickles, is that all you are capable off?"

Zhang Liu was truly surprised, his opponent's defenses were nothing to scoff about. He was managing to make the defensive technique crack here and there, but he wasn't going through it with his regular attacks. For now, he jumped back and tried to reorganize his thoughts, hoping to think of a better strategy.

Before he could do that though, he felt that something was off. He could see his opponent move one of his hands upwards, his palm opened wide. Warning's started shooting off in his head prompting him to quickly use his movement technique. He dived to the side while Deng Cai clenched his palm together into a fist. The moment he did that the ground under Zhang Liu's feet shifted as if it was trying to encase him in sand and rubble.

The only thing that was caught was Liu's faint afterimage, the little aftershock not really doing anything to the lump of earth that was now in that place.

"You bugs are really good at evading... but how long can you keep this up?"

Deng Cai moved both his hands forward, his fingers started moving in a sort of random fashion. Suddenly pillars of sand burst through the rocky battle stage. They looked like elongated tentacles with a pointy tip on the end. The tips were different than the rest of the technique's 'body' it was composed of hard rock which had a razor-sharp edge to it.

There were multiple of those popping out from the ground and they quickly surrounded the white-haired Zhang Clan cultivator. He quickly utilized his lightning steps, his feet were shining in a blue light each step he took thunder was heard. His opponent didn't give him much time to react as the earth tendrils quickly sped towards their target.

Zhang Liu utilized his dodging skills to his fullest, the audience was on the edge of their seats as they saw the elongated sand tentacles shot out from various places. They all had one task, to pierce this white-haired youth. Flight was impossible for someone in this realm, so the earth-based attacks were proving effective as Liu was having trouble gathering his thoughts and was only able to dodge.

Luckily he was nimble, his cultivation technique was immortal graded and his Dao was a superior one. Running out of spiritual energy before his opponent wouldn't be something that would happen in this situation. Deng Cai's techniques were quite advanced and in the heavenly grade, still they paled compared to what Zhang Dong passed onto his disciple.

Seconds turned to minutes and the youth was still standing, the dark palm young master's face full of smugness slowly cracking as it switched to one of anger. No one had ever been able to keep up with him for this long while he was taking things more seriously. This technique that he was using was fierce and used up a lot of spiritual energy but his opponent didn't suffer any damage besides a couple of cuts to his robe.

'How can that trash keep up with my Sand Dragon Spears so well, he should be drained of his energies by now...'

Evading the hundreds of spear-like tendrils wasn't a simple task. The fast that Zhang Liu was still out there with minimal damage was a great achievement of its own. Yang Kai was just looking at the fight and he also was looking slightly ticked off. Why was his disciple still playing around with that insignificant worm?

"Cai, what are you doing, finish this already!"

The youth's master slammed his fist down, his aura exploding outwards which sent shivers down everyone's spine.

Deng Cai just looked at Zhang Liu that was still jumping about, his eyes bloodshot after he got called out by his own Master.

"How dare you make me lose face in front of my master, Die!"

Due to his masters egging on Deng Cai decided to charge into the fray. His barrage of sand spears continued while he himself utilized the previously used movement technique to gain momentum. He couldn't let his master get mad at him, he would be severely punished and maybe even deprived of cultivation resources.

This might have not been the best decision though. His ranged technique got sloppier as Liu noticed the amount of those blasted sand things decreasing to a more manageable number. He could see his enemy charging in like a mad bull, the rocky armor around him increasing in density while the ground cracked with each step he took.

'It's that technique.'

He already saw this move before, he knew that it was unwise to let the opponent gain momentum as the power of this skill increased with the rise in energy. So he did the opposite thing that Deng Cai was expected and bolted right at him.

"Fool, you are courting death!"

Cai sniggered at the idiot that was charging in his direction. He was very confident in his defensive capabilities, even more in them than he was in his offensive ones. No one of a similar realm had ever been able to damage his rock armor, he was assured that the moment the two clashed he would snap that Zhang clown in half.

People in the audience stood up ready to see the two clash. Most of them were of the opinion that the poor white-haired kid didn't stand a chance. They expected him to be pummeled into a ripe tomato after this exchange or maybe getting out of there with his evasion skill at most.

But then something strange happened. The youth started changing, his whole body started to glow in a deep blue light. Sparkling electricity was getting shoot out in various directions as the youth changed to something that looked more like an elemental being made from pure lightning energy.

This change was followed by a bright light that blinded most of the people looking at the exchange. A resounding boom of thunder quickly followed the flash of light along with a residual shockwave that activated the protective barrier that was protecting the people outside the battle stage.

The people took a few seconds to regain their senses. They all hurriedly looked to the spot that the clash happened only to gasp in surprise. There Zhang Liu stood, looking quite lofty while lightning energies and fluctuations of his superior Dao emanated from his form.

Deng Cai, on the other hand, was quite far away, right at the edge of the tournament platform. He was just sprawled out, his upper body leaning against the barrier that kept him and his opponent locked inside. He looked to be out cold, his left cheeked seamed to be caved in and he was missing some teeth. He was bleeding profusely from his mouth, the gem on his forehead looked to be cracked and his eyes were vacant.

The whole area went silent, the people couldn't even cheer out for the winner as they knew that the Dark Palm sect wouldn't take kindly to this. The only thing that could be faintly heard was the crackling of lightning and the gnashing of teeth that was coming from Yang Kai's VIP booth.

Chapter 153

The people were silent yet again, not from being shocked about Zhang Liu's one-hit knockout. They were looking up into the highest VIP booth where Yang Kai was sitting in. Everyone here knew by now that this man had a bad temper and was quite unreasonable. He wouldn't have set up this bet otherwise.

Everyone here just wanted to leave at this point. They weren't allowed though as various Dark Palm Sect members poured in and already surrounded the area around the colosseum to keep people from escaping. This was their turf and one of their important elders was in the middle of something. No one from them cared what this something was, they were just there to silence the people if push came to shove.

"GET UP!... I ORDER YOU TO GET UP!"

Yang Kai shouted out while looking at his disciple that wasn't looking all that handsome anymore. His face was caved in, a fist mark visible in that spot. The youth was out cold, his body was just twitching slightly from the abrupt ending that it had suffered.

"WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU ARE DOING, I WILL DISOWN YOU, YOU USELESS TRASH!"

The man continued berating his disciple, still hoping that there was a chance to save his good name. He didn't even care about the lost wager as much as losing face due to this whole thing. First, his disciple turned out to be weaker than some tiny Zhang Clan junior with no background whatsoever. Secondly, he would lose the bet if that disciple of his didn't wake up making him the master of a trash like that.

While this was going on Zhang Liu was slowly calming himself down. He had managed to land a perfectly placed counter on the man's face, but this was more luck than skill and he knew that. Deng Cai had miscalculated, thinking that his opponent was much weaker. This gave him the needed chance to use his lesser version of the Embodiment of the Thunder God to deliver a devastating finisher.

This technique was really difficult to use with his current cultivation, he could already feel his muscles twitching and his bones rattling from the strain he had suffered. He quickly breathed out while canceling the technique, his body that was covered by lightning turned back to its regular form. The youth looked a bit pale, but he was mostly okay but his battle potential was only at about 50% at this moment.

Something strange happened next. Zhang Liu was also taught his Master's aura detection techniques so he felt a strange shift. From the small gem that was embedded in Deng Cai's forehead a strange energy started to radiate.

Liu couldn't really see it, but he could feel energy escaping from the chipped gem. It was as if a fountain of water shot out into the sky into various directions and small orb-like will of whisps shoot out into the distance. The places they were going were varied, some flew back into the town as if they were searching for something or someone. Some of them just launched themselves into the distance, a long journey ahead of them.

Just a few moments after this transpired at a small house there was a certain woman. She was tired, her eyes looked to be red along with her nose. The woman looked at a certain child that was laying in a bed, the boy's was diagnosed with a strange sickness not too long ago and was fated to soon die. This wasn't the only child in this small room, the kids were just hollow husks.

She was holding one of the children's hands while trying not to cry. But all of a sudden she felt something, the boy's finger twitched just a tad. The woman wasn't a powerful cultivator so she didn't notice, but the stolen fragment of his soul had just returned and it was embedding itself back into her comatose child.

"Little Tei?"

She jumped up with vigor and surprise as she called out the name of her child. The little one gave out a grunt in response as color started returning to his cheeks. The same thing started happening to all the other kids around her, everyone jerked a bit as they began waking up from the nightmare.

"Honey come quick!...T-the kids...the kids are waking up!"

Zhang Liu was oblivious to the fact that thanks to him, the people that Deng Cai had sucked fragments of their souls away had begun recovering. Not everyone could be saved, depending on the state their current bodies were in. But the most recent victims of the soul-sucking were all starting to recover.

Suddenly the white-haired youth felt a powerful gaze on him. His whole body trembled as some villainous aura surrounded him, not letting him move a muscle. He was somehow able to gaze upwards with only his eyes and a slight neck movement. His eyes met with the furious Yang Kai that switched his targets now. He was glancing at the person that caused him to lose the bet.

The core formation expert also had a gem ingrained in his forehead and he could see the soul fragments that were freed. That was a lot of work that went down the drain, as he knew well how the mysterious gem was used. This was something that he didn't want to get discovered as this was clearly a technique used by demonic cultivators.

The soul fragments that were escaping couldn't be stopped now while the soul gem was broken. The problem wasn't that, but now there was the possibility of someone noticing that his disciple was using a demonic art.

Demonic and demon arts were characterized by a couple of things. There were mostly fashioned to increase the practitioner's cultivation by hurting others. There were various ways, using someone's blood, their flesh, or even their souls. A demonic art would suck your target dry and transfer part of their straight into the demonic cultivator. These arts were ghastly, cruel, and looked down upon by most people in this world.

This didn't keep certain people from cultivating them though. These techniques and skills were inhumane but they worked. It was far easier to absorb someone's body of work with the vampire-like demonic arts than spend millennia trying to better yourself on your own.

"Did anyone notice...should I silence them all...but first..."

Yang Kai narrowed his eyes and looked at the youth that defeated his disciple. If he decided to keep his word, he would have to declare this Zhang junior the victor and leave everyone alone. Still, he didn't feel like he had an obligation to do that, these trash cultivators from god know where didn't deserve any mercy, they had made a fool out of him and now they needed to pay the price.

"What is this, that young man clearly used some kind of demonic technique to win this fight, you all witnessed it!"

The man pointed out at Zhang Liu, the youth responded by looking up to the man shouting at him. The people in the area murmured among each other, not sure what the man was talking about. The person from the Zhang Clan had clearly won fair and square, the other person was also clearly the bad guy in this situation that was holding everyone hostage.

"I said... you all witnessed it, right?"

Yang Kai released his whole core formation great circle aura throughout the whole colosseum. The people that weren't really fighters felt the weight of the world on them as they knelt down.

"Yes, elder Kai is right, I saw that child eat some kind of pill before attacking, that was clearly against the rules!"

A person shouted out, he was wearing a regular Dark Palm sect robe. This was one of the people that was guarding the area not letting people out. Due to his words the people in the audience noticed what this overbearing sect wanted them to do. The people winced from the oppressive aura that the cultivators from this sect started radiating.

"Y-yes... I saw him swallow a pill too..."

"The Senior is right, he clearly cheated!"

"He should be disqualified!"

Soon random voices were heard in the region. Everyone was willing to throw this youth under the bus just to save themselves. The people here were mostly cultivators from other clans and smaller sects. They all clearly didn't want to have anything to do with this situation and with that dictatorial sect that was causing it. Some felt bad for the youth and the clan behind him, but it was better him than them.

Zhang Liu looked around the battle stage, the people were shouting at him. Their voices started out faint, but the longer he listened the louder it got. They even looked angry and started throwing food and other various things to the satisfaction of Yang Kai that was aiming for it. Zhang Jin and the others just gritted their teeth, the two Dark Palm sect elders moved closer and were keeping an eye on them, not letting them move a muscle.

"Hogwash!"

Huo Qiang declared while glancing at Yang Kai and all the people in the colosseum that were shouting out profanities.

"Watch your mouth!

One from the sect elders stepped over, his brows furrowed as he stared Qiang down.

"Young master clam down, you must not act!"

Huo Qiao stood up placing himself between Qiang and the Dark Palm sect member. He knew the big picture, if they acted now even their Patriarch wouldn't be able to do anything about it. The red-haired man just clenched his fists tightly, he then sat himself down still deliberating on the best action to take.

'What will that bastard do now...'

Zhang Jin thought to himself while looking at this helpless situation. The Feng women were to the side, they were just standing there not able to do anything besides watching things play out.

'The boy is in danger... what am I supposed to do...'

The old man didn't see this going anywhere positive. That Yang Kai was a typical tyrant that had to have his way. He wouldn't budge an inch if he set his mind to it and he had the backing of nascent soul cultivators behind him.

Yang Kai smirked, he just needed to threaten the people here a bit and they all took his side. This is how the world operated here, the strong were worshiped while the weak were tossed aside. No one in their right mind would side with the people opposing him, if he wanted he even could make everyone present here disappear from the face of the planet.

"Yes, that's right."

He swished his sleeve and glanced down at the judge that was just standing there.

"Don't you also think that he cheated and should be punished, honorable judge?"

The man started sweating, his palms already damp. There was no way that he could go against the young lord, but it made him look bad if he sided with him. In the end, he decided to take the hit to the face as he nodded.

"Y-yes, the young lord is right, the contestant named Zhang Liu clearly cheated... the match results are void."

The man glanced at Yang Kai that was nodding while the judge was speaking.

"For his punishment he should be removed..."

The man that the judge was staring at suddenly moved his palm upwards indicating that he should stop talking.

"Honorable judge I think you should leave the punishment of this villain to me, he did harm my disciple."

The judge nodded not wanting to argue with this nut case at all. The man clearly disowned his disciple a moment ago, now he was acting like a proper master who was trying to take his vengeance.

Yang Kai abruptly descended into the ring on his flying sword, the shield that was blocking Zhang Liu from leaving vanishing.

"You had your fun you little bug. You have only yourself to blame..."

Zhang Liu tried to move backwards but he couldn't. His feet felt like they were glued to the ground and he felt a heavy burden on his whole body. He tried circulating his cultivation but it was to no avail, this man was just too powerful for this youth that was only in the foundation establishment realm.

Yang Kai just stood there, tiny orbs that looked to be made from earth hovered in front of him. The moment the man pointed with his finger one of those orbs shot forward at an astonishing speed. The rudimentary attack rapidly struck the white-haired youth's thigh, penetrating it.

Zhang Liu gritted his teeth, blood gushed out but he was unwilling to show weakness even in this dire situation. This only made the Dark Palm sect Master angrier as he continued shooting the rock marbles at the defenseless youth. His shoulder, his other leg, his knee, and even his feet were the next targets as the young man was getting pelted with no remorse. If this continued for long, the youth would surely be dead...

Chapter 154

"Brother! Noo...!"

Zhang Xue shouted out while still being stuck in the waiting room, the rest of the juniors were still stuck there and being guarded by some scary sect uncles. She was able to see everything through one of the small windows but she could only watch as her brother was getting tortured.

"Junior sister, you mustn't!"

Zhang Tai was holding onto the young girl, not wanting her to charge out. He knew the stakes and that this lovely girl would be pulled into this bloody mess, probably losing her life. Liu's sister trashed about trying to wrestle herself free, but she was held back by her senior brother. He was also dismayed, he and Liu had their differences but it was still in good faith. He never wanted him to die, he was still part of the Zhang family, his death would be avenged.

"This one will be the last one..."

Yang Kai called out to Zhang Liu, the boy was already half dead but he didn't say even one word. He was barely standing, both his legs a bloody mess his bones broken in many areas and his flesh not looking better either. His eyes were staring daggers into his enemy's pair, he was defiant to the last breath.

"Those eyes... I don't like them... just die!"

Yang Kai snorted and produced a larger rock orb that he pointed at the youth's forehead. He took aim and flung it forward, if this attack went through the boy would die on the spot.

"Screw this!"

Zhang Jin shouted out as he finally jumped forward hoping to make it in time to save his grandson.

"Halt, what do you think you are doing! Grab him, don't let him interrupt the senior!"

The two cultivators that were in the VIP booth with Zhang Jin roared out. The alerted more of their companions to the elder that was diving towards the battle stage. Just as the two were about to grab him a sudden attack came from the side. There was a giant blazing fist flying towards an unlucky Dark Palm member, this older male not having enough time to react as he got clobbered right in the face.

"Young master, what are you doing?!"

Huo Qiao yelled in shock as his young master delivered the strike to the unsuspecting Dark Palm member. With this he had sealed their faith that was now tied to the other two clans that were here.

"Wait for what? My Huo clan won't stand for this, call the other elders over here this instant! We will assist the Zhang and Feng Clan in battle!"

"Well spoken, we'll assist you!"

Feng Liena quickly skipped over and delivered a devastating kick to the second core formation expert. She had a higher cultivation realm than the man and it was also of superior quality, so the man had no way of defending himself. He was sent flying backward and was embedded in the bricks of the structure the people were in.

Pandemonium soon broke out as people started clamoring to get out of this death trap. Dark Palm members started pouring in, alerted by the sudden retaliation and set on delivering their brand of justice to these backwater clans.

Zhang Jin didn't look back, but he could hear an explosion going off from behind him. He could hear various people screaming still, his eyes were glued to his grandson that was moments away from getting his forehead penetrated by Yang Kai's attack.

"I...I'm not going to make it..."

His face sunk as he was just too far away. There were more Dark Palm core formation cultivators standing in front of him and even some already moving up from behind. He clenched his fist tightly, his teeth gnashing as he activated a special item that was handed to him by the Zhang Patriarch.

"No, I must make it!"

A bright light surrounded his entire body and people could feel a spike of spiritual energy in the area. The core formation experts could faintly see the old man turning into a blob of light as he flew towards them. They reacted fast as they hurled their cultivation techniques at the enemy, to no avail as they got steamrolled by the old man and tossed aside like ragdolls.

"No good, raise the barrier output!"

Someone shouted out as the force field that was surrounding the ring with Zhang Liu and Yang Kai inside expanded in thickness. Everything was happening in a matter of seconds, but time was running out as the rock orb was already flying for the youth's head. The light around the man started to slowly fade but he was still charging forward, his fist on a collision course with that barrier.

'If I can just get through this!'

Zhang Jin forced all of his being into this punch. If he managed to destroy it in one blow, he would still have a chance in saving his grandson that was moments away from getting lobotomized. His fist finally connected with the shield, the dome of energy jolted around cracks formed around it as it resisted the heavy blow. Yet in the end, the barrier still managed to halt the old man's panicked advance only shattering after it was too late.

"N...NO!"

Zhang Jin's eyes were bloodshot as he saw the spinning orb just millimeters away from Zhang Liu's head. He had lost his momentum due to the barrier and needed to kick himself off the ground once more. He wouldn't be able to make it in time like this.

Zhang Liu was having a hard time keeping himself awake, he had lost a lot of blood and could feel that this was it. He could see flashes of his youth, they were mostly together with his younger sister and mother, their father spending most of his days cultivating to make their family proud. Right at the end he finally saw his master, Zhang Dong. The man was hard to read and he had a quirky personality that sometimes could be seen when his pokerface crumbled.

'Xue...Mother...Father...Master... I'm sorry...'

The youth looked at the haughty Dark Palm sect master, his gaze defiant till the end. The man was just standing there with that stupid grin on his face, the youth only hoping that his Master would avenge him afterward.

"Hah, nice try... but he dies!"

Yang Kai snickered as his attack was about to end his enemy's life. Yet, to everyone's bewilderment something baffling happened next. The moment the rocky orb made contact with the youth's forehead they saw a strange character appearing on his forehead. This character was the symbol for lightning, its appearance was followed by strong energy fluctuations that were even above the great circle of core formation.

Suddenly Zhang Liu's whole body found itself getting enveloped in an energy field. The moment the rock orb connected it evaporated into nothingness, this wasn't the end though. The barrier produced a massive shockwave that blasted outwardly in all directions catching Yang Kai off guard. A massive pillar of light shot up into the sky as it covered the whole football-sized field with itself.

The giant blast of energy was hard to miss, anyone that was currently fighting just stopped as they felt oppressive energy surging into their body.

"W-what is this light...GAHHHh..."

"Noo...."

People shouted out as they felt a strong jolt of electricity running through their bodies. The pillar of light expanded slightly further and then exploded with a loud thunderous blast. The screams came to an abrupt stop, the bright light quickly subsided to reveal most of the people down on the ground.

They were all alive but out cold, the blast that originated from Zhang Liu had taken out most of the people in the area. There was one more surprising fact, as anyone that was from the Zhang, Feng, or Huo clan and was in the vicinity of the blast remained unharmed. Most of the people in the colosseum were now incapacitated, but still some of the stronger core formation warriors remained.

"W-what happened, what was that pillar of light?"

Feng Liena called out while glancing to the center stage where the light beam originated from. She was standing next to her grandma and the two Huo clan members that were previously with her in the VIP booth that didn't exist anymore due to the fighting. They saw Zhang Jin charge into the ring and soon afterward the blast occurred.

"This spiritual essence belongs to him..."

Feng Liena said while glancing around her, some of the Dark Palm members were coming out and ready for battle.

"Yes... did the Zhang Patriarch place some protective Daoist magic on his disciple... but this scale..."

Feng Maling mumbled to herself while at the same time waving her staff and ready to battle some more.

"Most of them are down but this is not the end, let us grab all of the juniors and escape!"

Huo Qiang nodded while smacking his fists together, the brand new ruby gauntlets that he received from Zhang Dong began glowing red and releasing bright red flames.

"Leave those bastards to us, you go evacuate the kids!"

Huo Qiao sighed from the side but he also nodded, his hands glowing in a similar light as Qiang's did as he charged into battle alongside his long time young master. A Dark Palm member saw an angry-looking man with mutton chops, he quickly pulled out his communication jade.

"The clans are starting a revolt, send help to the colosseum!"

He poured his spiritual energy into the jade but something was wrong. The moment he did that sparks flew and it just exploded into many tiny pieces. He didn't have enough time to figure out what was wrong as he had to put up a block to cover his face. This wasn't the right choice as the moment the man delivered his infernal punch the Dark Palm cultivator could feel his forearms breaking.

The fighting resumed but at a smaller scale as the two Huo clansmen made a path for the Feng ladies. Back in the ring there was a certain large boulder. It was at least three meters tall and two meters thick and it had strange runes surrounding it. Opposite of it was a white-haired youth, he was gently hovering above the ground the lightning symbol still clearly visible on his forehead.

The large rock slowly crumbled into dust revealing an astonished Yang Kai. The man looked slightly disheveled but was mostly fine. He was looking at the youth that was hovering and giving of strong Qi fluctuations that were even above this Dark Palm Master.

"W-what is this, some kind of life-saving treasure from his Master or Clan?"

The man could see that the boy was already out cold, his eyes had rolled up into their eye sockets but he was still alive. The aura radiating was an amalgamation of lightning and holy Dao and it was even keeping the youth's wounds in check.

"Take this!"

Yang Kai didn't wait for an explanation and produced a large sand serpent that was at least five meters in length. It quickly flung itself at the floating youth, its rocky fangs going for the kill. To the man's dismay the moment his technique came in contact with the forcefield, the serpent blew up into a mass off debris.

"You think a weak life-saving technique like this will keep me away!"

Yang Kai roared as he rose up into the sky, he was standing on a huge snakehead that was made from a mix of sand and gravel. This new giant was several times larger than the previous serpent and gave of stronger core formation energy. The huge monster screeched as it opened its huge maw, an orb of energy appearing in front of it. This attack was very similar to the one the Zhang Cultivators used when they went into their staple attack formation. The difference being, that they were using water elements while this technique used the earthly ones.

Zhang Liu was a sitting duck, he was already out cold and unable to move. The life-saving technique would probably give out after some time if this continued, no one could tell how much punishment it could handle. The huge beam of spiritual energy exploded forward, would the boy survive this no one knew.

"Over my dead body you whelp!"

Suddenly someone appeared between the yellowish beam of light. The person was wearing a peculiar looking metallic armor over his body. The man looked quite big at least two meters and a half, the armor was pitch black. The armor looked like some edgy fantasy getup, there were spikes coming out of the shoulder blades and two large horns from the helmet. The torso part was quite pointy and triangular and the eyes glowed in an eerie green hue.

The person in the suit was holding on to a giant mace, the length of it was at least the same as the height of this man. The end was kind of spherical with curved spikes coming out of the 'head part'. The person inside this armor was Zhang Jin and he instantly swung this weapon against the incoming beam attack. Sparks flew in all directions but he managed to force the attack to the side, the resulting shockwave making the giant sand serpent tremble.

While these two clashed with each other, another scene was taking place in the Zhang Clan base that was Spirit Spring City.

Warning!!! Disciple Zhang Liu is in critical condition, life protective mark has been activated!

"The hell is going on, SOMEONE EXPLAIN THIS!"

The loud shout of an angry Zhang Clan Patriarch was heard throughout the whole city that made everyone in it drop to their knees. No one knew what their lovable Patriarch was angry about, it was very rare to see their leader acting like this so everyone was scared. The man in question was glaring at his two retainers Zhang Ya and Kuo that were face planting in fear on the ground.

"T-the truth of the matter is..."

Chapter 155

Earlier at Spirit Spring City in the dimensional regalia treasure:

The floating island in the void of the medallion had seen better days. The whole place was riddled with craters and rubble, even the buildings there were partially destroyed. The reason was the person who was in there and he was the one and only Nascent soul cultivator of the Zhang Clan.

Zhang Dong floated around while being in a seated position. His robe dangling downward due to gravity while he rubbed his chin. He had spent quite some time at just getting used to his new cultivation realm, he had long consolidated it and moved on to training in his techniques.

He didn't have the cash shop to go back to so he had to use his own understanding of the Dao to make progress. This wasn't a problem though, thanks to him having an astonishing amount of knowledge concerning the Dao of lightning. The upgrade to his cultivation technique also increased his understanding in the field of the holy elements so his healing arts would be more potent as well.

"Well, this place looks like shit... but with my current cultivation I can almost instantly repair it by infusing my Qi into the medallion."

He could barely get the pocket dimension to expand in size when he was still in the great circle of core formation. But things were different now, he was a Nascent soul grandmaster, a true behemoth in these lands. His true battle potential yet unknown as he hadn't faced a foe at the same level yet.

"Time to repair this place."

Matt knelt down and placed an open palm on the ground. The whole lump of earth that he was standing on was a part of this treasure. Thanks to this he could repair it without having to go outside to touch the medallion that was still in that protective room. His golden spiritual energy flowed into the earth beneath and he could already feel the fissures and craters sealing themselves back up again. In a matter of moments the scenery was back to normal, still not fully though.

"Well... I guess repairing the buildings would be too much to ask from this treasure..."

The structures like the large dorm looking building or the other ones that were built in this dimensional space couldn't be recreated like this. He would have to have his clansmen do the repairs manually. Some of the structures had collapsed due to several mistakes on his end. He had to watch his output a lot more now, a simple swing of his hand with a minimal amount of Qi in it could destroy the landscape around him.

"Haha, It's good to be the leader. Not like anyone can complain to me about destroying things here."

Matt was hesitant about his leadership position at first, but now he was slowly warming up to it. It was much easier to just gather points with the help of his clansmen. He just needed to shove them slightly in the right direction and they did most of the work for him. Not having to worry about a popular vote when it came to making new laws was also a nice bonus.

"I don't think I would be able to pass most of those new laws if we had things like a Senate or a House of Representatives..."

Matt stood up after getting the ground back into shape, though it looked slightly barren as only the basic plant life recovered like grass.

"Benevolent Dictator Zhang Dong... has a nice ring to it..."

He laughed while walking towards the dorm house where the platoons had stayed at when they were training.

"Still, I'll have to look into that when things settle down..."

He was someone from modern times and his country was also a democracy. So he leaned in that direction, but in this world ruled by strength it would be hard to propose that way of thinking. Getting people to follow elected officials that weren't actually stronger than them in battle would be a strenuous task.

"Well I got most of the techniques and the Qi flow down now, this new enhanced spiritual sense is quite neat as well."

"I should probably craft that dagger now, wonder how much stronger I will become when my body also reaches the nascent soul level...also what's above a golden body... platinum?"

Matt rubbed his chin, thinking that that metal looked silver and would be just backtracking. Though a silver sheen was nice as well, maybe he would get a pure shiny chrome body that blinded his enemies.

"I will ride eternal, shiny and chrome...or something like that?"

No one was there to appreciate his bad monologue, so he moved on and was ready to enter his crafting abode to move on with the crafting. He wanted to take his attempt at the heaven grade weapon slowly, this was mostly the reason why he spent close to a week in training his Qi control. This skill was paramount to crafting weapons as making a slight mistake while infusing the metals and materials with his Qi could turn a treasure into junk.

Warning!!! Disciple Zhang Liu's body condition is rapidly decreasing! Warning!!!

Suddenly he heard a siren that was followed by a big red pop up window right in front of his face. It said that Zhang Liu was in a dire situation, he didn't know what was going on nor that his system even had this kind of function.

"What the hell ..."

He quickly tapped that prompt, the window quickly switched to Zhang Liu's disciple window and he could even see his photo in the top left corner. On the right side, there was a miniature version of a human body, it looked like one that you found in a medical book. Normally this figure was green, the colors changed depending on the amount of damage his disciples suffered.

"W-what is this!"

His eyes bulged as he knew how this disciple window should look like. He had trained with the kids before and they had suffered some minor injuries. The colors shifted from green to blue, yellow, orange, red, and then black. Black was the color of death and he never saw his disciples ever getting anything below the yellow color. To his astonishment, most of the diagram was red or orange and there were places turning red at the same time as he was looking at it.

"What's happening in that city? did they run into some demonic beasts on the way home?... what's going on?"

Matt rattled his brain, he didn't know what was going on. His grandpa and his retainers assured him that this was just a friendly get together for the clans. There shouldn't be any problems along the way as it was a safe zone, Zhang Jin even had that prototype treasure that he made to help him out if something went wrong.

"I must call them!"

Matt hastily left the dimensional regalia and appeared next to the medallion in the spacious empty room. The guards were startled as they couldn't even give him a salute, their Patriarch just zoomed past them and flew up the stairs leaving an afterimage behind.

Warning!!! Disciple Zhang Liu's life is in danger, killing intent detected, should the system activate the protection mark? Warning!!!

Matt stopped after another popup window showed up. He remembered that he spent some points on his two disciples when he was examining his system more throughout. He remembered that this was something high-level masters did for their pupils, so he spent a good amount of his points in his system on that mark. He almost thought that it was a rip-off, but now it could be Liu's only chance of survival.

With the pinpoint precision of a seasoned gamer he poked the 'yes' button as fast as his nascent soul cultivation allowed him to do. This of course didn't get unnoticed, a simple finger poke from someone this strong produced a giant shockwave blast that turned the stairs that he was standing into rubble.

Warning!!! Disciple Zhang Liu is in critical condition, life protective mark has been activated! Trying to stabilize, please wait!

This explosion didn't get unnoticed, guards poured in like bees to honey as they thought that their main building was getting attacked. The moment they got there though, they saw their Patriarch rising out from the rubble a strange expression on his face. He looked at them with a stern expression that made them stand up straight, their rear ends clenched.

"Where are Ya and Kuo, bring them here... do it now!"

The Zhang soldiers didn't need to hear the order twice as they bolted in various directions. While they were searching for Zhang Dong's two retainers, he himself pulled out a communication jade and tried contacting his grandpa that should be there with Liu.

"Nothing... I'm not getting through..."

He didn't know that the systems protective mark had fried all communication devices in the area, even the Dark Palm Sect headquarters in Jade Grass City had gone dark. This was a blessing in disguise as they wouldn't be able to call for backup for now.

"What's happening there?"

He removed himself from the ruined structure and was now in the main hall of the Zhang Clan compound. He wanted to just bold for that city right here right now, but he was holding himself back. He needed more information, his two retainers needed to fill him in before he made his way here. He had already experienced situations into which he went without any sort of plan or idea of the foe he was facing.

"Good, his vital signs are stabilizing..."

While moving towards the office that Kuo should be in, while at it he also kept looking at Zhang Liu's disciple window in his system. He noticed that this mark that he spent good spirit points on was actually keeping this boy alive. Previously dark red areas were turning brighter as time passed, which indicated a chance of survival.

"Zhang Kuo greets the Patriarch."

"Zhang Ya greets the Patriarch."

He moved his head away from the status window as his two retainers finally showed up. They were all standing out in the open as they had met halfway. There were other Zhang family members around them along with the guards that had called these two over.

"I will make this short you two, was it the Dao festival? Tell me, were there some dangers in the city it was being held?"

The two looked at each other after they stopped bowing, then Kuo replied to the question Zhang Dong said.

"Nothing in particular Patriarch, the festival should be ending in a couple of days, we are expecting the grand elder to return within the week."

Matt raised his brow, he could tell, the two were lying. Thanks to his enhanced spiritual sense he could tell this, what Kuo said was partially right but he was withholding information. Why the man was doing it was unknown to Matt, he had no time to spend on these games though.

He truthfully didn't have the slightest idea that the Dark Palm sect was located in Jade Gras City. There were far too many cities and towns with Spirit, Jade, Phoenix, or Dragon in their names, for him to remember which one was which. His two retainers were still keeping up with the request of the grand elder Zhang Jin, so they were just following orders.

"Is that so..."

The people in the room twitched the moment Zhang Dong said those words. They felt an oppressive aura coming from their Patriarch. This was something very uncharacteristic of their leader, everyone was surprised as they went down to their knees, gasping for air.

"P-patriarch appease y-your anger..."

"Appease my anger? My disciple is on his death bed and you still claim that everything is alright?"

"The hell is going on, SOMEONE EXPLAIN THIS! I know that you two are withholding information from me!"

Zhang Dong pointed his finger at his two retainers accusingly, his aura washing over them which made them tremble in their boots. The cat was out of the bag at this point, so the two didn't have any reason to lie anymore. Their leader already knowing that something was fishy.

"T-the truth of the matter is..."

"Jade Grass City is... part of the Dark Palm Sect..."

Matt stepped back, the pressure around his people subsiding the moment the truth was revealed.

"The grand elder didn't want to worry you, Patriarch..."

The two had their faces mushed into the ground and couldn't really see if Zhang Dong was still mad or not. They were just following orders from their perspective but this could have been seen as undermining the leader's authority. From the Patriarch's point of view this could be considered treason and he could even have them killed.

"The Dark Palm Sect again... damn you gramps..."

Matt mumbled to himself while glaring at the two people at his feet. He was ready to take off here and there, before he could though he was interrupted by a female voice.

"Your disciple? did something happen to little Xue and Liu?"

This was Zhang Jie, the mother of his two pupils. She had a strained expression on her face, not really sure if she heard it right. Matt looked at his cousin and placed his arm on her shoulder, he gave her a solemn look before replying.

"Don't worry, I'll bring them back."

He then looked at Zhang Ya and Jin as he spoke out.

"I'll deal with you later."

He was already putting the coordinates of Jade Grass City into his system. Before Zhang Jie could reply he was already floating in mid-air, his body flashing in a golden light. The spiritual energy spiked in the surrounding that caused everyone to gasp out, was this really their Patriarch? This man was a lot stronger than they remembered him to be, they didn't get much time to gawk though. The man's body turned into a being of lightning and blasted straight upwards, the people in the vicinity were flung to the side just from his takeoff.

The people outside the Zhang Clan headquarters could see a bright beam of light shooting into the clouds followed by a thunderous boom. Everyone looked up into the sky only to see a thick bolt of lightning shooting from the cloud that was directly above them. Some of them could have sworn that they saw a person inside that huge lightning bolt.

Chapter 156

People murmured among each other. Everyone clearly heard the city leader's voice before the large beam of light took off. They weren't sure what was happening, but the city owner probably had something to do with it. The clouds parted and they saw a giant golden lightning bolt firing off into the distance and golden lightning was something that the Zhang Patriarch was known for.

While the commoners gossiped with each other the Zhang Clan members were left stupefied.

"D-did the Patriarch just fly without his sword?"

"What was that strange phenomenon?"

"Did he... reach the Nascent Soul realm?"

The Zhang clan members that witnessed their leader taking off from this spot looked at the large hole in the ceiling. They all gulped wondering if Zhang Dong had actually taken that step forward that no one from their clan had ever done before.

"This complicates things."

Zhang Kuo stood up while looking in the distance where Zhang Dong had taken off. He knew what the Dark Palm sect would do if they saw their leader who had reached the nascent soul level. The other problem was that something had happened during the Dao festival, it didn't take this man long to put one and one together to figure this out.

"We must call Senior Zhi."

Zhang Kuo looked to a person on the side, this was someone that worked for him.

"Give out a decree, everyone is to return to Spirit Spring City we need to activate the grand formation!"

"Also prepare the battleships, we need to aid the Patriarch!"

The person bowed and quickly moved out to carry out the orders, the people that were gathered there were still perplexed by the whole situation.

"I'm leaving on the first ship!"

Zhang Jie proclaimed while running to get her battle robe ready, she knew that her children were in trouble once again and she didn't want to wait here twiddling her thumbs. The place got louder as the senior members from the clan started running around like headless chickens. This situation looked even direr than the one where they were ordered to visit that secret ground, it seemed that someone from their clan had offended the big overlord that was the Dark Palm Sect.

Zhang Zhi got the call first, the man didn't take long to bolt on his flying sword towards Spirit Spring City. His true destination was the city where the Dao festival was held, but first he wanted to meet up with the Zhang force that would be heading there.

His wife being a Feng Clan member quickly called up her old contacts in the female-run family. Their side didn't have any info on anything, no communications were going through. Their side was skeptical about the whole thing and decided to wait it out, but to be sure they also started gathering their most powerful experts to aid their Matriarch.

Word also reached the Huo clan that began their own preparations as well. The three clans had made an agreement to share information with each other. Everyone was gathering up their forces, but they knew better than to just barge into Jade Grass City. They didn't like their chances when going against the Dark Palm Sect, so for now they would be preparing their forces and wait for more information to arrive.

The two clans didn't like the look of this. If a conflict arose they would probably have to abandon those young masters that were sent to that tournament. There was no realistic way of going against a sect with Nascent Soul cultivators. The congregation of their forces was more a formality than a show of force, done more to not make them look weak in this kind situation.

Out in the distance, there was a sudden rumble. A large beast at the core formation level was munching on some delicious meat of its prey. The monster was the apex predator of this area, but even it shivered uncontrollably as it felt a massive spike in spiritual energy. The creature had never felt an astonishing amount of power like this before, the only thing it could do is prostrate itself towards the incoming being.

The thing that was making this meat-eater afraid was a person that was rapidly approaching. This person was hard to spot as he was surrounded by golden lights, lightning bolts firing off and thunder clapping everywhere. Everything in the vicinity either passed out or prostrated itself like the beast.

'God damn, I'm so much faster now... but that blasted city is too far away... it will take me an hour to get there...'

This was an angry-looking Zhang Dong, he looked at the zooming scenery as he was rapidly flying towards Jade Grass City. It would have taken him one or two days to get there on his flying sword when he was at core formation. He was several times faster now, but this wasn't enough to get there in under an hour.

'I hope they can hold up until I arrive. Don't you die on me...'

Matt pushed his cultivation to its limits as he charged forward, he was feeling a myriad of emotions. Worry about his disciple and his new family that could very well die soon. Anger about the fact that the Dark Palm Sect was aiming for them and even sadness due to his grandpa withholding information from him.

'Am I so unreliable?'

He tried tossing these questions to the back of his mind for now. The battle ahead was more important, he also had to think about what he should do after it's all done. The Dark Palm Sect would be knocking on their doors if he trashes their city, even more, when they realize that he reached the nascent soul level.

'Should I make a contract with them?'

He had done his research and wanted to avoid that option. The eradication of his clan could probably be avoided if he took one of those binding contracts. If he did that though, he would be nothing more than a slave of that Dark Palm sect. They apparently used some strange soul binding pacts that were more or less slave contracts. The person that he would be bound to could order him to do anything and if he refused his soul could be destroyed.

'Not a very good deal... but probably the least bloody conclusion.'

He would probably have to work as some kind of sect enforcer or bodyguard for the next snotty sect master. Still everyone wouldn't need to fight and their clan would fall under the protection of the powerful sect. Could he trust his life to some murder hobos though? He could very well end up betrayed and dead after even signing on the dotted line. He wouldn't be able to do anything if that sect decided to do something to his clan, they were just too untrustworthy.

'The other option is to fight it out... but can I beat all of their old nascent soul farts myself?'

That was the big question, he felt like he shouldn't have problems with someone at the early stage. If they were as strong as that Pride demon he faced, he wouldn't have a problem. Was that the standard for the early stage or was it more? maybe it was even less, he needed more battle experience.

'Can the system help me? I don't have many points and no shop to buy any op items... the only thing I can spend my points now is to...'

He had one idea in his mind, but first he needed more spirit points and many more of them. He was only flying for a couple of minutes now, the indicator on the map showed him getting closer slowly it would take some time for him to get there. Meanwhile at Jade Grass City another battle was unfolding.

Zhang Jin's large obsidian spiky mace radiated with oppressive green energy. The old man brought it down on his enemy, his opponent was a giant rocky serpent that was at least forty meters in length. Its head was gigantic compared to the armored man, but even it couldn't withstand the hit from that weapon.

"BOOMMM"

The giant rock serpent's head exploded into a million pieces and its body was flung back into the audience seats, luckily the people had already recovered from the lightning blast and fled the scene. The whole place was riddled with craters and holes, the water that was outside the ring was dirty from all the sand that had gotten into it.

The uncharacteristic black knight with the giant mace landed on the ground, the added weight from the suit that Zhang Jin was wearing made the ground shake and shatter from the impact. An angry Yang Kai was seen not far away, he had suffered another setback and his technique was canceled after his large rock serpent got his by that strange mace.

"What is this, how can you be this strong? What's with that strange treasure, where did you get that!"

Yang Kai roared while pelting the man in black armor with a barrage of rock orbs, the amount was staggering which made it look like machine gunfire. To this man's dismay his opponent didn't even bother to dodge this onslaught, the condensed rock orbs just shattered into many tiny pieces after hitting the armor.

"Are you rebelling against the Dark Palm Sect? Do you idiots think that you have a chance? You will all die as an example!"

Zhang Jin's opponent wasn't having any of this. How could he, a prominent Dark Palm Sect master who was also a one in a billion genius be losing to some old fart from god knows where? Would he have to use some of the forbidden arts to fight off this trash of an opponent?

While Yang Kai was having a crisis, Zhang Jin was shocked by how well this so-called 'Power Suit: Iron Kaiser' that his grandson had made for him was working. He wasn't sure why Zhang Dong gave it such a name but the product was working out well.

This was one of the latest creations of the Zhang Patriarch. He had modeled it to work like an Iron man suit of armor and it was running on demonic beast cores. This was also the reason why this black suit of armor had that gloomy greenish glow to it. On the inside there were many beast cores embedded into various core parts, like the shoulders and the chest plate.

The treasure was mostly made from beast cores in the great circle and late stages of core formation. It worked like described, it was a power suit that the user could wear. It boosted the wearer's offensive and defensive capabilities allowing them to battle people at the top level of core formation. The only downside of this item was the quick usage of spiritual energy, the person couldn't really use it for more than an hour or even less depending on the power usage.

Iron Kaiser at 74% energy

Zhang Jin heard a robotic voice, something akin to text to speech. This thing even came equipped with a basic Ai, but it wasn't really much it only alerted the user of how much juice the suit had left, or when it suffered critical damage. This product was still in the prototype stages and this Zhang Grand elder only received it for testing purposes.

"Rebelling? What nonsense are you spouting? Did you want us to just roll over and die instead? I'll take you down with me, you damn bastard!"

The elder roared out, the metallic armor making his voice sound a lot more ominous. He charged forward, his whole body covered in deep green energy that shifted to the top of the mace. He swiftly swung it downwards producing a massive shockwave of Qi that flew at Yang Kai who could only put up layers upon layers of defensive techniques to barely block the overwhelming strike.

"Don't get ahead of yourself you old fart! You think you are the only one with secrets here?"

The Dark Palm member jumped high into the air, his forehead glowing. The gem that was embedded into it started spewing up things that looked like globs of energy. These energy masses had some strange faces flickering in and out of them, going through various expressions but mostly showing fear or anger.

Zhang Jin looked up and took a step back, this was clearly a demonic cultivator's technique, but was this Dark Palm Sect a demonic sect?

"Are those souls?... what kind of dastardly demonic art is that?"

Chapter 157

Unable to determinate objects characteristic, need more data.

Zhang Jin's power suit's mechanical voice proclaimed after the question was asked. This AI was very basic so it had no advanced appraisal system like the one Zhang Dong had himself. The old man still couldn't get used to this strange treasure, was there a person trapped in it, or was it some kind of soul that was talking to him?

Yang Kai was glowing in a reddish light, a copious number of souls shoot out from his gem and started surrounding his own body. The souls started screaming out and pouring into the man's orifices like his mouth and ears as if they wanted to be one with him. Their high pitched shrieks were even heard by people outside the arena, the loud sound causing them to tremble in fear.

This wasn't for the faint of heart as Yang Kai's body started bulging out, his muscles expanded and his veins were popping out as if he was ready to explode. The more souls that he absorbed the paler his face got, this wasn't all though as suddenly his body started to turn transparent. It was as if his body was flickering in and out of existence as it switched between the material and the immaterial plane.

"W-what is that technique..."

Zhang Jin shouted out while already swinging his large mace weapon forward, he produced another ranged strike of green energy that flew upwards at the man that was looking more like a ghost than a person now. The mass of Spiritual energy charged forward right at the enemy, but the moment it collided with his body it just past through it.

"How is that possible?"

Zhang Jin's attack was ineffective, it had gone through the opponent that just phased through it. Did he turn into a ghost that wasn't affected by regular spiritual attacks?

"Hahaha, no one who has seen this technique has come out alive! Behold my Phantasm Spectral Body of the Nine Hells!"

"None of your feeble techniques will work on me, but I can still harvest your soul just fine. After I'm through with you, I'll be sure to impale your body on a pole for everyone to see!"

Yang Kai cackled as he descended rapidly, his fingers expanded and turned into sickle blades. His mouth expanded as well, making him look quite grotesque, his high pitched screams being heard throughout the destroyed colosseum.

"I'll be sure to place you right next to this little bastard that spoiled my plans! You all should just die like the trashes you are!"

Zhang Jin wasn't the only person fighting around here, but the others were busy with their own battles. There were far more Dark Palm Sect elders ready to keep Huo Qiang and Feng Liena busy.

The first thing Zhang Jin did was to back off, not sure what would happen if he got scratched by those long looking fingers. While he was jumping back he made sure to kick a large rock at his opponent. Yang Kai didn't even flinch as the large boulder just flew through him not impeding his approach at all. This confirmed the old man's theory, this technique really did make the man intangible.

The two started playing a game of cat and mouse. Zhang Jin was skillfully dodging the strikes not sure about the result if he got touched by this strange ghost art. He tried attacking with some ranged attacks, but just like the previous ones they only went through the attacker without damaging him at all.

"Stop running you old bastard!"

Yang Kai was slowly losing his cool, this technique was taking a lot from him but he wasn't getting anywhere with this. The old fart was just running and he couldn't keep this up forever, he knew that he would run out of souls eventually and suffer a powerful backlash if this continued for too long. The clunky looking suit of armor that he was wearing didn't apparently make him slower in any way.

While he was thinking about his next move, he saw someone out of the corner of his eye. It was Zhang Liu that was still floating up in the air, the barrier that was covering his body was still there but could it hold against his attack?

"If you keep running... then the boy dies!"

He quickly changed his strategy and turned to the side, his body expanding in height as he looked more like a monster than human now. Zhang Jin was taken aback and quickly bolted for where his grandson was floating in the air. He had no plan whatsoever but he couldn't let this villain harm his boy.

"No, stop you fiend!"

The monster that looked like a cross of a banshee and slender man charged forward. He wasn't really aiming for the youth though, he just wanted the old fart to try defending him. When he did, he would quickly strike and perform a devastating attack to his soul.

This Phantasm Spectral Body of the Nine Hells was a special technique, it didn't really make Yang Kai stronger but it allowed him to shrug off all sorts of attacks. He was actually slightly weaker in this form, but he couldn't be harmed. His attacks didn't affect his opponent's real-life body but instead targeted their soul. It was very effective against anyone below the nascent soul level as their souls weren't strong and mostly without any protection. There were very few items and very rare arts that could apply damage to this demonic ghost technique.

Zhang Jin arrived in front of Zhang Liu first, his armor was already enhancing his body above Yang Kai's level so this wasn't a difficult feat. The only thing that he could do was to gather up more energy and swing the person-sized mace at his opponent, maybe if he gave it his all it would deliver a devastating blow.

Yang Kai on the other side sniggered and increased his speed. He would wait for that idiot elder to do a big swing and then he would devour his soul whole. This man was quite the connoisseur that liked feeding on aged souls the most. This was also the reason that he was going after Feng Maling that had quite a delicious soul to his taste.

The ground rumbled and people in the vicinity could feel a massive amount of spiritual energy filling the area. Everyone that was fighting in the vicinity quickly jumped back, the Feng and Huo clan members followed suit.

The two people clashed, the person that turned into a monster ghost expanded even further his fingers looked like large blades that were on a collision course with the black knight's body. The person in the dark suit of armor swung his weapon in a last-ditch effort, his power suits energy reserves dropped to twenty-five percent in an instant as he infused most of it into this swing.

The resulting energy wave blasted a giant fissure into the ground that expanded forwards and to the sides making it look like the earth was parting. The surge of energy washed over Yang Kai's body but still his ghastly figure didn't feel any pain or pressure from this massive attack that carried over into the town behind him.

"You Fool! Your soul is mine!"

The large ghostly sickle like hand moved towards the old man's chest. He had made a large swing and was now unable to dodge or put his guard up. The pointy fingers nimbly cut the air towards the enemy, not going for the flesh but for what was inside of that meat suit.

"Clang..."

A strange thing happened though, the long digits instead of penetrating inside just bounced off the dark armor. Yang Kai stopped dead in his tracks, what was this thing made of that his ethereal body couldn't even penetrate was this some kind of rare spirit metal? He didn't have much time to think as he felt something hard slam him to the side, this was the same mace that Zhang Jin was carrying.

"Huh... the Qi attacks can't damage that art... but the material that this treasure is made of can?"

Zhang Jin was being super cautious when fighting this demonic cultivator that he didn't even test out if this dark metal had any special qualities. He didn't think that a simple melee attack would be better than using grand Qi attacks that could devastate the area.

Yang Kai suffered a large hit, his body started shrinking and flickering on and off as if his ghost technique was running out of juice. The Zhang elder didn't give his enemy time to recover though, he was quickly on him like white on rice. What ensued was a one-sided beatdown, the dark knight's mace pounded the Dark Palm Sect's master into the ground while loud thumping noises echoed.

"For the Zhang Clan, take this!"

No one expected this one-sided reversal, even the other elders from the Dark Palm Sect weren't able to aid their leader who was getting turned into minced meat. Zhang Jin was without mercy, he quickly pummeled Yang Kai into the ground the man was now twitching while having a hard time uttering even a single word.

"That Yang Kai lost, just like that?... was this Zhang Jin always this strong?"

Huo Qiao muttered from the side while holding another man from behind by the neck and choking the ever-loving crap out of him.

"No, it must be that strange treasure he is wearing... it made him far stronger. Young master, we should quickly withdraw while we have the chance!"

The bodyguard alerted his young master, with Zhang Jin's victory the strongest opponent was out of the way. What done was done, the only way out of this was to flee. After that they would have to think about the next step to take, but for now getting out of this city was the first thing they all had to do.

Huo Qiang was just smacking a Dark Palm Sect member around as he heard Qiao. This prompted him to look inside the ring, his eyes sparkling slightly while looking at the large obsidian suit of armor. He wasn't sure why, but he really liked the way that thing looked, if only he could get one in red was what he was thinking.

Feng Liena and Maling had rounded up the junior members from the three clans by this time. Thanks to the strides forward that all three clans had made during the two years, they were somehow able to fight off these sect elders. The EMP like attack that turned the communication jades into scrap has given them an advantage for now, but they knew that after that last blast that Zhang Jin produced everyone in the city would be alerted.

"En, we should retreat for now at the harbor, all of our clan members are gathered here. We can use the failure of the communication jades to our advantage and evade further combat!"

Feng Mailing chimed in, she then looked at the old man in the edgy black suit still surprised about how strong he was in that thing.

"You old fart, grab your clan member and let's go we don't have time!"

Zhang Jin looked to the side and nodded, he then glared down at the injured body of Yang Kai. He was battered and bruised but still alive, he just needed one good smack to finish the job.

'Can't let this guy live!'

He knew what to do as he moved his large mace above his head, aiming to cave in the Dark Palm Sect master's head with one last large swing. Letting a petty man like this live any further would be a travesty, how many people had he slain during his life already? There was no pity for people like this in this old man's heart. He poured in some spiritual energy into this last swing, the greenish glow on the mace materialized as he began swinging down for the killing blow.

The large weapon headed on a collision course with that man's head, if it connected it would turn into an overripe tomato as it burst. But just a couple of centimeters away from the target the swing came to a stop. Zhang Jin's muscles bulged as he felt like something was holding him captive. He couldn't move a muscle, adding more Qi to his armor didn't solve this problem either. The green energy dispersed into nothingness as if sucked away into the ether by something.

Zhang Jin wasn't the only person that couldn't move, every person from the Triforce alliance felt massive pressure being applied to their very being. The junior members collapsed onto the ground without any warning, the core formation elders managed to resist somewhat but still, they found themselves kneeling.

"What is this? You dare attack the Dark Palm Sect in front of this Wu Ming?"

Chapter 158

Wu Ming took his time as he floated up in the air looking down at everyone that was in the mostly destroyed colosseum. The architecture of the area was trashed and it looked like a tornado and an earthquake went through this place.

There weren't many people left here, there were several Dark Palm members that were mostly beaten back by the triforce alliance elders. Besides that we have the group of junior members from the three clans that were now down on the ground, their ability to stand being taken away all thanks to the nascent soul grandmaster above them.

The man in question didn't say much, he hovered above ground and took his time to examine the situation. He looked at Yang Kai that was a bloody mess on the ground, the mace of the man in the strange black suit of armor had stopped. It wasn't moving a muscle as Wu Ming was locking him in place.

He then gazed to the side, Yang Kai's disciple Deng Cai's hand was sticking out from some rubble. His own master had forgotten about him and didn't even get him to safety before he began his battle with Zhang Jin. Not like Elder Ming cared about this useless youth, if he got abandoned by his own Master then there had to be a reason for it.

It took him only a couple of seconds to get the gist of it. His allies were mostly beaten and bruised and someone was about to murder a prominent senior member from the sect. Even though he didn't like the man with the gem in his forehead, he still had to abide by the rules. There was also the part about him being the son of the sect leader, he couldn't just let him die here unless he wanted to face his wrath.

"Truly a pitiful performance, I expected more from the son of that man..."

Elder Ming descended slowly, hands behind his back. He arrived between Zhang Jin and the beaten up Yang Kai. The Zhang Clan member was still infusing his Qi into his body as he was trying to get away. He could only twitch slightly, his whole body felt like it was stuck in a block of iron a constant pressure keeping him from budging.

"And this is... interesting..."

Wu Ming poked Zhang Jin's helmet as he looked over the armor he was wearing. The man liked to collect treasures, this was also one of the reasons why he liked attending auctions in various places.

"Mysterious craftsmanship, this was made by a true master. Shame that it's still only an earth grade treasure, even though it's a pinnacle one."

Zhang Jin couldn't do much as the man picked up his mace and started looking over the craftsmanship. Apparently this man didn't think anyone around here was worth his while as he was keeping them plastered to the ground. Even the bloodied Yang Kai wasn't getting much of a reaction from this elder Ming.

"Mmm yes..."

The old man with the salt and pepper hair shook his head after hearing Yang Kai cough out loud. He took out a pill from his spatial ring and placed made it float into the downed man's mouth. The medicinal effects were quite astonishing as the wounds were closing at a rapid pace.

"That was a heaven grade pill, they aren't cheap."

The battered and bruised man felt air going back into his previously collapsed lungs. He vomited out some blood and quickly took out various other medicinal pills to aid his recovery.

"Y-yes Elder Ming, I'll be sure to reimburse you for this favor!"

He wobbled back to his feet, he looked like a person that had tomato juice dumped on him. His clothes were soaked along with his face. Yang Kai glared at the man in the obsidian armor suit that was still unmoving and getting held back by the elder.

"This is an embarrassment for the entire sect, how could you let some third rate clans bring you to this state?"

The man was surprised, almost everyone from his sect had been defeated by these cultivators here. He wanted to figure out what could have made them do this but he was a bit preoccupied with looking at Zhang Jin and Zhang Liu. The youth was still floating in the air giving off some strange spiritual fluctuations that this elder was curious about.

"What kind of Dao is that?"

He took his eyes off the man in the metal suit and floated forward slowly. The other people that were allied with him were slowly recovering while eating healing pills. They didn't move a muscle though, they needed to wait for this scary nascent soul elder of theirs to be done with his research. It would be rude to act without getting ordered and no one was willing to risk offending a person in the nascent soul stage.

Wu Ming approached Zhang Liu, his finger moving towards the glowing shield as he gave it a poke. He felt a repelling force against his digit, so he increased the pressure. The glowing shield buckled under the increased strain but was holding for now. The man even felt a discharge of Qi getting sent back towards his body, this was probably some kind of defensive mechanism.

"Interesting...really pure spiritual energy... still lacking though..."

The mark that was placed by the system was at the very top of core formation, it was even edging into the half step nascent soul level. Yet it wasn't quite there yet. Anything below the nascent soul realm wouldn't pique this man's interest. The Dao that was flowing out of this mark was interesting but it wasn't something that this man could use for himself.

"E-elder Ming, please let me readdress my grievances!"

The man looked back to Yang Kai, the man had seen better days. He was just standing there after having somehow recovered, his gaze on the man in the black suit of armor. Wu Ming knew what he wanted and didn't really care, the technique that was suspending the boy in mid-air was more interesting than what Yang Kai was up to. Still, the order needed to be kept and these people did go against the sect an example had to be made of them.

"Your grievances you say..."

He looked to Zhang Jin who was being silent, not out of his own choice. The suppressing aura forced him to submit and he was even having a hard time breathing.

"Yes, we can't have a blemish like this be kept around."

Elder Ming turned away from Zhang Liu and looked at the black armor. He stretched out his finger and did a slight motion forward as if he was flicking someone's nose. A large shift in Qi energy was felt by the masters in the area, they watched on as the black metal that Zhang Jin was covered started rattling around.

"Hoh, quite the sturdy treasure...but..."

The old man flicked his finger forward causing the black armor to shake even more. Soon it started bending and showing cracks before it collapsed and shattered into many pieces. Zhang Jin's terrified expression was seen after he got disrobed by the Nascent Soul master that just needed two flicks with his finger to do so.

"There, I think you should be able to handle the rest on your own now."

Wu Ming turned back towards the youth once more, but before walking away he gave out an order.

"Ah yes, you will gather some elders from the sect and organize a cleansing. We must not let other sects think that we are weak, this is your mess so before you resolve it don't even think about going back to the main sect!"

The Nascent Soul elder didn't care that Yang Kai had backing back at the inner sect, he was still of higher status than the younger man. This whole mess was started by him and he was going to end it. He would do so by pulling out the problem by the root, which was killing anyone that was involved.

"Yes Elder Ming, this Yang Kai will not rest until every single one of these scoundrels is dead!"

Ming went back to poking the barrier and applying more pressure wondering how resistant it was to his Qi. He wasn't expecting much from it though as it was already buckling under the pressure. Truthfully he just wanted to get out of here, the auction was over and the only reason he was still here was that he noticed the huge explosion that was caused by Zhang Jin's attack. He wanted to give this brat Yang Kai a couple of slaps for causing this commotion, he even let himself be defeated by some weak clans that didn't even have anyone above the core formation level.

The gem on Kai's forehead was slightly cracked but he managed to hold onto the souls in there. He was filled with rage, this was probably the biggest loss to his face that he had suffered in his life. If it wasn't for Elder Ming he would have been done in by some no-name cultivator.

"Damn old bastard, making a fool out of me!"

He delivered a smack to the old man's face, he couldn't defend himself and didn't have the armor to protect himself anymore. The strength difference was immense as Zhang Jin felt his cheekbones breaking from the impact. Yang Kai was enraged, this anger wouldn't go down until he eliminated every single person that was related to this old man.

"I'll devour all of your souls and torment you for decades!"

The Dark Palm Elder had ordered him to eradicate the offending clans, this wasn't a problem but it could take a while. He didn't want to waste his time so he decided to finish up with this old fart. He moved his hand towards the old man's chest and performed a grasping motion. Zhang Jin suddenly felt something getting forcefully ripped out from his very being.

"S-stop..."

The old man groaned as his soul started getting extracted from his body. He couldn't muster up even a spark of spiritual energy, his hands and legs went limp. The man screamed out in pain, he was getting torn apart from the inside. His body started to visibly shrivel up while his soul got transferred to the man's hand.

'My children...I'm sorry...'

His body dropped to the ground without much of a thud. He was nothing more than a bag of skin and bones the light in his eyes slowly extinguishing. Flashes of his long life went through his mind, the good, the bad, and the mundane. This long life was finally ending, leaving this man with many regrets. The bitterness about having brought ruin to his family was engulfed by silence and the neverending darkness that followed soon after.

"This soul... isn't bad..."

Yang Kai licked his lips, the gem in his forehead glowing in purple light as the soul entered it. The cracks that were in it started to slowly patch themselves up thanks to the boons from this battle. He looked to Elder Ming that was done with probing Zhang Liu. The barrier that was keeping the youth protected shattered in mare moments after the Nascent Soul grandmaster applied a bit more pressure.

"Mmm... be sure to clean up."

Wu Ming looked bored as he slowly started to leave, the Zhang Clan members couldn't even protest. Most of them had long lost consciousness and were already surrounded by the other Dark Palm members that were ready to carry out the cleansing. From the group only the core formation elders were still managing to hold on. They could only grind their teeth after seeing Zhang Jin's lifeless body hit the ground.

Yang Kai made his way towards the youth that caused him to lose the bet.

"All because of this piece of trash... this soul isn't to my liking... far too young."

He snorted while picking up the boy from the ground. He still wanted to perform the deed himself a good strike to the head would do. He wanted to feel his opponent's blood on his hands, this would extinguish his rage oh so slightly.

"Die!"

His punch with his whole cultivation realm behind it flew forward. Even if Zhang Liu was at his strongest, he would have no way of defending himself. However, right before the fist made contact with the white-haired boy's face something appeared in front of it. It started small, like a little droplet of water floating around. The drop expanded turning into a small puddle that was hovering around vertically and in the way of that punch.

The moment Yang Kai's fist connected with the puddle it stopped. The Dark Palm Members looked from the side, bewildered by what they were seeing. There was a hand sticking out from thin air, coming out from what looked like a small floating portal.

"Argh...! W-what is this!"

Yang Kai screamed out in pain as the hand grasped his fist tightly, he tried pushing or pulling but it felt like he was trying to pull the whole continent by himself. The floating portal started to quickly expand while the hand that was sticking out moved forward. Within moments the people could see a man emerging from within.

He had shoulder-length white hair and a well-built physique. The robe he was wearing was pure white with some golden patterns sewed in here and there. The robe had some shiny metallic parts to it, the chest area was well protected and the hand that was holding onto the other man was covered by a tight gauntlet.

Yang Kai went down to his knees while trying to exert the full extent of his cultivation, still, the person that was in front of him wasn't budging. He didn't even seem that interested in the man he was holding the hand of, and just looked around the area. His eyes quickly darting between the people in the area, they quickly came to a stop after he noticed a certain husk of a man on the ground. The moment he noticed him the people in the vicinity felt a spike in spiritual energy follow by two words.

"The...Fuck?"

Chapter 159

A little bit earlier in a location between Spirit Spring City and Jade Grass City.

Thunder boomed and the clouds parted as some passerby's trembled in their boots. No one had enough time to react, the moment they heard the loud sound the being in the clouds was already gone. The only thing indicating that someone was even there was the straight path in the sky followed by hurricane-like winds. This was, of course, Zhang Dong racing towards his destination.

'I'm only halfway there, they seem to be holding up though.'

Matt had his disciple window out and was looking at Zhang Liu's status. The protective measures that the system put on the youth were still there and they hadn't gone down much since he took off. This was letting him know that whoever triggered that mark to activate wasn't able to follow up afterward.

'Why did they stop though? Did someone get involved and protected the boy?'

Matt wasn't sure about the reason, maybe the whole thing was some kind of misunderstanding and his disciple only got critically wounded during this so-called Dao festival. It was in Dark Palm Sect territory, so he could very well be showing his hand too early. Revealing that he was a nascent soul cultivator brought with it various problems.

Before he could reorganize his thoughts on the off chance that it was some kind of misunderstanding, the disciple window blinked. The mark's energy level started going down going to a bit over 50% in a matter of seconds. Something had to be happening there, how could this defensive measure drop down from being almost fully charged to half.

'It should be able to tank hits from core formation experts at the great circle level... are there many people of that level piling up on him or something?'

Matt's palms started sweating profusely after he thought about the other option that was more realistic.

'There is someone at my level there...'

It didn't take long for the system screen to glow red once more and the protective technique to go down to just 10% of its maximum charge.

'I'm nowhere near that city... what's happening there?'

He started panicking, he was already burning through this spiritual energy to fly at an alarming speed. It would take him about thirty minutes to get there, this was an amount of time in which anything could happen to his clan members or allies. While his mind was getting overtaken by dread the energy counter went down to zero and his screen went red once more.

'God damn is there nothing I can do.'

He racked his brain for an answer, this system sometimes showed him new ways to use it if he only thought of a feasible way.

'Could there be something that I could have missed?'

The system did update slightly after he reached the nascent soul level, it even came with one big handy new feature.

'Maybe there will be an option that relates to that?'

He quickly went through his disciple window trying to find the answer, he even stopped flying so fast so that he could concentrate. He was rapidly clicking through the options and going through sliders to see if something new popped up.

'Sharing spiritual energy...'

'Transfering knowledge...'

'Affection levels, devotion levels...'

'Defensive measures...'

'Other...'

'Special feature tab...'

'There it is!'

There was an actual 'Fast Travel' tab that brought him over to a new section of his disciple window. Some of the options were grayed out, but the ones that he could bring up gave him various ways of traveling to his disciples.

Small Portal (One Way) [ 100 000 SP] | Creates a small portal the size of the user to the location of the disciple.
Instant Transfer [ 1 000 000 SP ] | Instantly transports the user to his disciple, can also transport the disciple towards their master.
Large Portal (Two Way) [500 000 SP] | It creates a large portal that allows two-way travel.

The things he could buy here had various requirements that he had to fulfill before he could even purchase them. The ones he could use had all the minimum requirements of him being in the early stage of the nascent soul realm. They also required a certain amount of devotion and affection that the system was counting.

He didn't have quite enough Spirit Points for even the cheapest one, that being the 'Small Portal' one. But thanks to having a large amount of crafting materials in the form of beast cores and some leftover spirit stones, he was able to get that bare minimum. About a week had passed since he used up all of his points, but thanks to having two cities that gained him points passively he was able to gather enough.

'Okay, I got it... now activate!'

He stopped in his tracts and floated above some unknown landscape. The moment he pressed the fast travel option it told him to select the disciple he wanted to travel to. This was a slight surprise as he was able to even select his other disciple that was Xue, guess you didn't have to spend the points for every student separately. You still needed a certain devotion and trust level to be able to teleport to a given disciple though.

Energy rippled after he selected Zhang Liu from the small two people list. The moment he pressed the prompt in front of him it transformed into a little teleportation gate that looked like semi-transparent liquid. He could see some blurry scenery on the other side, but he had to squint to make out the fine details.

'Is that... a fist?'

He was someone at the Nascent Soul level so he saw the whole thing in slow motion. The person that was punching forward was doing it slowly compared to what he was capable of now. He reacted somewhat instinctively and pushed his left palm into the little portal, grabbing the fist mid-flight. He used his superior cultivation to cancel out any spiritual energy that the person on the other side put into this attack.

Soon the portal expanded enough for him to walk past it, the destroyed scenery on the other side becoming clearer after he passed through the liquid-like gate. He gazed at the man that he was holding the hand of and noticed the forehead gem that he had, this made him think to the time a similar person visited his clan to give them the order about the secret ground.

It didn't take him long to figure out that this guy was up to no good and was trying to murder his disciple that was now behind him on the ground. This prompted him to increase the pressure in his grip making Yang Kai drop to his knees from the pain. Matt felt some strange rock armor shattering into dust before he got to the man's bones that crumbled quickly afterward. Before he could call out to his opponent with a question he noticed a certain pile of black metal.

'Isn't that, the Black Knight prototype I made?'

He didn't like the look of this as he knew who was the person he gave this suit of armor too. He quickly noticed the shriveled up body of Zhang Jin laying there motionless. Even with his enhanced spiritual sense, he couldn't feel a drop of life from that withered body.

"The...fuck?"

His loud voice resonated through the area, it was backed by his cultivation level that took everyone by surprise. Everyone from the Dark Palm Sect took a couple of steps back, even Elder Ming raised a brow as he was looking with interest at the white-haired man that just walked through a portal.

'How is that possible? You shouldn't be able to form teleportation gates without a medium.'

Wu Ming was taking his time, this was an unknown variable. He didn't know if this person was friend or foe, he could very well be someone from another well-respected sect so he had to be careful. The man that arrived was apparently preoccupied with something else and wasn't paying attention to him, he would use that to his advantage.

"Unhand me, do you even know who I am?"

Yang Kai protested while going down to his knees. Veins on his neck and forehead were bulging as he tried getting away, but to no avail. He was even looking to the side to elder Ming. He was hoping that the man would save him, but Ming was just floating in the background not doing anything in particular.

'That bastard is scared to make the first move, this person is also in the nascent soul. Will, he abandon me?'

He thought to himself, battles between nascent soul cultivators were quite rare. People that had gotten to this level were all cold and calculating, they wouldn't risk hundreds of years of cultivation on a battle that they weren't at least 90% sure that they could win. This was the stance that Wu Ming was taking as well. Even though this was a child of the sect leader, he wouldn't blindly jump in to rescue him.

"No one cares who you are."

Before Yang Kai could raise another complaint he was slapped. His cheek ballooned and he was silenced rather quickly. His cheek and jawbone shattered instantly like it was made from paper mache. He then felt a burst of strange unfamiliar spiritual energy getting exuded from this man dressed in white.

"Someone tell me what happened here!"

Zhang Dong shouted while releasing a burst of spiritual energy. Wu Ming backed off slightly as this attack was aimed towards his own aura that he was using to keep everyone from the triforce alliance in check. Feng Liena and co felt the suppressive force leaving the area and it was replaced by something else. Everyone could finally look up and they saw the Zhang Clan Patriarch just standing there, a golden hue surrounding his whole body.

"S-senior Dong... that man he... used some kind of demonic art to trap Zhang Jin's soul in that gem treasure he wears on his forehead."

Feng Maling was the one to speak up first, the others were slowly gathering themselves up and even the junior members were waking up.

Matt was already standing in front of the shriveled up body of his grandpa. It looked more like a corpse at this point than a body that was fine just a few moments ago. He dragged Yang Kai along holding him by his hair and part of his head. He placed his hand on Zhang Jin's chest, soon golden energy washed over him. The whithered body started to slowly recover but even when it did, the one performing the healing arts was frowning.

"This... the soul is truly missing..."

He stared at the slightly cracked gem that was embedded into the forehead of this Yang Kai and tried examining it.

Slightly cracked Dark Soul Gem |

This type of soul gem is used in tandem with various demonic arts. It is mostly used to trap souls of other beings inside of it. The practitioner that had captured the soul can then extract the trapped souls and preform various techniques with their help.

This dark soul gem houses a myriad of souls and is used to nourish its user's cultivation by siphoning energy from the trapped beings inside.

Matt's face twitched slightly after he went through the explanation. He pushed his spiritual sense into the gem while holding the man close. He indeed could feel various souls trapped inside this thing, they were different than his own nascent soul but thanks to it he was able to handle things related to them better now.

"You..."

He glared at Yang Kai, his finger going towards the man's head the tip releasing small electric arcs that were gold in color.

"N-no... I am the son of the Dark Palm Sect's great leader, you can not kill me!"

The man started thrashing about, his eyes darting from the incoming finger to Wu Ming that was still standing on the side and not doing anything.

"Elder Ming, what are you doing save me!"

Wu Ming gave off a sigh, this has gotten too troublesome for even him. He came to this city for a simple auction and now it looked like this Yang Kai had offended some other Nascent Soul monster that he didn't know the background off.

"Fellow Daoist... I implore you to let that young lad go, I'm sure we can come to an agreement."

"I'm not sure from which sect this friend comes from, but I'm sure you wouldn't want to wage war over such a trivial matter."

Wu Ming stretched out his hands as if he was shrugging. In this man's opinion this was something that the junior generation caused. People of his level wouldn't really move for small matters like this, just some core formation and foundation establishment cultivators got hurt, there was no reason to make a big fuss about this.

"Trivial matter?"

Zhang Dong looked at the body of his grandpa that had slightly recovered and then to Wu Ming. He knew that this person had to be the one that caused his grandpa's armor to give out. He was also sure that it was him that caused the protective Mark to give out on Zhang Liu. This guy was clearly just trying to evade a fight and then reorganize later, he couldn't give him that chance though.

So, he did the only thing that he deemed to be right. The hand that was holding Yang Kai glowed brightly, his Qi invading the man's very being.

"Nooooo...Wu Ming do something... you old bastardddddddd!"

Yang Kai's whole body started glowing brightly. Rays of light came out of his orifices like his eyes and ears and shot out into the air. Wu Ming didn't have enough time to react as he was taken aback by the sudden attack from this unfamiliar cultivator. Yang Kai's body started giving out crackling sounds and soon enough it exploded into nothing more than dust. The only thing left was the purple soul gem that was now between Zhang Dong's two fingers.

"Y-you..."

Chapter 160

The Zhang Clan members that were present here looked with awe at their Patriarch. Their eyes were glued to his glowing form and followed his every movement. They were quite touched that their leader had made his way here in such a short amount of time. He was even risking offending the Dark Palm Sect by defending them here.

"Master...Grandpa..."

Zhang Xue called out from the side while looking at her senior uncle and her grandpa that looked to be dead. Her brother was also down on the ground not too far away from where Zhang Dong was standing. The group of juniors and elders were further in the back, which gave them a good view of what was happening down on the center stage.

After the flashing light subsided they saw that the man that caused them so much trouble was gone. He was just disintegrated out of existence by their Patriarch who made it look easy.

"Was the Patriarch always this strong?"

"So that's the Zhang Clan's leader..."

Huo Kong gulped after witnessing the display of power. He began thinking that he might have been too hasty in his conclusion. Maybe his father didn't blow this senior uncle's achievements out of proportions.

"He is far stronger now than two years ago."

Kong's father looked at his senior brother with sparkles in his eyes, he wanted nothing more than to ask him about the way he had managed to reach the nascent soul level in just a measly two years.

Feng Liena was also astonished like the rest, she didn't expect Zhang Dong to rush to their rescue. Her heart didn't flutter that much as she came to the realization that he was probably here to save his disciple. She tossed her selfish thoughts to the back of her head, now hopeful that this man would produce a miraculous outcome as he did before when they were stuck in that secret ground before.

While Zhang Dong's allies were quite beaming with curiosity, the man in question was holding onto the purple soul gem. Nothing was left from Yang Kai, his body had turned to fine dust and was carried off by the wind by now. He glanced at the item in his hand but was also keeping his attention on the Dark Palm elder that was floating to the side. He didn't choose to attack him just yet, but fighting could break out at any moment. He wasn't sure what that old man was thinking about, but he was looking at him with a focused gaze. He on the other hand wanted to tend to this soul gem to help his grandpa out.

"There are a couple of things that I can overlook, but killing the sect leaders son isn't one of them... identify yourself!"

Wu Ming sounded a lot less friendly now, this whole situation got a whole lot more troublesome the moment Yang Kai was killed. He would be held responsible for this, he wasn't sure how the Dark Palm Patriarch would react. He probably didn't have to worry about losing his life, his position was too high for that. Still, he could be locked up for multiple years without being able to leave the sect premises.

"Could you... wait a second? Think I have this figured out, I'll be with you in a moment."

The man with the white robe replied while moving over to where Zhang Jin's body was laying. Wu Ming was taken aback by the blatant disrespect that this man was showing towards him. Was he a nascent soul grandmaster such an unimportant character? Was the giant sect that was behind him something you could insult without any worry in the world?

"You are courting death!"

The sentence that shouldn't be used had been delivered. Wu Ming's face was getting red and he looked like he was going to pop a vein at any moment. This person wasn't giving him any face at all, he might have been in the nascent soul level as him but he looked far too young. He was being cautious with him, but he was slowly getting fed up with the whole thing. There was so much that this man could stomach, he was still someone that was used to a certain level of respect. This was also why his reason started getting clouded and he decided to test this man out, without gathering enough information beforehand.

Wu Ming moved his hand upwards, his palm going in front of his face as he held it vertically while keeping his fingers together. His hand began to change its coloring going from pale to black in a matter of seconds. A shadowy aura that expanded outwardly formed, it took the shape of a blade that was pointing straight up into the air.

The Dark Palm elder then swung his hand forward, the air around the shadowy blade rippled. The people in the area started coughing up blood as even though this attack didn't look that imposing it had the backing of a nascent soul cultivation realm behind it. All the core formation seniors that were from the triforce alliance put themselves between the energy fluctuations and their junior members. Even they that were in the great circle of core formation were shivering. They were trying to muster up all their might just to block residual Qi from an attack that was aimed at someone else.

"I'll court your mom!"

Zhang Dong shouted out, golden energy surrounded his palm in a similar way as Wu Ming's. He delivered a backhanded slap to the incoming shadow blade. The two forces collided with each other sending some residual Qi blasts to the side. To the Dark Palm elder's surprise, his shadow blade bent in an awkward fashion and it bounced to the side. There was a loud bang as another part of the colosseum building blew up leaving another large hole behind.

Elder Ming retreated slightly, he looked with interest to the man that pimp slapped his attack to the side. This might not have been one of his strongest techniques but it still packed a punch and had the backing of his middle stage nascent soul realm.

"I told you to wait."

Zhang Dong glared at the man that sent some edgy shadow blade attack towards him. His focus went back to the item he was holding, his opponent was probably shocked so he would think twice before using a half-assed attack like the one that he did.

'There were some books about soul arts in the library from the secret ground... but this is a demonic technique.'

He was quite sure that if he destroyed this gem that was holding the souls they would be set free into the surrounding. The souls should then begin searching for their old bodies as they are naturally attracted to them. But normal souls couldn't survive outside their bodies for too long, if they didn't find a vessel they would vanish into nothingness. If the soul was from a stronger person, or it had strong desires it could survive longer. Some then turned into vengeful ghosts or decrepit souls that haunted the lands with broken memories of their past lives.

Matt was hesitating to destroy the gem, the possibility of releasing some vicious specters was high as he didn't think that their bodies existed in this plane anymore. He also felt that there was a possibility of saving some of the souls that were trapped in there at a later date. So instead he guided his spiritual energy into the soul gem and began searching for the soul that belonged to his grandpa. It wasn't that hard to find as it was one of the newer ones that had been trapped in this place it also was strongly reacting to his spiritual energy as if it was drawn to it.

'There you are...'

Matt guided the soul from the gem to Zhang Jin's body. People were curiously looking at what this nascent soul senior was doing, he was holding a gem with three of his fingers. A golden glow appeared once more as something akin to a glowing ball flew out of the jewel and quickly embedded itself between the old man's eyebrows.

'Did that work?'

Matt squatted down and held up Zhang Jin, resting his head on his palm as he tried examining the 'patient'. He could feel that the soul was back in there, but it was weakened for some reason. The man didn't seem like he would be waking up any time soon. He wasn't sure if the demonic art caused some damage to Zhang Jin's soul, but he didn't really have enough time to figure this out as the other nascent soul cultivator was regaining his composure.

"Who are you... are you from the Dragon Gate Sect? the Demon Subduing Sect?... or maybe from the Limitless Sword Society?"

Matt turned to the man and looked up to him. He had a vague idea about these organizations but didn't know anything specific. His retainers probably thought that he already knew the power structures of the lands and didn't bother him with things related to them. They didn't know that this person was naturally lazy when it came to politics and would rather spend time crafting or learning new skills. This did make him recall that he needed to come up with a cool name soon though.

While the two people were staring at each other, the unmoving bodies of Zhang Jin and Zhang Liu started slowly moving. Matt had realized that he had something akin to telekinesis after reaching the nascent soul level. This was also the reason that people at this level could fly without the use of treasures.

"Hmm, who might I be? Do you really want to know... but before that, what do you intend to do with these people?"

He pointed to the people behind him with his thumb. They were, of course, the members of the triforce alliance, the group was still standing there by this time all of them were wide awake. The bodies of the two Zhang members slowly hovered towards where that group was standing, Zhang Dong didn't feel like it would be wise to fight while his two family members were out cold.

Wu Ming looked to the group of weak cultivators, not really sure what this man's reasoning was.

"Them? They were disrespectful of the entire sect, they deserve nothing but death... but why would you..."

A lightbulb flashed above elder Ming's head and he looked to the hovering bodies of the two people. This man had to be related to these two, why would he bother to save them otherwise. The eighteen-year-old youth was clearly his disciple and the old man had some similar facial features to the white-haired man.

At first, this Dark Palm elder had the misconception of thinking that this man was from some powerful sect and this Zhang Liu was just some disciple he picked up. It wasn't odd for eccentric nascent soul masters to have disciples all over the place. But this man uncharacteristically cared too much for the others involved in this drama. Normal cultivators wouldn't go out of their way to help the entire clan of their disciples while offending other powerful cultivators. This man was willing to do it though, this made Wu Ming think that he had a more intimate relation with them. He might even be one of them!

"You're part of them... you're not part of any sect, are you? You're just a rogue cultivator!"

If this was the truth than Wu Ming didn't have to worry about anything coming back to bite him. He was mostly being cautious as to not get their sect into some drawn-out war with another equal or more powerful sect.

He glanced at the man with the white hair, then to the people in the back that heard him speak. It was clear to him that he hit the nail on the head.

"You dare hide your realm in the territory of our sect!"

Being a nascent soul realm cultivator in this lands without a strong backing was something that you couldn't do. You had to associate yourself with someone in power otherwise, a life of constant running was the only thing that waited for you. While Wu Ming was in the middle of his monologue though Zhang Dong managed to hover his disciple and grandpa to where his allies were. His whole body then started crackling with golden lightning, his aura expanding.

"Listen up everyone, all of you return to Spirit Spring City where my Zhang Clan is located, I will join you there shortly. That is the only place where you will be safe from the Dark Palm Sect. After I'm done with a couple of things I'll return there!"

The moment he said those words the whole area was engulfed in golden energy, lightning bolts flickered everywhere and booms of thunder resounded through the destroyed colosseum. Everyone within the vicinity gasped in shock, the other Dark Palm cultivators around the area felt an oppressive force wash over them as they found themselves losing consciousness.

Wu Ming snorted a bit as he surrounded his body with a shadowy aura, this attack that he was seeing was quite weak. It didn't affect him at all as he was able to block it with just a plain aura shield that every cultivator at his level was able to produce. He was mostly sure that this man had no backing, he would have announced his faction by this point if he was sane.

"Do you really want to go against my Dark Palm sect? You an everyone involved will be eradicated!"

Before the man could get an answer he could feel something emerging from the brightly lit area. This something was a large fist that was crackling with golden lightning energy coming right for his head. During the exchange, you could faintly hear the man in white talking.

"I'm going against it because I know that you'd do that, you moron."

Chapter 161

The people had noticed that something was afoot. At one point the audience started pouring out, the communication jades had gone down so information wasn't going through as well as it should. The Dark Palm members formed a perimeter around the large building keeping all those people that wanted to escape there.

Most core formation elders that were stationed in this city and were close by, went into the arena. The people keeping order outside were mostly in the foundation establishment realm, with two or three people being on the weaker end of core formation.

"What's happening inside senior..."

One of the sect members posed this question to an older looking man that looked to be the one in charge here. The man played with his beard while trying to get some more info with the help of his communication jade but to no avail.

"That doesn't matter, just keep anyone from leaving, that was the last order that the young Master had given us, The grand elder is also there now, so everything should be fine."

Wu Ming had gone inside some time ago after noticing the large blast of Qi that destroyed a quarter of that large arena. The nascent soul elder didn't give them any orders in particular, but Yang Kai did before the communication devices went out. They would continue to follow this order out of fear of offending a prominent sect master.

While they were diligently carrying out the order something finally occurred. A golden like storm shot out into the air and into the surrounding area momentarily stunning some of the cultivators outside. This was the aura attack that Zhang Dong used to knock out all the core formation cultivators in the vicinity. This didn't reach outside though as he was afraid to hurt the civilians outside. He was only able to keep the attack away from people close to him, like the members from the triforce alliance that were at the arena building with him.

Soon people could see two blurry figures taking off, the ground rumbled and the spiritual energy around the area exploded. Hurricane like winds erupted in the city causing quite a bit of residual damage. Everyone looked in the direction of those two figures, the two busted through some jade green pagodas. One was covered in a golden hue while the other person was clouded in shade like energy.

Wu Ming and Zhang Dong clashed with each other, their colliding fists produced shockwaves that caused widespread damage. The people that were the closest to this fight scream out in fright, quickly scattering to various locations to keep themselves safe.

"Two masters are fighting, run for your lives!"

"Is another sect attacking? What's going on?"

"Oh no... the city is getting wrecked!"

People shouted out in panic while trying to get away, rubble was falling everywhere. Matt managed to push his opponent back while they clashed sending him barreling into the ground. He floated up in the air and looked around, taking a second to reassess this situation.

'This doesn't look good... if this continues we'll destroy the whole city... and might even cause casualties.'

Matt didn't care much about the Dark Palm Sect base that was in this city, it would be even better if it got smashed into pieces. The problem was the commoners living here, he didn't want to cause mass destruction or injure anyone that wasn't involved in this scuffle. The two nascent soul cultivators were doing the equivalent of throwing some left jabs at each other at the moment. They were feeling each other out, just measuring each other's all-around power level.

'This guy clearly doesn't care, I bet he would throw meat shields at me if he figured out that I didn't want to attack the regular folk.'

Normally people at their levels didn't care that much about the lives of others. His opponent probably wouldn't think that this Zhang Patriarch cared about harming the citizens of this city.

'I think we need a change of scenery...'

Matt looked to the side and focused his senses, he was trying to find a certain location.

'There, that's a good spot to start things out.'

He grinned slightly while looking down, Wu Ming was already standing up and glaring daggers in his direction. He soon jumped right in, but his opponent didn't throw himself at him, no. The cultivator called Zhang Dong started flying upwards as if he was fleeing. The Dark Palm Elder didn't know what this guy was up to, but he followed after him while delivering some ranged attacks that looked like a barrage of shadowy arrows.

"Where are you going, you think you can escape?"

Wu Ming noticed something about this cultivator, he was clearly only in the early stage. The four stages of the nascent soul had distinct power signatures to them. It didn't matter how much spiritual energy the cultivator had. Even if someone in the early stage had more spiritual energy than someone in the middle stage, you could still tell them both apart. The so-called marker of the stage was quite distinct.

From Wu Ming's perspective, he had the upper hand, even though this enemy he was fighting had massive amounts of Qi he was still only in the early stage. He felt that in the long run, he should be able to take this win. This man was also acting strangely, after delivering a good hit he just backed away and started flying away instead of going with the flow of the fight. It made it seem as if he was trying to flee or at least gain some space between Wu Ming and himself, maybe he wasn't that good at hand to hand combat?

Zhang Dong that was glowing like a light-bulb flew through the air, everyone that saw him coming instantly fled into their homes. Right behind him was quite the angry-looking man with salt and pepper hair, the black arrows that had the shadow attribute raced right behind him. For some reason, Zhang Dong slowed down each time and received the ranged attack with his own energy negating it in the process. This was odd as he could very well just dodge them instead, not many people knew that he was doing it so that those ranged attacks wouldn't hit a passerby.

'Is he mocking me?'

This only made Wu Ming that was flying behind him even madder. He figured the man was taking his attacks just to show him that they weren't up to par. He wanted to increase the number of his attacks, but his opponent didn't look fazed. He needed more time to charge up a stronger one, but if he did that Zhang Dong would be gone by that point.

The chase continued and more shadowy attacks rained, this time though the white-haired man dodged to the side. The old man that was doing the chasing smirked, thinking that he was probably at his limit and couldn't just defend himself anymore. The attack that Matt dodged flew into the distance and hit some kind of defensive formation. The formation wasn't able to hold on though and a couple of those shadow bolts descended downwards into the buildings that were behind this shield.

"Nice hit, but I think you missed a spot."

Zhang Dong gave Wu Ming a thumbs up before moving his hand upwards while forming a lightning spear. He chucked it in the same general direction where the shadow arrows flew, his attack causing more destruction than the previous attack.

"W-what's happening, we are getting attacked!"

"The defensive formation has crumbled just after one hit, are those nascent soul cultivators!"

"Why are two nascent soul masters attacking us, is this an attack from an opposing sect?"

The people looked up into the air with fright in their eyes. They saw a cultivator dressed in some strange armored white robe, slightly behind him was another cultivator that was wearing a Dark Palm elder robe. One of the people on the ground recognized the older looking person and quickly spoke out.

"Isn't that Elder Ming from the main sect?"

"What is he doing here?"

The people murmured among each other, Matt showed a slight grin and quickly shouted so that everyone could hear him.

"Yes, Elder Ming ol' buddy ol' pal, let us destroy this sect outpost before they figure out that we are from the Demon Subduing Sect!"

Wu Ming was taken aback, his eyes bugged out in confusion as he didn't know what to say.

"W-what nonsense are you spewing!"

The man tried to give a retort but the man in the white battle robe gave out a dazzling radiance that blinded most of the people in the area. A loud rumbling sound followed suit that also drowned out whatever elder Ming was saying. A barrage of guided lightning spears that just looked like a mass of golden lightning bolts descended upon the Dark Palm cultivators, raining doom upon them.

This, of course, was the outer sect base that belonged to the Dark Palm sect. Matt had gotten a brilliant idea after he noticed that his opponent wasn't really looking where he was shooting his attacks. The Demon Subduing Sect name came up previously, from what he could recall he knew that both of these sects were antagonistic towards each other. He wasn't sure if this silly scheme would work out, but he was willing to give it a go.

The seed of doubt was placed now, he just needed to remove the only person that could give away his bs act. Firstly he targeted all the main buildings at this base, making sure to cause mayhem and destruction. He was still feeling bad about attacking people out of nowhere, but this was the start of a war. He realized that he had to put his own people first, he was already being merciful by focusing on the structures and the core formation cultivators in this area. He wasn't even going for kills and was trying to just cripple their cultivation bases for now.

After the flash of light cleared, you could hear the groans and moans of the people that were implicated by Matt's wide-area lightning barrage. The whole place was a mess, the ground and buildings were trashed and the area looked like it had been hit by missiles.

"Haha, take that you vile Dark Palm scum! Elder Ming, we should go now before they call for more help!"

This was a big gamble, would they even believe this obvious lie? There was also the other problem of the Demon Subduing Sect getting angry at him for spreading some misinformation, but he could just deny the claims if that time came. Elder Ming, on the other hand, was already coming straight at him, his whole body covered in a shadowy aura.

"Stop spouting this hogwash!"

He was fast to recover, he wasn't sure why this man was doing this type of act but he just had to take care of him before any further trouble arose. Before he could close in though, the white-haired man's figure blurred, in an instant, he was right in front. The two made eye contact for a fraction of a second before Wu Ming saw a palm going for his face. He was rushing forward and couldn't react to his enemy's speed.

This wasn't an attack though, Zhang Dong's digits pushed into the older man's face as he grabbed him by the face. Due to the sudden grab, Wu Ming's lower body flew forward while his neck and head were pushed backward. The two men then flew into the distance leaving the area of the outer sect headquarters.

The older nascent soul cultivator grasped Zhang Dong's wrist and pushed his shadow Qi into his own digits in the hopes of wrestling himself free. To no avail as the divine lightning Qi that formed a thin protective layer was holding in place. The man pushed his whole middle stage to the apex while trying to wrestle himself free, but he just couldn't budge this man's vice-like grip that he had over his face.

Wu Ming's body then flew through the air as he crushed into some boulders. He was finally free and found himself in some unknown location outside of the city. His opponent was just hovering above the ground and looking at him, hands crossed over one another as if he was taunting him.

"Well then, Mr. Big Grand Elder of the Dark Palm Sect. I don't think that you will surrender peacefully?"

Wu Ming just looked up at his opponent, eyes squinting. He waved his hand producing an obsidian Jian sword that had similar Qi qualities to that shadowy Qi that he was using. The old man pointed the sword towards his enemy, no words came out of his mouth but Matt could feel that this man's danger level went up a notch.

"Didn't think so..."

Chapter 162

The whole Jade Grass City was in an uproar. Everyone was hiding in their homes or running for their lives, people were in full panic mode the moment they got wind of two nascent soul cultivators fighting it out in the city. This was a city with millions of people in it, but there were no such things as the police force or a fire department to help people out in the time of need.

Every prominent clan or sect that was living here just closed off their doors and hid away in their mansions, protecting themselves behind their defensive formations. The people with the lack of these sorts of protective measures either hid in the cellars or tried seeking shelter somewhere else, even deciding to run outside and wait it out in the nearby mountains.

While everyone was running around like headless chickens a certain elegant looking gentleman was standing at a large gate. The gate looked to be made from pure gold and it had two winged serpents entangling the columns on each side. Right at the top of the gate, there was a large red sign with the words 'Yinglong Pavilion'. Behind it was a large building that looked like a reverse triangle with the bottom flattened.

The man was sticking out like a sore thumb, mostly due to what he was wearing. He had a very western looking tuxedo, pure black jacket, and trousers that had a satin stripe. Under the jacket, he had the usual black vest and white dress shirt. He wore nice black leather shoes and his cufflinks had a dragon shape to them. The whole getup was completed with a black-tie and a monocle that the man was fiddling with. His gray hair and beard went quite well with his refine gentleman looks, which made you think that this was some kind of butler that worked for a noble.

"Reporting to Lord Tian!"

The man nodded at the other person that looked more like your traditional cultivator as he was wearing a robe. This robe had a similar winged golden dragon pattern on the back like the one on the gate.

"Following the large explosion, the Sect elder that was at our auction house had left towards its source."

"The explosion originated from the Colosseum where the Dao Festival was taking place this year."

"The sect that owns this town had sealed off the access to the building before our men could get more information, but after a further inspection this is what we have found out..."

The man started telling his superior about the fight inside the arena building and the two nascent cultivators that burst out of it. One of them was the Dark Palm Sect Wu Ming that was a special guest at this branch auction house. The man also brought over the info that the two were seen destroying the main base that the sect was located at. The man called Tian was given Zhang Dong's description and that he was an unknown cultivator that suddenly appeared seemingly out of nowhere. It was unclear how or why the man sneaked into the city, but they were speculating that he probably hid his cultivation level.

"After the two nascent soul elders left a group of cultivators belonging to the Feng, Huo and Zhang clan came out. They showed hostility towards the Dark Palm Sect that was blocking people from getting out of the Colosseum building. A fight ensued soon and they left in the direction of the docks. It is unknown if they are related to this incident but it's highly likely..."

"Hmmm...Quite interesting..."

The butler looking man nodded while thinking about something.

"Announce my message to everyone, the Yinglong Pavilion will stay neutral in this matter. Activate the defensive formation and bring all the treasures to the main vault."

The man clasped his hands and headed inside, moments after the sound of the defensive formation activating was heard and a barrier flickered around the large Pavilion building. The man himself remained outside, his eyes focusing in one direction as he felt a battle taking place.

'They began their battle... that one is Wu Ming... the other one... quite peculiar...'

The man fixed his monocle while slowly floating up and standing on the large gate as if he wanted to get a better view of the battle.

'Wu Ming's opponent is in the early stage, but still...'

Thunder and lightning resounding throughout the area, giving even this dandy looking man a shock. The man wasn't going to get involved in this, but he was quite curious. Who would attack a large sect in one of their cities out of the blue, was this a prelude to something larger?

'Quite peculiar, indeed. A storm might be coming to these lands... maybe something interesting will finally happen!'

The man chuckled to himself and peeked at the battle through this monocle, the item enhancing his view to the point that he could even see the two fighter's silhouettes even though they were multiple kilometers away from him. He zoomed in just in time to see the two men clash with each other, the shock-waves from their clashes reverberated right towards the city and caused many mini earthquakes.

Matt floated back and looked to his arm, he was holding onto a hilt of a sword. Yes it was mostly just a hilt now as the blade of this sword of his had been cleanly sliced off after a couple of exchanges. The weapons that he had were only of the earth grade, so they had no chance of lasting against that man's black sword that was a heaven grade treasure.

"You're a slippery bastard and you don't even have a weapon!"

Wu Ming scoffed at his opponent, he was slowly getting into the groove. Ever since he pulled out his sword he was on the attack, his opponent had already gone through multiple weapons. He had sliced and diced them into scrap metal each time and finally noticed that this poor sap didn't have any high-level treasures.

"I'm not convinced, who are you really, stop hiding your real age!"

Elder Ming was also unconvinced about this man's origins. The part about being a renegade cultivator was probably true, but Zhang Dong's youthful appearance was throwing him off. A nascent soul cultivator below the age of two hundred was already hard to find, but this man looked to be below the age of a hundred. For this reason, the man had a theory that he was using some kind of high-level disguise technique.

"Hiding my real age? What are you on about?"

Matt threw the destroyed sword hilt into his spatial ring, not bothering to pull out another one. The items that he had weren't able to handle his increased cultivation level, so even if he wanted to use them they would start crumbling. His opponent didn't even have to destroy them himself, if Matt pushed his energies into the blades they would start to burst from the inside. The weapons at the earth grade just weren't able to hold the massive nascent soul Qi load that was getting poured into them.

Wu Ming pointed his dark jian at Zhang Dong and continued.

"You are clearly hiding your true appearance, there are no masters on your level that are this young, what's your purpose here, are you trying to start a war?"

From Elder Ming's perspective this man was plotting something, he had already mentioned the sect that the Dark Palm sect was on bad terms with previously. This made him think that this opponent was from a third group, one that would gain something if they and the Demon Subduing Sect went to war. There were a couple of options here, but there was nothing to he could go off of here. This man was a mystery and he used a strange cultivation method that he never had seen before.

"Hiding my true appearance? Buddy, I think you have things mixed up here..."

Matt didn't really care what this man thought about at this point, he would be taking him out one way or another so he didn't have to lie anymore. The only thing he had to be careful was from other people that might be listening in on them.

"I'm just your regular thirty-two year old, but enough about me, I have a question for you."

"Are you considered strong in your sect?"

Zhang Dong moved his hand to his chin and looked upwards to his enemy, the old man not looking too happy about the whole ordeal.

"What? Of course, I'm one of the core elders of the sect, the only one that is truly above me is the sect leader!"

The man stuck out his chest as if he was happy with his proclamation, he was also hoping to give this man a fright by saying that he was on the stronger side.

"Is that so...That makes things... easier."

Zhang Dong moved his hand to his neck and proceeded to crack it a couple of times before slowly rising up.

"You did well to handle my strength at 15% of my true power, but what will happen if I further increase it to 30%!!!"

He shouted out the last part dramatically, his body began radiating with the already familiar golden light but it was a lot more condensed this time around. Matt wasn't really being serious with the percentages, he also had no way of truly measuring his own output as they did in some shows that he watched back in the day. He still wanted to say that line, it was something that the people in this world weren't all too familiar with.

His body flickered as he activated the higher tier version of his Embodiment of the Thunder God. His eyes started turning white, golden lightning bolts flickering on and off within them. His white locks shifted into golden energy and rumbling of thunder filled the area as he charged forward. Before his opponent could even flick his sword, he was able to blitz him thanks to his increased speed. The Dark Palm elder found himself with a footprint embedded into his cheek as he received a swift kick that propelled him into some boulders on the side.

Matt had already spent some time exchanging blows with this man, he had figured out a couple of things during this. For one, he was in no way weaker than someone at the middle stage of the nascent soul level. He also noticed that if he remained in close-quarter combat at all times, the other person's battle prowess dropped significantly. He had a theory concerning that, it was probably mostly due to the upper-level cultivators spending more time learning large scale attacks than sticking to the basics of combat.

Matt was still someone relatively fresh to all this battling nonsense. He had only two years of fighting under his belt and he wasn't afraid to duke it out at close proximity. This was also attributed to him having quite the strong body refining technique that made him impervious to most damage and lowered the pain that he felt.

On the other hand, the most powerful cultivators had long abandoned the early gained techniques. Exchanging them for grander ones, but the harder the technique the more Qi it used, and the longer the activation time was. Sometimes the basics were the way to go, it was far easier to deliver a simple kick or punch to your enemy than to focus on that flashy finisher move to end it all. Even the swordmasters that you'd think would fight at close range, mostly used some ranged slicing attacks that parted the rivers. You didn't actually see them exchanging blows with each other at close range instead, they clashed with their strongest attacks that were backed by their Dao.

'I only learned that one new move it would be wise to just end it like this, but...'

This was also why Matt was staying close to Wu Ming. He didn't really have any nascent soul moves beside one that he learned during this week. This was the safest way of winning this fight, just using his superior cultivation method that gave him better all-around stats than this person that probably knew some peculiar techniques that could shift the tide of this battle. There was also a flip side to this, he wouldn't really learn anything new, he wanted to test his limits while he had the chance to do so.

'I guess, I'll give him some time to recover.'

"Is that all? Is this what a Dark Palm sect elder amounts to?"

Matt flew upwards into the air and looked down at Wu Ming, the man shook the rubble off his robe. His body flickered with shadowy light as he jumped upwards. He began making some strange hand gestures that culminated in him putting them together. The moment he did that a spike in spiritual energy was felt by Matt in the area and something started appearing from behind him.

It looked like a mass of black energy that was getting sucked into a certain spot. The energy started taking form soon after, Matt clearly saw something being created out of nothing. This 'being' looked like a massive looking Raven. This being of shadowy energy was even larger than he was in his avatar form as it towered over him.

"That certainly is a big boy..."

Matt commented while looking at the two beady eyes that were locked on to him.

Chapter 163

"Halt, you may not leave!"

A man with a spear pointed at some people, with him there were many others with similar weapons and clothes. This was the Jade Grass City docks and these men were the guards stationed there. They were following a previously given order of not letting anyone leave the city that a superior from the sect had given them.

They were having slight troubles as there were many people that came for the Dao Festival here. Everyone was going crazy after the two nascent soul uncles started fighting, fleeing the city was the only thing on there mind. The guards were able to keep the numerous people at bay for now, mostly due to the fear of the Dark Palm sect looming over them. Otherwise, the various clan warriors would have charged through these guards that were at most at the foundation level.

This was only to this point though, as a certain group of people charged into the dock area pushing everyone to the side.

"What are you doing, you may not leave, this is what the elders from the Dark Palm sect had decided, are you going against the venerable sect?"

The guard captain with the highest cultivation realm shouted out while seeing a large man with red hair charging forward.

"Venerable? Think you have them confused with some other sect, now move!"

The warning that the guard gave the group didn't work as they all got tossed to the side like ragdolls. The man with red hair was of course Huo Qiang, behind him were all the people from the triforce alliance. Clans that were to the side, looked shocked at the brazen show of force. Everyone was wondering who these people were, that didn't fear the powerful sect that was behind these guards.

"Everyone, go to your ships, we will follow Brother Dong's orders and go towards the Zhang Clan's Spirit Spring City!"

"Qiao, go with the Zhang Clan, and protect their ship, take care of Senior Jin."

Huo Qiang knew that the old man was injured, he was still out cold and getting carried by some Zhang members. Zhang Liu on the other hand had awoken from his slumber and was more or less healed thanks to some recovery pills he had previously gotten from his master. The pills had the holy element infused into them, so they worked wonders for external and internal injuries of any kind. He and Feng Nuana were running along with the rest of the people from their camp, the short girl was glancing back and forth from the youth as if she wanted to say something.

"My lord, is it wise to do that? Shouldn't we return to the clan and alert the Patriarch?"

Huo Qiao asked while everyone was making their way into the docks, the guards that were there not really being able to do anything with the core formation experts around.

"Hah, you saw it all... Senior Brother is the only one that can protect us... we just need to tell that old fart to hide for the moment."

"Young Master, please stop referring to the Patriarch that way..."

Qiao nodded and saw some reason in this. What good would it do to hide away in their main city, only to wait for the incoming doom? He didn't think that the Dark Palm sect would let them live, even this nascent soul elder was already ordering that Yang Kai to eradicate all the three clans that were involved in this fiasco. Probably letting themselves be protected by an allied nascent soul master like Zhang Dong was the better option, but he was still only one man.

"Are the communication jades still not working?"

Communications were still out, the jades in themselves had probably been destroyed and they needed new ones. Even the ones that were in their spatial rings were not working anymore. This worked in their favor as the sect that was chasing them wouldn't know that they left, or that the incident even happened before someone from this city reported it. They had some precious time now, the word about this incident hadn't reached outside yet.

While everyone was running towards their designated ships a big screech was heard. It sounded like a cry from some kind of bird, everyone that was rushing forward had to grasp their ears. The core formation elders quickly surrounded the juniors with their aura to protect them from harm.

Everyone looked into the distance to the spot that this loud cry originated from. The cultivator's eyes went wide as they saw that large beast opening its wings. It looked like a huge raven, but this beast was the size of a kaiju a lot bigger than normal creatures that were even in the core formation level. Its size was immense when it flapped those giant wings giant cyclones were created that produced massive windstorms.

"Master is fighting that?"

Zhang Liu and Xue were squatting down on the ground along with the other junior members, taken aback by the sudden appearance of that creature. Was that some kind of nascent soul technique that they didn't know about?

"Is that a Spirit Soul-Beast?"

The old granny from the Feng clan called out, her eyes squinting as she tried to look in the direction where the action was happening.

"I heard it takes a lot of time to create a Soul-Beast like that, not every nascent soul cultivator is able to do it..."

Most of the people here didn't really have information about the various techniques a nascent soul master used. They were shrouded in mystery, but this one was more of a staple so it was more widely known. Still, how one produced such a strong beast that rivaled its own master in battle strength was an enigma.

"What's a Spirit Soul-Beast?"

One of the junior members asked while quivering down on the ground.

"A Soul-Beast is something a nascent soul master is able to create. It's more than an attack, this beast as its name states possess its own soul. We don't have much information on this matter, but it is believed that it has something to do with the nascent soul of the cultivator. It can freely move around and has a mind of its own as well."

The old lady explained while forcing the hurricane-like winds away from the group of youths that she was protecting. She didn't know all the details but, she was sure of one thing. A cultivator that had a Soul-Beast with him had a massive advantage over one that didn't have it. Supposedly those beasts could be even stronger than the person that created them and would follow any order without asking any pesky questions. The beast was supposedly created with the help of the cultivator's nascent soul, so it was a part of them.

While the triforce alliance was concerned about what Zhang Dong was against they saw a blinding light in the distance. Opposite of the giant black bird there was something or someone. The flickering light expanded in scope while looking spherical in nature.

Then something strange happened after the sphere turned gigantic, something burst through it. It looked like a massive clawed hand, following it was a massive roar. The yell sounded like a mix of a monsters growl and the sound of thunder. The Spherical orb of light burst like a balloon after that monstrous claw showed itself, revealing the monster inside.

"W-what is that... it's... golden?"

"What kind of beast is that... it's not a dragon, is it?"

What materialized was a beast that the people here weren't familiar with. The body of this creature was hulking and covered in golden scales. It wasn't as big as the shadowy raven that was flapping its wings in front of it, but the presence that it had was even above that flying creature.

The golden creature had two large horns sprouting from its head. On its back the people could see huge webbed wings, sharp claws were present on some parts of those wings. Its eyes were smooth and glossy, the whole creature had lizardly features to it. Out of its nostrils lightning bolts were shooting out and the moment it gave out a roar the whole place shook as if the heavens were angry.

This was what Matt would call a Western Dragon. This counterpart of the Dragon species wasn't serpentine in nature, it had powerful-looking fore and hindlegs that could deliver massive blows to its foes. It also didn't possess the classical deer-like horns that the eastern dragons had.

Without a warning a colossal explosion of plasma erupted, shooting wildly into the heavens making the cyclones and winds stop. The imposing scaly golden body slowly moved forward. The leathery bat-like wings expanded to the creature's sides. The creature glared at the large raven in the distance, its long tail thrashing about and causing destruction to the surroundings.

Suddenly the dragon reared up on its hind legs, the muscles bulging as it jumped towards the dark shadowy raven beast. Its savage claws that looked like sword pillars sliced through the air as it flew towards its enemy. The Raven Soul-Beast gave out a high pitched caw while moving its huge wings towards that charging dragon.

When the wings moved forward a burst of spiritual energy erupted and a massive amount of black feathers shot out. The feathers looked like guided missiles that were on a collision course with the golden dragon in front. The beast that looked like it belonged to Zhang Dong didn't falter, it used those sharp claws to bat at the ranged attack, destroying the mass of feathers in the process.

"Is that... the Patriarch Soul-Beast?"

The Zhang Clan members shouted out after getting the name of this technique from the Feng elder. The beast had some characteristics that their Patriarch had, mostly that it was shooting out lightning bolts whenever it went. It also had that golden regal aura that their leader exuded as well.

Closer to where the two monsters were fighting, Zhang Dong was floating to the side, his robe fluttering in the wind. He moved his hand out with his fingers outstretched while shouting.

"Ruby Eyes Golden Dragon, use dragon claw!"

The golden dragon responded to the order, using it's massive clawed hands as it swiped at the large raven that evaded to the side. Elder Wu was just floating there looking a lot paler than before while gasping for air.

"Now use, plasma breath!"

The dragon's toothy maw opened wide and a stream of bright golden plasma shot out, the black Raven barely managed to put up some kind of shadowy shield that broke almost instantly.

"H-how could this be..."

For the first time during this battle, the man had fear in his eyes. He thought that he would surely win after activating this trump card. People that had Soul-Beasts that were at the early stage of the nascent soul were rare, mostly due to the complexity of the technique and the massive strain it put the cultivator on. Somehow this young-looking man had summoned a strong Soul-Beast to combat his. The many years of experience were telling him that that strange-looking flying lizard was a lot stronger than his own.

He could tell from the way the two were clashing, that with each attack his beast took he got weaker. The dragon was abusing the flying monster around, the residual electricity blasts that were coming of it were a constant threat. This technique that the man just used was a strong one, but it was also a double-edged sword. The creature created was strong but it was linked to the cultivator that created it, with a soul bond.

Wu Ming felt each attack that his raven received and he used up a lot of Qi to keep this technique going. He thought he could overwhelm this white-haired man with the addition of his Soul-Beast but the opponent had managed to pull out an even stronger monster instead. The Dark Palm elder started inching away to the side, slowly floating away while his beast got abused by the so-called Ruby Eyes Golden Dragon.

"Where do you think you're going?"

Before he could run though, he had his way blocked by this enemy cultivator.

"You're looking a bit pale there, having trouble keeping your technique up?"

Matt was curious, this was apparently the same type of technique he was using but it was taking a lot more from this old man than from him. It was probably due to the fact that he had a one in a billion cultivation method, he had truckloads of spiritual energy and he very rarely ran out of it.

Matt cracked his fists together while the two beasts in the back were fighting it out. The dragon was clinging to the large blackbird and biting into its neck, its powerful claws sinking into the other soul-beast spirit flesh as it got maimed.

Chapter 164

A shadow bent at an awkward angle turning into a claw as it tried going for Zhang Dong's throat. Before it could reach it's designated spot the man in white rapidly dodged to the side. His whole body was covered in glowing Qi energy, his hair fluttering in the wind while crackling with electricity.

Wu Ming did his utmost best to deliver killing blow after killing blow to this younger cultivator, but to no avail. His opponent was very slippery and even when he was unarmed he managed to deliver several blows while countering.

"I guess that's how far you can go, huh?"

The battle turned somewhat one-sided. Matt found that his speed, power, and even resilience was above this Dark Palm elder that was already in the middle stage of the nascent soul realm. He wasn't sure if this old man was a good reference point though. Just as his strength was above him due to having a better base thanks to this system of his, someone else could very well outrank this guy even in the early stage.

He didn't come out unscathed though, he suffered a couple of slices from that black sword. They were quite shallow though and he reasoned that if he had similar graded equipment that this fight would have been even easier. From this, he started thinking that he should have no problem with cultivators that were in the early stage at all. He could probably fight a couple of them if they were at the middle stage. If one was at the late stage, he wasn't all that sure the jump in power might be massive depending on the grade of their cultivation method so he needed to take people at that realm on an individual basis.

'I don't think there are any people with cultivation methods at the immortal level in the Dark Palm Sect, but there could be manuals like mine in this world.'

After meeting Feng Liena he knew that there had to be people like him in this land before. There might even be some that are living around here just as he is. Sometimes he came across structures that didn't fit the Xianxia vibes all too well, or certain individuals that stuck out like a sore thumb. Just like this one uncle that looked like a butler of a noble house that was staring at him from afar, probably not realizing that Matt here could actually see him all the way from here.

'Well, Alfred there doesn't look that hostile, he is about as strong as this Wu Ming... but can't really be sure...'

Matt looked to his opponent that was hovering in the air. The man's lip was cut and he was bleeding, his left shoulder was uncovered and it looked like something had burned it. His eyes were bloodshot and he was staring in Matt's direction with indignation. He had various emotions going through his mind, but mostly it was fear and anger.

"You will never get away with this, if you kill me the sect elders will hunt you down like a pig!"

'Oh, here it comes.'

Matt raised his hand, which made the sect elder quiet down in surprise.

"Hold up there, old man. You aren't seriously going to tell me to spare you now... like what's the point of telling me that your sect is going to get me?"

Matt wasn't sure why the cultivators at certain positions liked to throw their faction's weight around the moment they got in a pinch. If he let the man go, he would only increase his enemy count. He was sure that this guy would quickly report everything that transpired here, if he silenced him now he would even gain some time.

"What? Do you think I'm joking? The sect will eradicate your entire clan, everyone that is related to you will die, if you dare to lay a hand on me!"

Matt squinted at the man that was spouting nonsense, maybe he had punched him too many times and his brain wasn't working right?

"Yeah... like they weren't going to do that anyway, I bet you would be at the forefront of that..."

The large golden dragon flapped its large bat-like wings behind where Zhang Dong was hovering. Wu Ming was right in front, his own Soul-Beast was slowly flickering in and out of existence as it had been bullied by the golden dragon. Matt had spent slightly over two years in this world still, he wasn't really used to taking lives. He had realized by now, that sometimes it was necessary to survive, for him or for the people that he was protecting. He wasn't fighting for himself anymore, if he went down his whole clan would probably follow suit. Also, this man probably had a large body count behind him, so he wouldn't be losing any sleep after killing a murder hobo like this.

"Think we have talked long enough..."

The white-haired man proclaimed while closing his eyes, the dragon behind him gave out a loud roar that caused the surrounding scenery to vibrate. Zhang Dong moved his right hand forward, four fingers closed with only the index finger pointing out. The digit was placed right in front of his face, spiritual energy gathered towards the tip as the whole area resonated with the sound of thunder and crackling electricity.

The dragon behind him wasn't being passive either, his large jaw sprung open and those sharp chompers came out. The Soul-Beast took in a large breath, its chest expanded, and started to glow as it prepared for its own attack.

"You people love clashes like this, don't you? Will you face me head-on, or will you run like a coward?"

Wu Ming's whole face contorted, his teeth clenching tightly while blood dripped from his mouth. He couldn't remember a time where he was disrespected this much, this wasn't something that he could take lying down. He reacted promptly, his black blade in his hand as he started pouring the last ounce of his energy into his weapon. The black Raven behind him screeched out loudly and started to mimic the golden dragon as it gathered large amounts of energy into its beak.

The whole place rumbled, the ground shook and the winds picked up yet again. The people back in Jade Grass City were starting to get worried, they could see two lights in the distance. Some of the people could even make out the appearance of those two Soul-Beasts, the two being huge as they were. The growling and high pitched bird squawks were heard even back here, some people were bleeding from their ears if they didn't cover them up in time.

The two energies collided with each other. It looked as if a shadow was trying to engulf a golden beam of light in the distance, the two repelling forces struggled for just a moment before one of them won out. The black light bent inwards as it was overtaken by the bright holy lightning energies, what followed suit was a giant explosion that made the whole place shake as if it was struck by an earthquake above eight on the Richter scale.

A dust cloud of massive proportions was formed, hitting the city from the side after the clash of the two nascent soul masters. Buildings shook, glass shattered and people were screaming everywhere. The whole triforce alliance was mostly on their ships now, their mouths agape as they continued to look at the massive explosion in the distance. The only thing on their mind was who the victor of this battle was, but not like they had the luxury of going there to find out.

"Everyone, we must leave now!"

The elder members started shouting out while their spiritual flying ships rumbled into motion. The winds caused them to shake but it wasn't something that would bring their large flying vessels down. They need to use the massive confusion in the city to get away, luckily the Dark Palm sect base in this city was already hit by the Zhang Clan Patriarch. This allowed the group to slowly rise into the air and fly in the direction of Spirit Spring City as ordered by Zhang Dong.

Out in the distance in the middle of the storm there floated a lone cultivator. His hair was pure white and his body was draped in bolts of lightning that were slowly flickering in and out of existence.

"Hmm..."

Matt looked in the direction of where his enemy was in, not much was left besides a giant chasm that was blasted by him and his golden dragon. The Dark Raven was nowhere to be seen and he also saw a fallen body of the cultivator that he was fighting. The body wasn't moving at all, blood was also running into the destroyed ground underneath.

"Something is off..."

He closed his eyes and empowered his senses to the extreme. He had perceived something during the clash that he had with this old man, it was as if he gave up halfway and let himself get blasted into smithereens. The man's end came a bit too easy and he had a suspicion as to why.

"There you are..."

His eyes shot open and crackled with lightning, he blurred from his position and took flight in a certain direction. In the distance there was something flying away, it was Wu Ming but only a part of him. This was something that cultivators called a nascent divinity form. People that had reached the nascent soul level possessed an ability to survive in their soul form even if their fleshy body was destroyed. They were a lot weaker like this and required outside help to fully restore their old battle potential. With the help of some treasures, it was possible but highly unlikely.

"N-no...stay back!"

Wu Ming looked back as he felt the cultivator with white going after him. He had given up on the battle in the hopes of getting away and sacrificing his soul-beast. The other man had homed in on his nascent divinity form faster than he had hoped for. If he managed to get to the main sect area he would be safe, so he mustered all of his remaining Qi and flew forward.

"Sorry... but I can't let you escape old man..."

Matt was a lot faster than Wu Ming even when the Dark Palm elder was at full power. He didn't have much trouble in catching up to him and with no one to aid this man he was at his mercy.

"W-what do you want, I can give you unimaginable riches! I-if we work together we might be able to take out the sect leader!"

The man started breaking down, he stopped with the threats and tried acting subservient instead. He was even willing to throw his so-called cherished sect under the bus to save his life.

"Sorry, but there is no way I can trust someone like you."

Matt moved his hand out, Wu Ming's spirit form trembled and stopped in place as he felt a massive amount of spiritual energy surrounding him. Without letting the old cultivator spout more nonsense he clenched his fist shut, the energy around the soul quickly surged inwards and crushed the disembodied soul into nothingness. A small explosion reverberated after the deed was done, followed by an eerie silence.

Matt looked at his clenched fist, it was clenched firmly and unmoving. He opened up the fist and looked at his palm as if he was trying to check for something. Soon his hand began to tremble, the moment it did his facial expression also flickered with emotion, sweat running down his forehead.

"Heh... still can't handle it well without that technique..."

He gave out a sigh and clenched his fist back, the trembling subsiding in a matter of moments, and his facial expression went back to a more neutral look. The man looked at the scenery for a moment and then flew back to where the body of the man he just slew was. He didn't forget about taking the black sword and the man's spatial ring, now what was left was to move to the next step of his hastily put together plan.

Chapter 165

Matt leaned down and touched the dead body of elder Ming on the forehead. The man's body soon started vanishing out of existence turning into dust before his eyes. What was left was his robe and whatever else he was wearing. Everything was tossed into the storage ring while Matt himself started to examine the new one he got as his loot.

'What do we have here...'

He noticed that the ring didn't really have much preventing him from peeking inside. He thought that someone from a big sect would have some defensive measures preventing others from taking their stuff. Maybe the elder didn't think anyone would be brazen enough to actually steal the ring they always wore on their hand. This type of ring only had a simple lock that only worked when the owner was still alive, maybe this was considered enough.

'Well, not like mine has more to lock it either...'

He glanced inside and saw a nice stash of spirit stones, lower graded, and middle graded ones. Besides that, there were some old cultivation manuals, various pills, and quite an amount of treasures.

'Was this guy some kind of collector...'

There were various items just floating in there, weapons, necklaces, rings, herbs, and even some booze that looked quite expensive. He didn't really have time to look over all of this throughout so he focused his senses to see if there was anything at the nascent soul level, he already had the black sword with him.

'Not really that much in here...'

There was a couple of heaven graded techniques in here, even the manual for that shadowy cultivation art that Wu Ming was using. But it wasn't really anything better than what he had obtained from that secret ground.

'There is another heaven realm weapon in here, guess even elders don't have enough cash to have many of those around... or maybe he didn't bring his whole stash along with him.'

The other item was a large black glaive, it was an early heaven graded weapon and kind of what he needed right now.

'I'll use this to get my body refining to the next level... the sword I can use for combat, it's also a middle graded one. Don't really see any demonic techniques in here, though that guy with the soul gem didn't have any demonic arts in his own spatial ring either.'

He rubbed his chin and shrugged, he had managed to loot two Dark Palm Masters and was a lot richer but this wealth wasn't nearly enough for what he was planning to do. No, he would need a lot more, mostly more spirit stones or beast cores, any treasures that could be used to increase his spirit point count would do.

'I guess I should go back into the city, there should still be some loot left in that base of theirs...'

There was no more danger waiting for him there, besides this one Buttler looking guy that was still looking at him from the distance. The man didn't feel hostile though, the aura he was exuding was mostly just curiosity than malice.

'No use fighting a fight that I can avoid, shouldn't get too cocky...'

He thought to himself while flying back into Jade Grass City. After taking the residual energies of the two nascent soul fighters the city looked deserted, everything was closed and was covered in a layer of dust. He could feel people hiding in the buildings while he was flying by, but they were just scared civilians that he wouldn't bother with.

"Greetings, seen something you like?"

Matt asked the man that hovered down from the giant golden dragon gate. The two men looked at each other, their spiritual senses clashing against each other as they tried to feel each other out.

"Why yes good fellow, you have given this old man quite the show to watch."

The man gave a little bow, the monocle that was sitting on his face almost slipping out during it.

"Ah, sure... I'll keep this quick as I don't have much time. What is your stance on all of this?"

Matt was now holding the black sword in his hand, looking quite menacing. His Soul-Beast was also hovering in the back but outside the city, mostly there to alert him if any other nascent soul trouble arrived.

"No need for that look ol' chap, the Yinglong Pavilion always remains neutral in situations like this, there is nothing to fear."

Matt raised his eyebrow and then looked at the large store's name. He even recalled selling some of his crafted items and loot at a less prominent branch store.

"But if I may, could I pose the same question to you ol' chap. You're not thinking about robbing my good establishment here, are you now?"

The man's aura warped and you could see a cold glint behind those eyes. This pressure washed over Zhang Dong's body making him take a step back in surprise. This man was certainly stronger than that previous opponent that he fought just recently. Battling would be unwise, his plan of sacking this place was now being questioned by himself.

"Robbing? Me? No... I was just going to grab some stuff I left behind at the Dark Palm Sect."

Zhang Dong straightened out, his aura getting unlashed into the surrounding area and canceling the killing intent that was produced by the old English gentleman looking fellow. The man's face twitched slightly, his facial expression going back to a cheerful smile as if nothing happened at all.

"Well that's fine, as long as you leave Yinglong Pavilion out of your disagreement with that Sect, we will always remain neutral. I can give you my word."

Matt nodded, he already had a big faction going after him, he didn't want another one to be after his head. Previously he thought that this place belonged to the Dark Palm Sect. He had no problem in robbing his enemy blind, but this was another power altogether.

"Mmm."

He clasped his hands and did a little formal bow before jumping up and heading into the distance. The old man gave out a sigh of relief the moment Zhang Dong left.

'I might be getting too old for this.'

The man chuckled slightly while pulling out a handkerchief. He wiped the sweat from his forehead that came running out right after the other man had left. He had managed to scare him away, but he knew that if a battle ensued that his chances of winning were slim.

'Where did such a man come from.'

The man named Tian looked in the opposite direction that Zhang Dong flew off. In the distance, he could see a large looking beast. This was the golden dragon that was guarding the area, the peculiar thing about it was that it was still out there even after the battle had ended.

'He must have immense spiritual energy reserves to be able to do this, is he really only at the early stage?'

The man shook his head, thinking to himself that the man had to be hiding his true cultivation realm. Having a Soul-Beast so early in the cultivator's life was unprecedented. It was more realistic that the man with white hair was hiding his true level, he might even be at the late stage.

'I must report this, it would be better not to make an enemy of him.'

While the butler was blowing things out of proportions, the cultivator in white had arrived at the mostly destroyed outer sect base of the Dark Palm Sect. There was quite the number of injured people as he had fired off his Qi blasts in a random direction. Even though he was mostly aiming for injuring people, there could have been fatalities.

"Oh no...w-why is that man back!"

"What happened to Elder Ming..."

People shouted out and screamed as they saw the Nascent Soul cultivator approach them slowly. Before they could react to his approach they felt their legs giving out. An oppressive force washed over them and it felt like gravity was increased tenfold. They couldn't do much besides going down to their knees, their faces pale from the strain that their bodies were placed upon.

Zhang Dong's eyes flashed with divine power, it would be quite easy to just flatten all of these people right here right now. This was the group that was going after his newfound family. The question he had thought was if these people were all cold-blooded murderers as the man that he just clashed with. His sense washed over them, their bodies trembled in fear and he could even hear some of them weeping.

"I'm really not cut out for this..."

He shook his head and increased the pressure that his aura was applying to the people that were actually still conscious. He heard cries of protest but soon the whole place quieted down, the only thing that he could hear was silent breathing. Everyone that was in the vicinity of his aura attack had passed out, their lives weren't in danger though.

"Not like the lower cultivators matter that much, the battle will be decided by the elite few."

He knew that it probably wasn't wise to leave the enemy soldiers alive, but this world worked differently. The few outweighed the many, what counted were the nascent soul elders that were at the top. He could more or less focus on those, if he managed to get rid of them the battle would be won.

"Well, better get what I came here for..."

He closed his eyes and focused again, his energy washed over the area. Soon enough small trinkets and bags were floating upwards, these were all the spatial rings and bags that these Dark Palm Sect members had on them. Matt used his enhanced senses to home in on the peculiar aura that these types of treasures had and so he was able to identify them for a faster looting time.

He didn't really go through any of them just yet though, he just placed everything in a regular bag that then he inserted into his own high-quality spatial ring. There was a certain danger in having so many treasures that worked on spatial laws, if he tried cramming everything into a badly made storage device it could very well cause an explosion.

That's why he only trusted his very own storage ring that he received from the system. This thing was high quality and wouldn't break even with multiple other dimensional devices stored inside it.

"Should I take their robes... Could probably get some raw materials if I deconstruct them in my crafting abode."

Nothing was safe from his clutches, the people were left in their loincloth but everything else was cleaned out. Anything that was identified as a crafting component was going into the bag. The previously destroyed area was left with a bunch of naked people, even parts of the buildings were missing. The floor tiles that had some residual Qi in them weren't left behind, much less for any bronze or iron statues. The vault was cleaned out, not a single book remained after Matt was done here.

"Okay, think I got everything..."

He took another look around him, making sure that there weren't any secret chambers hidden below the estate. His senses weren't picking up anything of notice though.

"This is the thing that I came here for though."

He pulled up a map, it was something he got from one of the rooms that the Dark Palm members probably held their meetings at. It had some basic information scribbled on it, so he could easily decipher it. It had the location of their cities marked in and also where they bordered with the other sects. He could even see the current city and also Spirit Spring City on it, the font for his city was quite tiny though making him think that they weren't taking it very seriously.

"There... they do have one of those..."

"I need to go, they might increase their guards... but I don't think there should be more than one nascent soul cultivator guarding it."

Matt nodded and brought up his system map, this thing was quite handy for times like this. He put in the coordinates and now only needed to fly in the direction that the map was guiding him towards. The place where he was going was deeper in Dark Palm Sect territory, but he had no chose he needed the resources that were at his next destination to go through with his plan.

Chapter 166

In a faraway location, a small group of people was standing in a certain place. The atmosphere was tense, everyone had a solemn expression on their face while talking.

"What should we do... the Sect Master is still in seclusion, it would be unwise to interrupt him."

One of the old men in the room said in a grim voice. He then glanced at the others that were with him, this being three other men at his age and an old woman.

"No, we should report this as soon as we can! What if he punishes us for not doing it swiftly enough."

The woman said while trembling slightly, the simple thought of that made this person panic outwardly.

"Yes the information was dire, but... will you be the one to report it? How will you explain yourself?"

The old woman averted her gaze from the man and quieted down. No one here was willing to be the bringer of bad news, everyone was afraid of how the leader would react to it. The group of five was standing around a table, on that table lay a crumbled tablet with the name 'Yang Kai' written on it.

"Maybe we can withhold the exact time of this event transpired?"

A slightly chubby man said while whipping his forehead with some white cloth.

"Can't we put the blame on a junior member, just tell him that they mixed things up?"

The man laughed slightly while the others looked at him strangely. Throwing another person under the bus wasn't something they were against, but not like they had a reason to do that just yet. They weren't really at fault here and needed more information before deciding. Before the group could come to an agreement another person burst into the room while shouting.

"Bad news, bad news!"

This man's eyes were wide open and he was carrying a similar-looking tablet that was there on the table. It was cracked in the middle and he was holding each piece in a separate hand.

"What is this? You dare to come into this meeting that we the Grand Elders of the sect are having!"

The man stopped and looked like a frog was stuck down his throat, he quickly regained his composure and dropped down to his knees, his head hitting the floor.

"I do not dare Grand Elders! New circumstances have come to light, Elder Cuifen had ordered me to gather information about the 'situation'. A-a new problem has arisen."

The man visibly shook while not looking up, the five people in this room were all Grand Elders of the sect and were of the Nascent Soul level. He wouldn't dare to speak any more than this without their approval.

"Yes, I gave him that order, but you were supposed to be discreet!"

The old woman glared at the man that had burst in through the door, but her rage soon subsided as she knew that he probably had a reason for that.

"Speak, what has happened? I hope for your own sake that it's important."

The woman scoffed and then sat down at the table with the other three elders.

"Y-yes, I thank you for your benevolence grand elder!"

The man moved his head up and then presented the broken tablet so that everyone could see what was written on it. The moment he brought the two pieces together the characters for 'Wu Ming' could be seen by the grand elders.

The five elders were visibly shocked, one of them slammed the table while shouting.

"That bastard Wu Ming is dead? How is that possible, he was one of us!"

The elders looked at the person that was showing them the broken tablet. They all could feel that this was really the spirit tablet that belonged to one of the more fearsome grand elders from their sect.

"T-there is more, by the Grand Elder's order we looked into lord Yang Kai's whereabouts. We have reason to believe that the young lord had left the sect not too long ago together with Grand Elder Ming. Their location was Jade Grass City that is situated in one of the lower regions."

The man hastily recited everything he knew, he brought up that the two left for the auction house about two weeks ago. They had information that the two did indeed arrive at their destination and that the so-called Dao festival for the lesser clans was held there.

"Then all communications halted you say?"

The man that was asked nodded while replying.

"Yes, we have been given a report that the region had gone dark, we are not able to reach the outer sect that is located there or any of the sect members that reside there."

One of the Grand Elders rubbed his beard while thinking, his eyebrows slowly changing directions.

"That is indeed peculiar... sounds like some organized attack by some other sect."

"I agree, someone had to have planned an ambush for either the young master or Wu Ming, maybe even both."

The Grand Elders all quieted down, this was turning out to be worse than expected. The Sect Master would have to be given this information, a nascent soul grand elder had just perished. There was also suspicious movement in the background, they had to be really careful now. These people were naturally suspicious, there were many reasons that could have lead to Wu Ming's death. They hoped that it was only some kind of internal struggle rather than with another sect.

"We should report this to the Sect Leade..."

"Bad news...BAD NEWS!"

"What is it now!?"

Just before the man could finish his sentence another man in a Dark Palm sect robe burst in through the door. The five elders looked ticked of which made the man instantly drop down to his knees right next to the other man.

"R-reporting... there has been trouble at one of the Sect's treasured sites! I-it has suffered an attack by a nascent soul enemy!"

One of the Grand Elders slammed his fist on the table which made the wood that it was made from a crack.

"What is this, are we truly being attacked? Who is this person that attacked us? What is the site that was attacked? What of the damages?"

The man shouted out questions in rapid succession that made the Dark Palm member's eyes spin.

"The site that was attacked is the Glacial Gorge, where the sects spirit stone mine is located."

The people that were in the room gasped, this mine was one of the more lucrative places that the sect had it was even protected by a nascent soul elder at all times.

"T-the assailant has been identified as..."

The Dark Palm member stopped before saying the name, the pause clearly noticed by the Grand Elders in the room.

"Well, who was it? Who dared to attack our mine!"

The man that was kneeling shivered somewhat before finally replying, the information causing mostly confusion among these elders.

"The attacker has been identified as, Grand Elder Wu Ming!"

Everyone looked at the man with a funny expression on their faces. The five nascent soul elders glanced at the other man that was holding the tables, the name 'Wu Ming' clearly written on it. Another hand smacked the meeting room table turning it into dust, the two men that came with the bad news jumped away in fright.

"What nonsense are you spouting, Wu Ming's spirit tablet is broken!"

The man kept kneeling while replying in fright.

"T-this is the report I was given!"

"Explain in detail, what happened there! How long ago was this, is this 'Wu Ming' still there?"

Another elder threw his two cents in, the five were sure that something had to be off with this story. Either this was some kind of imposter or Wu Ming was scheming something behind their backs.

"Yes, the report stated this..."

.............................

A while earlier, somewhere out in Dark Palm sect territory.

"I'm getting close to the destination, I should change now."

Matt came to an abrupt stop while flying through the air. He glanced at the surrounding area, pine-like trees that were covered in snow-filled his vision. He landed on the ground and made sure that there weren't any people in the area peeking in on him.

"This probably isn't going to work... but better than just going in guns blazing."

He took out the spatial ring that belonged to the nascent soul elder that he had killed not too long ago. He took out one of the robes that were placed there. He changed into it, a large dark palm insignia was now on his back. His facial features soon shifted and his body began getting smaller. Who walked out from the snowy forest was someone that was the spitting image of Wu Ming the Dark Palm Sect Grand elder.

"Hmmm... testing, testing... you are courting death! ... Almost...how about... I, your Father..."

Matt made it sure to have the exact same voice as the man he killed. He could mimic his appearance and maybe some of his mannerisms but he couldn't do the same with his cultivation method. He also had the dark sword to protect himself with, he would have to hide his lightning and divine techniques while being at that mine. This was the best plan that he came up with, which was probably better than just barging in there.

"This should at least give me the drop on them."

He slumped his shoulders forward and took into the air once again. He placed the new won sword to his side and was sure to look as constipated as he could.

'They shouldn't ask too many questions if I look pissed of, right?'

He was close to the spirit stone mine, his map even started picking up some life signals. The moment he pushed into the nascent soul level his system also had an upgrade. His map range had increased and it even started giving him more info. The number of colors that the dots had increased, the color pallet showed him in what cultivation realm the person there was. If they were hostile or dangerous they would just flash instead of appearing in red.

'I also got that free technique with my skill tree.'

Going back a week, after Matt had pushed into the nascent soul realm the system provided him some rewards. He received a free skill for managing to cultivate into a greater realm on his own without using the systems help. This was something new, as the system never really rewarded him for doing things himself. He never got anything when he was going through the core formation realms on his own. This made him think that it could be another change that happened after the secret ground adventure.

The skill here was the Soul-Beast one. This was the reason he had it ready so early after reaching his new realm of power. He even received a small creation kit with a couple of options to design his monster. The choice was limited to some beast types, like large monster birds like a phoenix, flying serpents with wings, even a giant option. Matt was still someone influenced by his western earth values so he went with a popular choice and created a dragon.

There wasn't much to choose when it came to the features. The dragon was big and golden from the get-go, probably due to the way his cultivation method was upgraded. He was able to change the eye color and choose how bulky the dragon's body would be. The body choices changed the statics making the beast be more speed or power-based. He went with the middle choice not wanting a glass cannon or a slow tank, an all-rounder is what he decided on.

While Matt was remembering his Soul-Beast choices he had finally arrived at his destination. He saw a wide gorge, it was all covered in ice but looked like it was made from blue crystals instead. There were many holes in these crystal-like walls, probably leading into the mine shafts inside. There were settlements on both sides of the large gorge. These buildings looked rather plain and boring, probably only being used as cheap housing for the people working there.

From the top, rocky stairs with ramparts were leading into the previously spotted large holes. He could see people moving back and forth while pulling out carts filled with rough looking ores. Even from here, he could feel spiritual energy coming from those ores, small crystals were sticking out of those chunks which made Matt's eyes glisten.

'Time to get this show on the road.'

He thought while his face went into grumpy cultivator mode, the people below slowly getting aware of his existence.

Chapter 167

A man with a slight hump on his back and quite the lengthy protruding upper teeth was looking at some papers. He was sitting in a large leather chair, the desk he had the papers on looked to be quite robust and made from some rare spiritual wood.

"The production has increased by 1% for this month..."

The man murmured to himself in a silent voice, the parchment he was holding had various numbers written on them. This was the monthly report from this spirit stone mine. Everything that was excavated was listed in here, how many tons of spirit stone ore there was as well as its quality.

The man took out a pen from the side and started scribbling something down on the same report. Some of the numbers slowly shifted to something else. He placed the pen that was made from a large green feather to the side and then he glanced at the parchment again.

"The production has decreased by 2% this month, think we'll have to make an example of some of the workers and cut their pay again, hehe~."

The man's eyes turned into crescent shapes, his thin, crack lips quickly turning into a devilish grin. The man didn't have much time to enjoy his scheming as he heard a knock on the door. He flared his nostrils at the sound and placed the paper down on his desk before replying.

"What is is? This better be important!"

At the call another person entered the room, he looked like your average cultivator. He gave the usual courteous bow before the man and then started talking.

"Reporting to the Grand elder!"

With annoyance the man waved his hand, letting the other person know that he was allowed to speak.

"An honorable guest has arrived today, he wants to meet you, Grand Elder Zhu"

The man raised his eyebrow wondering who this honorable person was.

"Well? Does this honorable guest have a name or title?"

The man already had beads of sweat forming on his forehead by just being here. The nascent soul grand elder was giving him the death glare, but he had to perform his job and bring the information over as the other person was even more frightening.

"Yes! It's Grand Elder Wu Ming from the main sect!"

The elder named Zhu showed a lopsided grimace after hearing the name of the person that had arrived.

"Elder Wu Ming?... did he say what he wants from me?"

Zhu moved one of his fingers to his mouth and started chewing on it, his eyes glancing to the paper that he just forged to show that the mine was doing worse than it actually did.

'Are they on to me? Did someone rat me out? Is it a coincidence... I was sure to not leave any evidence behind...'

The man started hastily contemplating, the voice of the other person in the room finally snapping him back to reality.

"Yes, Grand Elder Ming gave instructions. He wants to have a meeting with Grand Elder Zhu, he requested it be a secluded room. He mentioned that he doesn't want to be disturbed and that everyone should leave the premise for your discussion."

The man gave a rapid-fire recount of the order he got, the thing he wanted to do the most was to leave. The moment he mentioned Elder Ming's name the other grand elder started leaking his nascent soul aura. This spiritual pressure that he was exuding now was making this cultivator's body shiver.

"Grand Elder Ming said that he is in a hurry and would like to have a talk as soon as possible. That was all, Grand Elder Zhu!"

The man with the overbite looked down onto the desk while thinking.

'Why does he want to meet me in a separate room... maybe he wants in on the deal too?'

The man strained his brain trying to figure out Wu Ming's purpose here. Why was he making an unannounced visit to this cold and gloomy place? At first, Zhu though that he was ordered to check up on him by the other elders. But this was Grand Elder Ming, he was one of the stronger members of the sect. If there was a problem they would probably send an elder that was in the early stage, just like him.

'No, Ming only cares about face and treasures. He probably wants to extort me for some spirit stones. He probably needs more to satiate that treasure addiction he has!'

Wu Ming's love for treasures was widely known throughout the sect. The man spent most of his time going from city to city to visit auction houses. Some people even speculated that he was so easy to punish people for showing disrespect only to rob them and get his hands on their treasures and spirit stones.

'Shit, does he have some proof? No... he doesn't need it. If I deny him he can order an investigation!'

Zhu knew that if an official investigation took place, they would find inconsistencies in the numbers. He was fabricating the reports here and there to siphon spirit stones for himself, even if the amount was trivial he was still stealing.

The old man stood up and slammed both his palms down on his expensive-looking desk, the item almost breaking from the strike. This startled the messenger here, that was still standing there waiting for a reply or for a sign that he could leave.

"You... go tell Elder Wu Ming that I will meet him shortly, also guide him to my personal cultivation room!"

The man bowed and quickly shuffled out of the room, finally free from the oppressive aura. Elder Zhu on the other hand had his jaw clenched and was gritting his teeth.

'I have no choice, I have to share some assets with him. If he reports me to the council, I'll be severely punished and they'll probably resign me to the border region.'

The region that this elder was fearing was one bordering with a hostile sect. In that place battles between the two factions were commonplace and even nascent soul elders like him had to take part in them.

The old man put on his game face and headed out. He needed to at least get a good deal out of it, after Wu Ming was on his side he would also be implicated in the scheme with him. This might also be a good thing in disguise as he could get the backing of a senior Grand Elder.

'Hm, with him on my side it would be less stressful to pull this off... and there is still a lot of spirit stones to go around...'

He left the room he was in and headed outside. The moment he went outside a cold breeze hit his face, the weather here was quite harsh. This wasn't much for a nascent soul master like him, his body had long since evolved. Things like trifling cold weather like this wouldn't even cause him the slightest shiver.

This wasn't the case for the workers here though. Elder Zhu slowly made his way through the pathway that was embedded into the side of the gorge. He could see the people that were pushing carts, blisters on their hands, and their feet covered in some makeshift wrappings.

The moment they saw the Dark Palm Grand Elder they averted their gaze. Everyone knew that this person was bad news, they already saw people get lynched for small offenses. The people that were working here weren't doing it by choice, this was a place that the sect sent offenders too. These could range for people that had some debt that they couldn't pay, to some that had killed or injured someone from their sect.

Human resources were quite easy to come by in this world, so no one really paid attention to the health of these workers. Even if they had short sentences, it was normal for them never to get released unless they had someone with enough backing for the Dark Palm Sect to honor their agreement.

Elder Zhu grimaced while looking at the prostrating mine slaves. Their shady appearance wasn't to his liking, he just wanted them to stay away from him otherwise he could even catch some disease.

"Damn useless bunch, work harder and dig up more stones!"

He said while walking past some workers that stopped with their work to bow before this man. His personal cultivation chambers were buried deep in the gorge as with the close proximity to the spirit stone ores it had superb Qi quality. Of course, there was a limit to how much Qi a cultivator could absorb, if they tried to cultivate hastily they could very well suffer a backlash to their cultivation. Still having a place with constantly replenishing Qi was something sought after and this was also one of the boons of being stationed here.

Zhu continued walking into the mine shaft, one of the branching paths taking him to a large door. Two people were guarding his entrance, they gave him a salute while also informing him that Elder Ming had already gone inside and was waiting for his arrival.

"Be sure to not let anyone inside, unless you have a death wish!"

He glared at the two guards that lowered their gazes. The door slammed shut behind him and he continued walking while increasing his speed, he couldn't let the man wait too long. Still, he felt that he was also a Grand Elder who didn't need to bow his head down towards other people at the same rank.

The winding corridor brought him to another door, this one was already open elder Ming probably being the one that did it. Zhu gave out a small sight after which he straightened himself out. Well, he at least he tried but his posture was quite bad. Inside was a large circular room, there were many blue crystals stuck in the walls. They were illuminating the whole area giving it a faint azure hue.

The first thing Zhu saw after he entered the room was the Dark Palm symbol on Wu Ming's robe.

'Hm, that robe... he really is here for a business talk if he is wearing that one.'

Elder Zhu smirked to himself and headed inside, making sure to lock the door behind him. He activated the protective seal so that the two men wouldn't be bothered by anyone else.

"Welcome Elder Ming, what brings you to this humble spirit mine?"

He waved his hand around while trying to show a faint smile, though it looked more like a devilish smirk from how this man's face was structured. The man with salt and pepper hair in front didn't reply though, he murmured something while not turning around.

Zhu wanted to lash out, but he held himself back this man was playing hardball.

"Heh, can't hide anything from you Elder Ming, what is the reason that you wanted to meet me?"

Elder Ming seamed to move his hand to his chin as if to contemplate but didn't reply either, Zhu in response started sweating and was the one to speak up first.

"I see... your silence says it all... You wouldn't have organized this meeting without the rest of the Grand Elder's if you didn't know. How about we do a 60/40 split..."

Ming looked to be shaking his head to that proposition which made Zhu's brows to twitch.

"... Do you want a 50/50? You know the burden of all of this lies on my shoulders! If someone finds out I'll be the one to blame!"

The distance between the two got smaller as Elder Zhu started approaching, the other party was keeping silent as if he wasn't satisfied with the deal.

"I'm not going below 45/55, you have to give me some face here Wu Ming!"

The man's eyes were bloodshot as he was staring daggers into the other Gran Elder's back. But then suddenly he noticed that something was off, he caught a glimpse of Wu Ming's side profile. The face was right, this was the man he knew, but something wasn't right.

"Wait...what is tha..."

Before he could react he saw the other man's body blur, a hand grasped his mouth and he felt foreign Qi forcibly getting injected into him. Now he finally saw what the problem was, this person was using some kind of disguising technique. The face and body structure was from the Dark Palm Elder, but the technique couldn't fool a nascent soul cultivators' senses that alerted him to the disguise.

"Dude, what are you even on about?"

The man impersonating Elder Ming finally spoke up, his head was tilted to the side and one of his eyebrows raised. This person was of course Zhang Dong, he wasn't really sure what this was all about but thanks to some kind of misunderstanding he was given a chance to catch this man by surprise.

Chapter 168

Moments earlier in the Glacial Gorge.

Matt was standing in the room that was filled with the colorful spirit stone ores. He poked one of the glowing ores, his system instantly gifted him with a prompt informing him that a source of spiritual energy was found. He quickly tapped the 'yes' option and saw his spirit point count rise up by a small amount. The glowing piece of crystal quickly crumbled into dust, the radiant glow vanishing.

'I'm in the right place... but do I have to poke every crystal separately...'

While thinking about his big heist he was reminded about the tragic sigh that he saw in those mine tunnels. The workers in the tunnels were mostly men, but he spotted some women here and there. Children weren't spared either as they were pushing the carts, why they were forced to do this was something Matt was asking himself.

'Is this how most sects operate in this world? Or is this one especially rotten?'

His contemplation was broken by a sound behind him. The door swung open and what seemed to be the man in charge walked in. Matt wasn't sure how he should play this out, he talked his way into this spot and just wanted to incapacitate this guy before getting all the loot.

It would be much easier if he managed to do this on the down-low, so he lured his target into a secluded location that was even provided to him. His opponent was here now, but how could he catch him off guard without alerting the rest of the people in this mine. Surely if they started fighting, the whole thing would become quite annoying to pull off. He wanted to suppress his opponent, but for this, he needed to get closer and not alert him to his true form.

The moment the Dark Palm cultivator walked in he started to talk. His way of speaking was quite rapid which left Matt with little time to reply. The moment he gathered his thoughts to respond the man resumed his monologue himself. He had no idea what he was talking about, but it was something concerning this spirit stone mine? Why was he getting offered a 50/50 split, what was that man even on about, Matt was quite at a loss for words. But, luck was on his side as the man had gotten into strike distance without him even having to say anything.

"Wait...what is tha..."

Matt felt the man's spiritual sense washing over him and he realized that his disguise technique was seen through. This wasn't a problem though, the man he was facing was weaker than Wu Ming and he had the element of surprise. He covered Zhu's mouth with his hand and clenched it tightly, his golden aura activated and his lightning Qi forced itself into his opponent's body.

"What are you even on about?"

He was able to disarm the old man with a hump on his back, he wouldn't be able the move a muscle while he was getting bombarded by superior Qi. The Dark Palm member found himself getting raised up into the air by the intruder that was using Wu Ming's appearance as a disguise. He tried mustering up all of his might, but his nascent soul was getting locked down by an immense force.

"Well, it doesn't matter. I don't have time for your antics..."

Elder Zhu couldn't do anything as the Qi of divine thunder entered his body. It traveled through all of his meridians and even made its way into his dantian, destroying everything in its path. The painstakingly created nascent soul was destroyed, the core crumbled and the foundation pillars shattered into million pieces. What was left was a husk of an old man, his body dropping to the floor, his eyes vacant. The attack was focused on his enemy, no Qi fluctuations were able to make it outside, none of the other Dark Palm sect members would be able to sense a thing.

"Not sure how long you will be able to live like this. Just see it as a new life as someone that you despise the most, a person with no power."

Matt looked at the man on the floor, he was out cold and had his cultivation crippled. The most difficult task was done and he now had free reign in this area. He looked around the cultivation room that this man used for seclusion. Besides the glowing spiritual ores, there wasn't much here. There was some furniture like a closet, this closet was used to stash the passed out person.

He contemplated on going for the kill, but he realized that that would only alert the other party to his whereabouts faster. He knew that just like his clan the Dark Palm sect probably had ways of tracking their more treasured members. Yang Kai and Wu Ming had to go, but he had a smokescreen covering Jade Grass City in the form of the communication jades not working. He feared that if he offed this elder, he would quickly have a bunch of them flying here as one of them had already died recently.

"They will probably be on alert, don't have that much time to do this."

He rubbed his neck while looking up, his eyes locked on his new target.

"Now to the next step! Spirit stones, come to daddy!"

Matt moved out his hand, his newfound telekinesis like abilities forcing all of the glowing stones from the walls. He gathered everything up in a nice pile and proceeded with the absorption process, this netting him some ten thousand of spirit points right of the get-go.

"Hm... not bad for a start...but I need way more than this..."

He brought up his system map, he was deep underground and his spirit GPS was showing him all the corridors in this here mine. He used his waypoint finder to select all of the places that had the thickest spiritual energy, there were a few. Now he could just fly outside and start absorbing everything in a fit of madness.

He dismissed that idea, he'd have some nascent soul goons on him the moment someone saw him running around in a frenzy. His disabling aura couldn't reach around the entire mine, there were just too many people around, someone would report it. He decided to take a slow stroll and even use the dark palm members to his advantage. Why does he need to gather it all himself, when the sect members will gladly do it for him instead?

'Think they have a main storeroom for everything think I can use that, this guy also had quite the small fortune in his storage ring.'

Matt was sure to disrobe the enemy sect elder and take all his storage treasures. He even found a heaven graded weapon in there, this made him want to cultivate his body refining technique even more. Time was of the essence though and he had no idea when he would be found out.

He fixed his robe and looked back into the now dark room. He scanned the place with his spiritual sense not finding anything worthwhile to take so he headed out. He followed the only corridor that he could all the way back to the large door where the two guards were at.

"Greetings to Grand Elder!"

He waved his hand at the two that bowed once again, the constant polite conversations were slowly getting on his nerves.

"Be sure not to disturb Elder Zhu, he had some things to think about and won't be going out of the chambers for a few days."

The two weren't in a position to question Matt that was disguising himself as Wu Ming. They couldn't do much besides bowing and returning to their post, unless something drastic happened they would follow this order even if their life was on the line. The grand elder's word was law and not many could go against it.

While walking through the long corridor Matt brought up his map. He moved his hand over to his system screen and made the whole image that was now in 3D spin around.

'This thing sure got a nice upgrade after I reached the nascent soul realm. The whole system might be somehow powered by my cultivation.'

He could see the whole spirit stone mine in his game-like interface. It showed him multiple corridors, those probably mined out by the slave workers here. The system was even able to find mineral deposits. He just needed to put in a search term and the system would work its wonders. He wrote spirit stones in and everything went into the familiar color shame ranging from green to red. Red showed the biggest spirit stone deposits while green just meant that there was none there.

'I could probably scan the areas around my cities to find mineral pockets in the future, wonder how far the scanning range is...'

He tossed that idea to the back of his mind for the time being. That was probably a very lucrative idea if he found a spirit stone mine for himself or even a mine with some rare metals for crafting. But now he had to focus on the problem before him, absorbing all of the spiritual energy that was in this place.

While looking at his system screen he managed to come out of the corridor that led to elder Zhu's chamber. He was now at a forked road, he could even hear the sound of pickaxes hitting rocks in the distance. There were even shouts of people, probably the guards that were forcing the workers to work harder.

"Hey, you there!"

Matt moved his chin up at a random guard, the guard instantly straightened out and moved closer while bowing.

"How may I serve you, esteemed Grand Elder?"

Matt made sure not to make eye contact, letting the guard know how much below him he was like a proper Grand Elder would.

"Yes, send a message to the person responsible for storing the spirit stones. I want all of the stones to be carried into one room for a proper inspection! Remember that I am a busy man, so hurry up I want every single stone from this mine to be gathered in one location at once! If they ask any questions, say that Wu Ming gave the order and that Elder Zhu has been relieved of his duties for the time being!"

He tapped his foot which produced a slight shockwave, his aura burst forward making a lot of people in the vicinity take notice.

"Be sure to also include the raw ores, have the workers help out if needed. Also... after they are finished I want them to exit the main mine, I have to give it an inspection too!"

He made sure to sound as loud and imposing as he possibly could. He was the only nascent soul cultivator here now, so no one could defy his order. The guard just shivered and nodded, he then took off to get the main manager informed about the order.

Soon he heard people shouting about and shuffling around. The guard was really speedy with his order, as the man responsible for the logistics of the stones even showed up to make a proper greeting. He looked quite chubby and was sweating a lot, but didn't cause much trouble after getting the stink eye from this Zhang Dong in disguise.

'While they are gathering the stones I'll look at the map, need to find the main vain that links all the spirit stones together.'

Matt rubbed his palms together, he wanted to milk this mine dry. It was slightly disappointing that he needed to cash the spirit stones into points right of the bat, but he didn't have much choice as he needed a large amount of them for his next step.

'Hope those guys agree to my plan... I just need to come up with a new faction name...'

Chapter 169

Everything was abuzz, people were running through the mine shafts pushing carts and even carrying stones by hands. Things like spatial rings were forbidden, the sect leaders not wanting workers to steal anything. This increased the workload on them though, but that was a price the men in charge were willing to pay.

"Quickly, the Grand Elder has given his order, we must carry it out!"

Everyone was scared of the new Grand Elder that showed up. The people were speculating but they knew that something was off about this situation. The old Grand Elder Zhu was missing now, some came to the conclusion that he was probably embezzling funds from this mine and he got caught red-handed. He was probably getting punished now, but this didn't explain why they were gathering every single spirit stone they have mined into the biggest storeroom here.

The Grand Elder in question was just floating outside the gorge at the moment, seemingly looking into the air while flicking his finger. No one dared to comment as they just hurried up with their work. This mine wasn't all that huge, so in a couple of hours, the last minecart with some raw spirit stone ores was dumped into the storeroom.

The whole room was radiating with spiritual energy now, there was a big mountain of pure refined stones in one corner. Another large pile of the raw ores right next to it. People were even having trouble breathing in this room, too much spiritual energy in one spot could cause something akin to poisoning if your cultivation wasn't high enough to resist.

"This is all we were able to gather Grand Elder Ming!"

A man in a long robe and a funny looking long hat bowed while the elder named Wu Ming stood just before the entrance to the storeroom. He had a vacant look and was just staring at the piles of gem-like stones just piled up to the roof.

"Grand Elder?"

Matt twitched and coughed into his hand before turning to the sect manager that was responsible for gathering everything here.

"Mhm, is this all of it?"

"Yes my lord, everything that hasn't been shipped yet is all gathered here! It's half a year's worth of what the mine produces."

The man replied while looking at the shiny pile in the storeroom, the spiritual energy making his eyebrows shake slightly.

"This is half a year's worth..."

Matt mumbled to himself while the man next to him continued.

"Yes Grand Elder, you arrived a week before we were planning to ship the stones to the main sect, the processing of the stones takes a while so we don't ship it out often."

'They probably also have to have one of their nascent soul old farts act as a bodyguard. Probably that's also why they don't transport monthly.'

Matt's reasoning, in this case, was, that the old nascent soul masters would rather cultivate in peace than act as convoy security. They probably came to a consensus of doing it twice a year.

"Mhm, leave me now, I need to check on the spirit stone... quality... don't let anyone else enter this room!"

Matt waved his hand and the large door behind him closed shut. He was now alone in this room, he felt like he was getting a tan from just standing in this radiant blue glow. He moved over to the biggest pile of refined stones and slowly placed his palm on it.

Spiritual energy source detected, absorb Y / N ?

He tapped the 'Y' on the screen, the room quickly filled up with a bright light. The whole blue spirit stone mountain began compressing into itself the moment the system started its absorption process. Matt didn't have much time to react as the mountain of stones quickly turned into a fine powder. He quickly glanced at his spirit point count that was shooting up and reaching into the millions without much effort.

'Yikes, and this wasn't even all of them...'

He stretched out his hand and tried doing something else, he used his spiritual sense to make a connection with the Qi energy that the stones were radiating. To his glee, the system gave him the same prompt about detecting an energy source. He quickly accepted and the whole storage room began shining once more, just this time it was covering a whole lot more surface area than before.

In a matter of moments everything in the room vanished, the refined stones just turned into dust while the rough ores crumbled into smaller chunks of normal rock. The people outside the storage room blinked, they could feel that something was happening inside but they had no way of peeking inside to check.

Before they could come up with a theory they heard the door creaking open. Elder Wu Ming walked out, but he did it in such a fashion so the others couldn't peek inside.

"Mhm, lock the door and don't let anyone inside... also direct the slave workers to leave the mines. I must access the situation, there was an alarming report and it could get dangerous."

The manager looked at the Grand Elder and then to the side to some of his workers. No one was sure what this man was talking about, was there some unknown dangers in the mine?

"A-are you sure Grand Elder Wu? This mine has been open for years and all the beast within the area have been slain."

The man asked, but the moment he did he felt an oppressive force wash over him.

"You dare question me?"

The manager's face went pale instantly and he began sweating profusely.

"I dare not, please show mercy, Grand Elder!"

Matt sent a menacing glare at all the people that were standing there and then just walked off without saying much. He was sure that they would follow his orders throughout as they were far too afraid of the thing called a Grand Elder.

'People ruled by fear and power, its probably easy to implement in this kind of world.'

While thinking he made his way back into the mine, he had his map opened up and could see the little dots that were representing the people slowly leaving the corridors. His destination was a certain location, he found it through the help of his map. It looked like one big red blob on it, but if you followed it you realized it spread throughout the whole underground area.

This was a giant mineral vein that connected all of the spirit stone ores together, it was truly gigantic.

'I should get even more spirit points from this giant spirit stone vein than from what they gathered in that storeroom...'

He increased his pace, walking deeper into the dark insides of the now abandoned-looking underground mine. Everyone had bolted outside as they were forced by the sect members that were quickly following their elder's orders.

The people outside rubbed their hands together while moving closer. They had been living here for a while now, so they knew that if they stayed close to each other the bodily heat would keep them warm.

"What is happening, those sect uncles have been acting strange lately..."

One of the younger slaves' asked an older looking man, the man delivered a quick smack to the youth's head as a response.

"Be quiet, what will you do if they hear you and give you a good lashing?"

The youth rubbed his head and felt slightly disgruntled, but he knew that this old man was telling the truth.

"Still, old man Su they are acting strange."

The young man didn't give up, he just brought his tone down so that the angry-looking sect uncles wouldn't hear it. The older man nodded slightly, this thing sure was strange. He had been stuck in this god forgotten place for over 20 years now. He was blessed with a strong resilient body, so he managed to survive this long. In his long life as a slave, this was the first time his captors were acting like that. The slaves were never given time to rest in the middle of the day, something wasn't right.

The old man didn't need to wait much for a reason though. The whole glacial gorge began rumbling and the mine shafts started crumbling. There was a blinding burst of white light that shoot out from the corridors and then the walls started collapsing. It was as if parts of them were removed and the structural integrity of the whole place got compromised.

"W-what is happening, the mine is collapsing!"

The Dark Palm Sect members shouted out in shock. The involuntary workers did the same, luckily at this point in time, there were no people in those mine shafts as everyone was forcefully removed. The people started backing off while the whole side of the gorge that the mine was located in, started to vibrate.

Right in the middle of this was Matt, he was now covered in rubble and just sitting there with not much air to breathe. He pushed his Qi outwards and formed his bubble-like lightning shield that ejected the fallen mine walls from his face.

"Okay, that might not have been the best idea... this place is already falling apart."

He checked his map again, and just as planned he had managed to absorb most of the spiritual energy through the help of the massive mineral vein. The vein connected to most of the spirit stones, those crumbled into dust the moment Matt used his system. This, of course, caused a massive collapse of all the walls, he had just yanked out a massive clump of ore in one go. When the miners did it, they did it slowly and reinforced the walls to that the whole thing wouldn't collapse on them.

"I guess, it's time to go then, this farce has taken long enough..."

He released his divine thunder aura and covered his entire body in it. Matt then headed right upwards while bending his energies to form a makeshift drill. The people outside had taken their time to escape and were looking from afar as the whole place rumbled.

"W-wait, what's that?"

They saw a golden drill shot out from the ground, the energy fluctuations were clearly from a nascent soul master.

"Is that The Grand Elder, what is he doing?"

"Did he cause the mine to collapse, why would he do something like that."

On the other side of the gorge that didn't collapse was the majority of the people, they all had question marks in their eyes not sure what was going on. There was even a louder commotion after two men emerged from the rubble, these were the two guards that were stationed at the secluded chamber that Grand Elder Zhu was resting. The problem was that the same elder that everyone feared was getting dragged by them, and he was quite naked.

Matt looked down at the people gathered there, they were clearly looking between him and the naked man knowing well that only he would be able to put him in that state.

'Uh, they are already using their communication jades, guess the jig is up...'

He hovered towards the group of people that had evacuated to the other side of the gorge. This side had all the buildings and facilities, while the one that had collapsed was just the mine and didn't have much besides guard towers and walls to keep people from entering.

Matt looked at the slave workers that looked terrified, the sect members had no idea what was going on but they probably wouldn't attack or follow him if he just left. He looked at those workers that were in dire need of a warm meal and rest. He couldn't just leave them there, the mine was now gone. He feared that they would be abandoned or fall to the sect's rage after they found out that they got sacked by a fake Wu Ming.

So he made a quick decision after spotting a couple of flying ships in the back of that encampment. He was still going to play his part, so he remained in his disguise and just headed towards the people.

"I'll be taking the workers with me, along with those ships."

He pointed at the large wooden boats that had the dark palm insignia painted on them. The sect members present here still didn't know what this was about, was this Grand Elder crazy? Was he betraying the sect? They already figured out that he probably took all those spirit stones for himself from that storage room.

Before they could question him though he moved his hand forward, the three large ships that were in the back buckled for a while before floating up into the air. They were activated by Matt himself and were guided to where the mass of people was gathering.

"Okay, everyone that is not from the Dark Palm sect please gather on the ship, we will be leaving. Oh and one more thing, please gather up every treasure, item, spatial ring that is in the position from anyone from the sect. Follow my orders and no one will be hurt, unless you want to end up like that guy."

Matt pointed at Grand Elder Zhu, that was wrapped up in a blanket. The guards had rescued him had mostly tended to his needs out of sheer fear of what his title stood for. Though they were a bit hesitant as they had longe since noticed that he was crippled.

The slaves were confused, the sect members baffled by the fact that their own Grand Elder wanted to take all their items. Was this some kind of robbery?

Chapter 170

The Dark Palm sect members shivered in the cold, they were left with only their undergarments huddling together in the cold weather. They glanced up to see a rather scary looking Wu Ming that was staring at them. The slaves that they used to abuse were moving all the food to the large flying ships that they used as a means of transport.

They were left with absolutely nothing and had to watch the group of slaves fly out into the sunset. The man responsible for this didn't leave together with that group, he just grabbed all the remaining treasures for himself. Things like flying swords and communication jades were all confiscated, but they had managed to inform the sect about the trouble happening here. For some reason, the man above them didn't look that concerned as if he wasn't afraid of the Dark Palm sect retaliating.

Name : | Zhang Dong
Affiliation : | Zhang Clan
Spirit Points : | 89327891
Cultivation Base Qi : | Nascent Soul [Early Stage 0,1%] (Divine Golden Nascent Soul)
Cultivation Base Body : | Core Formation [Great Circle+ 100%] (Golden Body+)

The man in question was looking at his status screen, this encounter had netted him almost ninety million spirit points. He also had a lot of spatial rings and bags to go through so he might be even able to reach over a hundred.

'This should be enough...should I go back to Spirit Spring City or try my luck some more...'

He had set the slaves free, quite a lot of them had their cultivation crippled. They all were wearing slave collars that acted like bombs, decapitating anyone that went out of line. It wasn't much of a problem to remove them, he also pocketed each one for more resources.

The moment of surprise was gone by now, the sect should have sent someone to take care of him. The question was if it was only a lone nascent soul elder, or would they bring more people to oppose him. He still had no idea how many nascent soul farts this sect had. Besides the two that he took care of, there was one more back at the old secret ground.

To his dismay, he felt something moving towards him from the distance. Instantly he knew that it was the Dark Palm Grand Elders coming to the rescue as he could feel multiple nascent soul cultivators flying this way.

'One...two...four...five... well... they certainly want me dead if they sent so many old farts after me.'

Matt squinted while looking in the direction that the people were coming from. He could feel that four of those people were in the early stage and one was in the middle stage.

'I haven't really been able to rest since I've left my city, engaging them would be unwise...'

He looked to the side, this was the direction that the slaves took off. He told them that they should leave the area and hide somewhere till the heat is off. There was a war coming and he had no way of protecting them, also telling them to go to Spirit Spring City would give valuable information away that could come biting him in the behind. He decided to just help them out, but if they made it to safety depended on them.

Still, he couldn't fly that way as it would expose the slave workers he just saved to unneeded danger. The nascent soul lunatics that were on his tail could slap them out of the air just for fun. He needed to go in a different direction and at least keep those five cultivators busy.

He didn't get a good look at the people that were chasing him, but from the looks of it, he was getting chased by four old men and one older lady. They were all wearing brownish robes that had quite a lot of sleeve space so that fluttered while they were chasing him.

He took off with a blast, propelling himself forward while holding his hands behind his back. A golden aura surrounded his body that protected him from the wind pressure and any bugs that would normally splatter all over his face if he flew into them. The quintet of angry nascent soul elders saw him taking off and instantly gave chase. One of the elders remained behind for a moment, just to get a more coherent report than what they got from the communication jades.

He was quickly filled in, the Grand Elder that was left for dead even woke up and started complaining but with his cultivation gone no one paid attention to him.

"Elder Guo, you must avenge me!"

The old Grand Elder called Zhu cried out, his teeth rattling in the cold.

"Tend to Elder Zhu, even though his cultivation has been crippled, he is still a Grand Elder, show him some respect."

The man gave his older while snorting, he didn't really care much for his fellow Grand Elder, but the hierarchy had to be kept. They couldn't abandon the old man just like that, at least not in the open. He would be relocated to the main sect and they would see if his injuries could be reversed. If it turned out that he was nothing more than an old man now, he would probably be abandoned or given a teaching role to the lesser disciples.

Guo quickly flew back after the other four members of his clan, he got a more throughout report and it looked like this Wu Ming was an imposter. From what Zhu had said, the man was using some kind of disguising technique. No one below the nascent soul level here was able to see through it, so that made it not all that exceptional.

Back in the sky, Matt was charging through the clouds. The people behind him were slower than him, but he would have to strain his cultivation to actually getaway.

'Mhm, I'm getting low on Qi here... I used up quite a bit after summoning my Soul-Beast and flying like a madman towards Jade Grass City...'

He thought about his next move, there were a few things that he could do. He could stay and fight those five people that were chasing him, but he didn't know if he could handle five of them at once or if there were more of them coming. The second option was to run away and he had just the thing to aid him with that. Taking both options into consideration he opted for a third choice that took both into consideration.

The people behind him weren't really getting any closer and he had to keep this up for a while so that they didn't go after the slave workers he rescued. For the time being, he decided to bring up his disciple screen, he went to the same section where he bought the fast travel option for his disciples.

Instant Transfer [ 1 000 000 SP ] | Instantly transports the user to his disciple, can also transport the disciple towards their master.
Large Portal (Two Way) [500 000 SP] | It creates a large portal that allows two-way travel.

He didn't want to use the portals as that wouldn't be an option during a fight. He also feared that one of those nascent soul farts would send an attack after him, or even dive in after. Then he would need to protect people in his front yard from enemy cultivators. He had managed to procure a massive amount of spirit points with his heist, so he could spend some points on the good stuff.

'I did get that fast travel point option back after I ascended to the nascent soul, but I didn't buy it...'

Besides these teleportation options for his disciples, there was also another one. It was a fast travel point between cities or strongholds that he was the owner of. For now, he could use it for both Spirit Spring City and Moonlight City, he just didn't do it before as he didn't have enough points.

'I can't set up the fast travel point without being at the location... the disciple fast travel system will have to do...'

The fast travel points in the cities were cheaper than the disciple ones, but at the time he just had no spirit points to spare. But thanks to that he managed to find that his disciple tab even had that feature in the first place.

While he was fiddling with his system he felt something. He instinctively dodged to the side and saw a large flaming boulder flying past him. When the huge rock landed down on the ground it produced quite the explosion.

'Oh right... those guys are still chasing me...'

He looked back and saw four people there, the fifth one was further in the back. They were shouting some profanities at him, mostly something to do with courting death and that he should reveal his true identity to them.

He started bobbing and weaving with his entire body as the people behind him continued sending ranged attacks. The terrain below them became riddled with large craters as if the group was composed of modern bomber planes.

"Hey, be careful, what if you hit someone with that?"

Matt that was still looking like Wu Ming returned fire. The Grand Elder that was at the front and also the strongest held out his hand and produced a shield of wind, just in time to receive a golden lightning bolt to it. This caused him to stop in his tracks, his shield cracked slightly but it managed to defend against the charged bolt.

"Lightning? Who is this man?"

"Elder Wan, are you okay?"

The female Grand Elder called out after the man in front stopped after getting hit.

"I'm fine, but this man is clearly an imposter, this is not something Wu Ming was capable of, are there any sects good with lightning magics?"

The group of five continued on while deliberating the true origin of this man they were chasing after. From the exchange Elder Wan had, he knew that this wasn't someone they could take lightly. He had taken out Zhu without any problem whatsoever, from the reports the sect members in the mine didn't even know that he had been done in till he was discovered by the guards during the cave in.

"Could he be from the Thunder-Storm Sect? But his techniques feel strange..."

The man was a mystery, he didn't fit any nascent soul cultivator that was known to them. They didn't think that he was a renegade or a new prospect as he was far too powerful for that.

"We'll just have to apprehend him and let him spill out the truth himself!"

"Yes, I bet the Sect Leader will reward us if we bring him in alive!"

The five people smirked as they didn't think that the man could get away from them, sooner or later he would tire himself out, and then they would surround him. None of these people thought that the unknown cultivator could handle them all on his own. He was also fleeing so this only confirmed their theory. Still, the quintet knew that an injured beast is the most dangerous one. So, for now, they kept their distance and continued with their ranged barrage. Due to this a long chase had ensued, when it ended no one knew.

...six hours later...

"Hey, what are you people even aiming at..."

Matt shouted while barrel rolling around the beam of heated energy that one of the chasing people fired at him. This wasn't all as a gale of wind blades chased after him the second he evaded the first attack. The people behind him were fuming with anger as the man that they were chasing was quite the slippery eel.

...ten hours later...

"Hey you guys, why don't we talk this over some earl gray tea?"

The group of old farts raged, even more. They pelted him with various ranged attacks over and over again but the only thing that they were hitting was the rocky areas below.

"Damn, if I didn't know it better, I'd say you wanted to kill me!"

He dodged a fire blast to the face, then deflected a couple of sharp icicles that were the size of telephone poles. These Sect elders had various abilities and didn't really stick to one type of elemental attack.

"I'm feeling unwanted here, think I'll just leave!"

Matt shouted out and bolted forward, the group of Dark Palm Elders just shook their fists at him and continued with their chase. It might have looked like he was doing random things at the moment, but he still had a plan in mind. He was heading in a certain location, making sure that the other nascent soul cultivators were mad enough at him to not notice where that was...

Chapter 171

Spirit Spring City, in the main clan building.

A large number of Zhang Clan members were being noisy. They all had solemn expressions on their faces while discussing the next plan of action. People like Zhang Zhi were here as well, he had left Moonlight city to help Zhang Dong. By the time he was going past the Zhang Clan main base, the others had already been returning here on their large flying ships. He met up with them half away and escorted them back to the main Zhang Clan city.

The Zhangs weren't the only family here, the Huo Clan, as well as the Feng Clan elders, were all here. Their juniors were resting in other areas together with people that got injured. The individuals here were vaguely familiar with each other. The Zhang Clan members could not deny Feng Liena and Huo Qiang participation rights in this discussion as they had quite a heads up over them in cultivation. It was knowns that the two were on good terms with the Patriarch, so they mostly everyone agreed to let them participate.

"How is Elder Jin's condition?"

Zhang Zhi asked while looking to the side to some of his family clan elders that were wearing white medical robes.

"He is stable, his body has fully recovered but..."

The person responding was quite an old looking doctor, his white beard reached all the way to his navel.

"But?"

Zhang Zhi narrowed his eyes while frowning, he didn't like the tone of that reply.

"There are no injuries on the grand elder's body, but he still isn't waking up, he is in a coma, we don't know why..."

The old man's forehead started glistering with sweat while he was answering the sole core formation elder from their clan. He was just a simple foundation establishment elder and didn't know what was wrong with Zhang Jin.

"It was that Yang Kai... he did something with the old man's soul!"

Huo Qiang spoke up while slamming his fist down on a nearby table, the table not being able to contain the force and cracking into several pieces. The other people in the vicinity quieted down, while Feng Liena shook her head along with the other two core formation cultivators that were next to her.

Huo Qiao stepped forward while coughing into his hand while trying to get the attention away from his rowdy young master.

"Yes, Yang Kai from the Dark Palm Sect performed some kind of demonic technique on Zhang Jin. Luckily the Zhang Patriarch managed to return your Elder's soul... I think. We will probably need to wait for him for a more throughout explanation."

The Zhang family members' eyes gleamed slightly at the mention of their favorite Patriarch, but then they remembered the situation they were in now and went back to their gloom.

"He told us to gather here, has there been any word of his whereabouts?"

The Huo elder posed the question that was on his mind, he was still apprehensive about coming here instead of the city his clan was located in. He couldn't go against his young master's orders though, so he followed him here.

"We tried contacting the Patriarch, but he is out of range of the communication treasure, he must have been traveling in the opposite direction of the city..."

Another side elder chimed in, the communication jades that people were using in this world had a limited range. The one that the Patriarch had was already an upgraded product. But even it wasn't able to cover the whole area of the Azure Dragon empire that they were in, things like satellites that furthered the signal didn't exist in this world yet.

There were devices akin to telephone towers, but they were placed by the governing sect and they would need to get their approval to use them which wasn't possible.

"Is that so..."

"Think we'll have to wait for Senior Dong to arrive, I trust that he will arrive just as he promised."

Feng Liena's sweet voice was heard from the side, the woman was sitting down with a couple of her family members. The old granny from the wind clan was already sending communications towards their own city. The information about the Dark Palm sects further movements was paramount, for now, they didn't get anything substantial besides some rumors that didn't go anywhere.

"That's a given, Senior brother wouldn't lie, if he said that he would be here he will."

The red-haired Huo master spoke out with a cheerful tone, but this didn't change the atmosphere in this large room. The biggest question on the mind of the people here were the Patriarch's whereabouts. Also if he was still alive and if he was strong enough to go against this behemoth of a sect himself.

At this time, somewhere in Dark Palm Sect territory, the man that the people of Spirit Spring City were longing for was busy dodging more Qi attacks.

"You old doo-doo heads never give up, do you?"

He chucked a spear of concentrated lightning Qi at the group behind him. Three of the elders instantly reacted, they placed themselves in a triangle formation with one person on top and two on the bottom. The air rippled and an energy shield appeared, the moment the golden spear of lightning collided with the barrier, the golden light vanished and the attack faded.

The quintet of old nascent soul monsters had been chasing this man for a couple of days now. They had gotten used to his attack patterns and knew well how to deflect or defend them by this point. The long chase was slowly getting to them though, they were people that had a short fuse.

The man kept egging them on with strange insults and they couldn't shorten the distance at all which put the group at a deadlock. Zhang Dong that was fleeing couldn't escape but the five elders couldn't catch up to him either. They all were nascent soul cultivators and even with Zhang Dong's Qi reserves getting lower he could still flee for quite some time and his pursuers knew this.

"We must seize him!"

"This farce has been continuing for far too long!"

Matt moved his attention forward and looked at his system window. He set up a waypoint for a certain location and was rushing towards it. If his plan worked well, then he wouldn't have to flee anymore and these five stooges would be dealt with, or at least busy with something else.

His enhanced vision picked up on a large structure. It was a large wall akin to the one that you would see back in China back on his mother planet. It was much wider and larger though and had large lookout towers spaced out through it.

'There... I'm close to the border... time to give those acting skills of mine another go...'

"TIS I GRAND ELDER WU MING, LET ME THROUGH!"

At a time like this, he wished he had the cash shop, buying skills that would help him get out from situations like these would make things much easier. Still, the teleport feature would be enough for now he just needed to make his next action stick.

He flew past the large wall and ignored the lookout towers as they still belonged to the Dark Palm Sect. The people on the walls recognized him and didn't activate the protective formation as Wu Ming was quite a famous sect elder. What he was looking for was a similar type of structure that was just one kilometer away from this wall.

"STAND WITH ME, BROTHERS AND SISTERS, LET US DESTROY THIS WEAK DEMON SUBDUING SECT. THE TIME HAS COME TO ERADICATE THESE WEAKLINGS. FOR THE DARK PALM SECT!!!"

His voice filled the whole area, anyone far and wide could hear his proclamation of war against the Demon Subduing Sect. He was still wearing the Dark Palm elder robe of Wu Ming and still had his appearance. He had flown to the bordering area of the two sects that were opposing each other. He wasn't sure what the deal with these two powers was, but he didn't care. The important thing was that the other party was a similarly strong faction and they were hostile with the people that were chasing him.

The four elders that were hot on Zhang Dong's heels noticed that they had reached all the way to the border area without even noticing. He had annoyed them all well enough for them to not notice where they were headed.

"What is that person doing..."

"Oh no... he still has Wu Ming's appearance! Quick stop him!"

There were some other Dark Palm members stationed here. This was the place that Elder Zhu was afraid of getting sent to when his spirit stone theft came to light. Not far away there was a nascent soul elder from the Dark Palm sect, he felt that there were people from his faction here so he decided to see what this was all about.

The same thing was happening on the other side on the Demon Subduing Sect's side. There was an elder in the nascent soul realm stationed on guard duty. He snapped out of his cultivation trance as he noticed someone powerful going past the border between them and the Dark Palm sect.

"What is this? You dare break the armistice?"

The whole place started buzzing with sound. Everyone on the Demon Subduing Sects side shouted out while pointing at a Dark Palm cultivator with salt and pepper hair. The man in question stretched his hand out while gathering a large amount of spiritual energy in front of it. In no time a large blade of wind formed, it shot forward right at the wall and collided with the protective formation that was activated by the other side the moment they heard the man's loud booming voice.

What followed was a barrage of multiple wind blades that caused the defensive formation that was able to defend against early-stage nascent soul attacks to buckle. Matt was using cultivation attacks uncharacteristic to his cultivation method as he didn't want the Demon Subduing sect to recognize him by them later on. The Dark Palm sect already knew that he was all about lightning, but not like these two forces trusted each other to believe any kind of info that they shared.

"Multiple nascent soul elders from the Dark Palm Sect are attacking us, send help immediately!"

A request for help was sent out the moment the enemy was spotted. The people here weren't prepared for such a huge attack though, their walls were barely holding up against one of the enemies old masters, what would happen if all of them joined in. The nascent soul master that was on the defending side managed to arrive in the nick of time.

"Divert all power to the defensive formation, we must last until the main sect sends help! We can't let this wall fall!"

The man diverted all of his spiritual essences into the formation while placing himself at a certain spot that acted as its core. He was only one person and the other side had six people of his caliber, the only thing he could do was to burn through his Qi and hope that help would come in time.

The five people that were on Zhang Dong's toes finally arrived, only to see their target kicking up quite a storm. Part of the defensive wall was already broken, the people on the other side were all frantically powering their defensive formation to last through this barrage.

"Happy to see you brothers and sister, don't worry I've already started with our planned assault!"

The five looked at the Wu Ming imposter and were about to shout back at him, but before they could the man's voice boomed out again.

"I WU MING FROM THE DARK PALM SECT WILL TRY TO GET TO THIS FORMATION FROM UNDERNEATH. YOU, MY FELLOW SECT MEMBERS, CONTINUE THE ASSAULT FROM HERE"

Again his voice was heard by anyone within a ten-kilometer radius. The moment he finished his sentence his body blurred and he dived into the rocky ground bellow while spinning like a beyblade. In mere moments he was gone leaving these five old people here, the group just looking at the partially damaged formation wall and the hole in the ground.

"What? ..."

"We must catch him and discuss the situation with the Demon Subduing sect, he won't be able to get past this formation alone and now he can't run!"

The leader of the group spoke up, not sure what the man was trying to achieve. If they apprehended him they could simply clear things out with the other party, they weren't fools so they should see it their way.

"Wait... he... he vanished? I can't feel his Qi anymore, how can this be!"

The five looked a the hole beneath them, just a second ago they could clearly feel the man's spiritual signature. But now, there was nothing.

"He couldn't have just vanished, just like his disguising technique he must have used something to hide his presence, find him!"

Two of the elders dived right into the hole, he couldn't have gotten far and his disguise was just a third rate skill. This other technique shouldn't be a problem either is what these elders were thinking.

The two returned after a minute, their heads lowered one of them scratching his neck.

"He... he wasn't in the hole... it didn't even go in that deep..."

Chapter 172

Spirit Spring City.

Zhang Xue and Zhang Liu weren't invited to the discussion that the elders were having so instead they were sitting in one of the rooms at their estate. The two were direct descendants of the previous Patriarch and now were the disciples of the current one. Their living expenses were covered by the clan and they had many servants along with a large mansion.

The siblings weren't alone though, people like Huo Kong, Feng Nuana were also here. Besides those two there were some other male and female cultivators of the younger generation around. Some from the Huo Clan while others from the Feng Clan that were accompanying their respective young lords.

Zhang Xue had invited them to over to stay in their guest house. The two other clans were placed in various locations of the main clan estate, but some had gathered here while they waited for word to arrive from their elders. Nuana and Kong, in particular, were people that these two Zhang clan members had gotten to know during the testing period. Liu was a bit hesitant about inviting the Feng Clan girl, but the small sister of the Feng Matriarch was slowly growing on him.

"When do you think that the elders will come to a conclusion? They still treat us like little kids!"

Huo Kong said out while leaning up against a wall with his hands crossed.

"Don't think they can come to a conclusion without Masters approval..."

Zhang Xue gave an answer while offering some tea to Feng Nuana and some of her friends. The group of girls was sitting around a table, tea in white porcelain cups was spread out on it. The short girl had braided her hair into twintails as they were looking light pink as always.

"This is quite fine tea... and this honey goes well with it..."

Nuana proclaimed while sipping on the drink, the tea back home wasn't as good as this, she wanted to ask how they managed to get it to taste like this but the timing was a bit off.

"Your master... are you really the disciples of that honorable person?"

Everyone looked at Zhang Xue that just smiled and nodded, the person in question was, of course, Zhang Dong that made a good impression on the juniors in this room.

"He was so admirable, how he delivered swift justice to that Yang Kai!"

The boys from the side perked up and joined in at the conversation. They all were there and managed to wake up just in time to behold Yang Kai's demise. They saw that dastardly Dark Palm Sect member vanish into fine particles. The image of the white-haired cultivator that had saved them was etched into their mind, they would never forget his gallant figure till they died.

The conversation shifted to the Zhang Patriarch, the kids started wondering about just how strong he was in reality. The young cultivators started asking Xue and Liu about their master. They were barraged by many questions ranging from how tough their training was all the way to what sort of boots the Zhang Patriarch liked to wear.

"Do you think your master could give me some pointers..."

Huo Kong asked Liu, the animosity from his voice that he used to have long gone. The red-haired youth had seen how righteous this man was while protecting Feng Nuana and was now seeing him in a new light. That he was the older brother of the woman that he had a thing for also was a big factor.

"Master giving pointers? I'm not sure he is versed in fire techniques that much. But he is a master of hand to hand combat!"

Zhang Liu stifled a laugh while trying to think about what his master would do. He was feeling quite proud of being his pupil, everyone in the room was looking at him with sparkles in their eyes. Having a mentor that was at the nascent soul level was something that these youths had been dreaming every day.

This peaceful atmosphere didn't last for long as it was interrupted. While they were chatting, they heard a loud thud and the sound of pottery being broken. The loud noise was preceded by a flash of light coming from a large side closet. This was also the place that Zhang Xue stashed most of her tableware and her tea sets.

This closet was to the side and there was no entrance to it from anywhere besides the room it was in. The people in the room looked at each other, wondering why there was a flash of light and a shift in spiritual energy coming from there.

"Is it a mouse or a rat?"

The girls backed away slightly, the most logical conclusion was that some kind of spirit beast sneaked into the closet and was kicking up a racket. It also could be some kind of intruder that was hiding in there before they entered the room. Due to this suspicion, Huo Kong and Zhang Liu reacted in unison while nodding at each other.

The two youths slowly shuffled their feet towards the sliding door, the people behind them quieting down. Kong placed his hand on the door ready to slide it open, Liu was on the other side his hand raised and ready to deliver a devastating blow to anyone that might have been spying on them. The people behind them gulped as Liu nodded, this prompted Kong to slide the door open his fist also raised the tension in the air high.

The moment they slid the door open cracked and broken teacups and saucers poured out. Inside was no assassin or demonic mouse beast whatsoever. There was a peculiar person that the people here were already familiar with. The man was wearing a characteristic white robe that had armor parts like metallic gauntlets and shoulder pauldrons. Yes this was the Zhang Patriarch, Zhang Dong had used the system's teleportation method to appear here where his disciple Zhang Xue was.

'Blasted thing teleported me into a closet.'

There he was, stuck in a small space barely large enough to support his height and width. He had a large white pot on his head that was slightly cracked. Shattered pieces of what looked to have been expensive tea sets were riddled all over the floor and were falling out from the broken shelves behind him.

The people in the room were stunned, Huo Kong and Zhang Liu were shocked and stopped mid-movement their fists raised in the air. Matt looked at the two youths that were standing in front of him with one of his eyes. The other was covered with the pot on his head, he slowly removed it and placed it to the side only to see it tumble down into the rest of the broken pottery.

"M-master?"

Zhang Liu spoke out while lowering his fist, Zhang Dong moved his hand upwards just showing his palm in a way that indicated that he didn't want the youth to speak.

"You see... your Master placed many teleportation arrays around the Zhang Clan to have a way of escape... but I was in the middle of a dire battle with five nascent soul cultivators. While activating it the spiritual energy from the fight must have interfered with my technique and I ended up here..."

So he said, the people in the room just stared while his deep voice filled their ears.

'Did it work? Why are they being so quiet... should I just leave?'

Matt's palms became sweaty and his introverted personality started acting up due to being gawked at by a group of people. This felt a lot more intimate than speaking out to a large crowd that looked more like a big blob from the distance. In this situation, he was starting to feel nervous as people that he knew were staring him down.

"Ah, well then...I'll just..."

"Master!"

"It's really the Zhang Patriarch!"

"How stunning, he is even more handsome in person!"

"Teleportation? That's a nascent soul for you, how fearsome!"

The kids in the room quickly moved forward all in awe about this man. They were just discussing this frightening master and he was fighting five nascent soul cultivators at once. He didn't look like he was injured so he must have made his escape, or even managed to slay some enemies in their eyes.

Zhang Xue moved over to where Zhang Dong was standing and together with her brother gave her master a bow.

"Disciple Zhang Xue greets Master!"

"Disciple Zhang Liu greets Master!"

Matt had the urge to scratch his neck after the two acted so formally. Before he could react the siblings looked behind them, glaring slightly at the people in the room. The youths picked up on the ques almost instantly and quickly bowed to the senior member.

"We greet you, honorable Senior!"

Everyone started bowing and showing their respect before him, this show of honor only made Matt want to get out of this room sooner. Even during these two years, he didn't really get used to this respect that these people showed him. He had what you might call a case of imposter syndrome, feeling like he didn't deserve all of this due to how he gained this power of his.

"It's fine, you can relax."

Matt wanted to sigh, but before that, he looked at his two disciples his voice sounding solemn.

"How is your grandfather doing? Did you arrive without any problems?"

Xue's and Liu's smiles quickly turned upsidedown after they heard the question. Xue lowered her head down while Liu stepped forward to give his master the bad news.

"Grandfather hasn't awoken, the physician said that he is in a coma and when he will awake is unknown."

"Is that so..."

Zhang Dong nodded slightly and then looked to the side.

"Could you guide me to where he is now?"

Xue nodded and moved in front of her Master.

"Follow me, Master. Uncle is resting in his own residence, other members from the family are tending to his needs."

Xue in front, Zhang Dong in the middle, and Zhang Liu in the back. The three white-haired cultivators went out, the other people in the room were silent and had enough tact to know what this was a family matter. They somehow knew who they were talking about, the man in the black suit of armor was also seen at Jade Grass City.

Though after the door closed, the people that were left inside became quite chatty. Huo Kong and Feng Nuana decided to report this to their family members, the man that everyone was waiting for to arrive has finally shown up. He would probably be the answer to this predicament they were facing and the only person that could realistically protect them.

After leaving the room, Matt continued walking after his female disciple. Grandpa Jin was resting in the same mansion that Xue and Liu were living in, it was quite large and housed a lot of the core family members from the main branch. Their arrival didn't go unnoticed, Zhang Dong's appearance was widely known and soon enough the whole place was abuzz.

"The Patriarch has returned!"

"Quickly send the information to the elders, the leader is back!"

Word of the glorious leaders return quickly echoed through the entire main clan base. The first ones to be alerted were the people that were holding the meeting of the elders. Almost instantly all of them stormed out, not even waiting for their Patriarch to arrive. Everyone was far too stressed, they needed answers about what they were going to do. They needed to know if Zhang Dong, the man that had already shown that he could work wonders was confident in achieving a new one.

On the other hand, while people were storming towards him Zhang Dong was standing before the large mansion that supposedly his grandfather was resting. The area he was in was a large outside garden, the problem wasn't in that though. For some reason, there was a massive gathering of people here and even though they came in various shapes and sizes, they all seemed familiar in some way.

"These are direct family members that had come to pay their respects to Grandfather."

Zhang Xue spoke out while alerting them to the Patriarch's arrival. The people moved to the side, knowing that this was the clan leader as well as their family member.

"Greetings Senior Uncle dong!"

"Greetings Patriarch!"

Matt moved his head over to Liu slightly as he asked.

"Why are they all here and why do they feel so familiar..."

Zhang Liu looked to the side with a solemn expression at the question but answered promptly with a slight sigh.

"They are all related to us and have a similar upbringing as you Master has, they...they are all related to Grandfather..."

Matt looked between Liu and the crowd, there were well over a thousand people there. And quite a lot of them had similar facial features to Zhang Jin's. He put two and two together, his mouth gaping wide at the realization.

'How many kids did this old bastard have!'

Chapter 173

Matt looked at the masses of people that parted to the sides. He placed his thumb and his index finger on his glabella while closing his eyes.

'What is this...'

He didn't feel like talking so he just moved forward, his destination the room that Zhang Jin was resting. He could feel the piercing gazes of all these family members each one feeling like a little prick to his soul. Thankfully he had his tranquil will technique, which saved him from losing his cool.

'Am I directly related to all of them?'

The garden he had to go through had a nice brick road and even a small bridge, a clear spring with koi fish was right under it. Due to the size of the whole area, the uncomfortable walk continued. The people that parted for him came back together the moment he walked forward. They all kept their eyes on Zhang Dong's wide back as if they were expecting him to produce a miracle just as the rumors said. He could even hear the younger ones whispering, not aware that an expert of his level had enhanced hearing.

He finally arrived at the door but before he could open the gates that would save him from this uncomfortable situation they sprung open themselves. Inside he saw more people, the most glaring thing about them was that they were all of the female gender and varied by age. It didn't take a genius to figure out who these women were.

'That's quite the varied range of tastes you got there gramps...'

One of the ladies moved forward, she looked quite refined. She had pure black hair that hung over her shoulders from the front as well as in the back. Her facial features were soft which made her look like the gentle type. Even though she was hiding it, he could tell that she was wearing quite a bit of makeup. Her age was unknown to him, but he wouldn't be surprised if she was over a hundred. She gave Zhang Dong a bow of respect before speaking out.

"Lord Patriarch, please save my husband!"

'Husband? So is this his wife? ... at least the official one?'

He peeked behind the woman and could see some of the other women's eyebrows twitch the moment she proclaimed Zhang Jin as her husband. This was probably his main wife while the rest were mistresses, from what he knew this wasn't anything out of the ordinary. Powerful men tended to have a couple of mistresses here and there, even children with them. The main wife was the one with the most power, she was mostly the one that tended to the house matters. Sometimes she even decided on the budget and who got hired.

While he was thinking about his reply another lady stepped up, this one looking younger. She was taller with a 'wilder' look compared to the first one. Her hair was long and crimson and fashioned into a long ponytail. The woman moved opposite the so-called main wife and greeted him as well.

"Please nephew, save your grandfather!"

The first woman squinter momentarily at the red-head, probably due to her acting too familiar with their Patriarch. Matt had spent some time in this city but his quarters were far away from Zhang Jin's mansion. His grandfather had tried inviting him for a family get together here and there but he always refused. He didn't like spending time with other people that he didn't know. Even back in his old life he mostly found himself in the corner of a barbecue while the other family members were talking.

'Nephew?... is she my aunt?'

He looked between the two women, he already realized that there was some kind of faction rivalry going on here. The ladies split into mostly two groups and stood behind the ones that came forward. One went with the courteous approach while the other went with familiarity, he wasn't sure what was going on here but for some reason he really wanted to give his old grandpa a punch.

The two women looked at the man in front, his face was emotionless as always. They took the hint and didn't press him, the Patriarch was known to be a man of few words. The took a small step back and just waited for him to reply.

"Um, where is grandfather located, bring me to him I'll see what I can do."

His two disciples were right behind him but they didn't speak up. Besides the two women that greeted him everyone else was keeping quiet, probably afraid to step out of line.

The main wife's character used a chance to slip forward and guided Zhang Dong to the room that Zhang Jin was being kept. It was a similar place to the one he was in after the secret ground ordeal. He was lowered in some kind of special spirit water that had various healing and nourishing capabilities that the clan was famous for. Thankfully he wasn't naked and was wearing something to cover his nether regions. After seeing the group of wives and children in the back, Matt was surprised that the pair wasn't ground into dust by now.

Even if the nature of this was quite peculiar, he was still worried about the man. He wasn't sure if his healing abilities were up to par. He was limited to the cultivation manuals he had procured from the secret ground and the ones he stole from the Dark Palm sect. The added knowledge explained some points, but it wasn't perfect by any means.

He moved towards the man that looked to be situated in what looked similar to a hot tub. He had some kind of breathing apparatus covering his mouth and nose and he looked to be asleep. The whole tub had a healing formation imbued into it, something that he came up with thanks to his holy elemental dao.

"Hm..."

The other people like the wife and the mistresses moved back, some nursing staff did the same. The watched as their Patriarch rubbed his chin and circled around the grand elder that was in a coma. The sleeping man hovered up which gave the women in the room a scare. They soon realized that this was the doing of their leader, he was now in the nascent soul which made sense.

Zhang Jin was moved to a nearby bed his body wasn't dropped onto it though but remained hovering in the air. Tiny golden needles flew out from Zhang Dong's spatial ring and embedded themselves into the old man's body. He looked like a pincushion as the tiny needles lodged themselves into all of his acupoints from the front as well as from the back in one go.

The people looked on from the side in awe as Zhang Dong reached out with his finger. A tiny bolt of golden electricity shot out, the tiny arcs of light flew towards those needles that were sticking out. Everyone had to stop themselves from gasping, not wanting to disturb a master at their work and in fear that they would be blamed if they caused a blunder to occur.

The light show didn't take long as everything was finished within a minute's time. The acupuncture needles were retracted into Zhang Dong's spatial ring and Zhang Jin's body got lowered back onto the soft bed below. The white-haired man rubbed his chin and took a step forward, his hand going to his grandfather's wrist as he checked for his vital signs.

'Nothing seems to be wrong with his body... his soul looks stable as well...'

He was sure to examine Zhang Jin with his appraisal skill, he had used before right before he returned his soul and it had the weakened status. Now on the other hand, there was nothing and his system wasn't telling him that there was anything wrong with him.

'Could there be another reason that he isn't waking up? He couldn't be... no...'

Matt squinted with his eyes and moved over to the bed and was standing in such a way that no one could see Zhang Jin. He leaned down first and checked the man's breathing then went for the eyeball test, checking if it would react to outside stimulus.

"Hey, gramps... are you just pretending to be in a coma..."

He whispered into Zhang Jin's ear after going through more tests. The moment he spoke out he noticed a really faint reaction, that proved his point.

"Is it because you don't want to face all those concubines and mistresses that are gathered here..."

He felt an even stronger reaction from his good ol' gramps after whispering that into his ear. He wanted to give him a good smack right at that moment. The guy even suffered through that healing procedure to keep his act up. He would rather get poked with needles than face all the kids that he sired outside.

'I bet they are all here as their lively hood depends on his life...'

He thought to the large group. Zhang Jin was the top dog in this clan right after him and had a lot of cash. Even though he was a massive pervert and a horndog he always took responsibility for his actions. All the children that he sired were welcomed into the clan in one way or another. Some as servants, some as regular clan members, and in between. It all depended on their potential and also on the social standing of the mother.

'Makes sense, if he dies most of them besides the main wife could be evicted from the clan if they have no backing...'

He leaned back and returned to the small group of women that came forward with questions.

"Patriarch, is there a way to save my husband?"

Asked the wife.

"Great Nephew, will hubby be okay?"

Matt looked between the two women that soon turned to each other, if looks could kill then both of their heads would be exploding now.

'Ah, I feel sorry for these people... well at least they have food on the table...'

He squinted again while looking to his no-good casanova of a grandfather and made a decision. He pulled out a dagger, it looked plain but the sharpness of its blade was paramount.

"There is a way to save him, but the procedure will be painful..."

"Due to the dastardly demonic arts of the Dark Palm sect an excess of Yang energies has gathered in his body, this will cause long-lasting damage to him unless the problem is resolved."

The people gasped, this sounded serious but the Patriarch seemed to have something in mind so they listened.

"I will need your help in the procedure, but I need you to steel your resolve as it won't be for the faint of heart!"

The two women stepped forward without thinking for long, giving a quick nod.

"As the consort it is my duty!"

"Anything if it will help hubby!"

"Master, can we also do something!"

Zhang Liu and Xue stepped up, quite eager to be of use to their master and help their grandpa.

"I'm afraid that the scene will be too gruesome for your young eyes, this procedure involves..."

He stopped himself and looked at the motionless body of Zhang Jin, then back to the group of people.

"We must remove the excess yang energies from his body, there is only one way to do it in this situation as we have no time. We must sever the part that makes him a man as it produces the largest amount of yang energies!"

He did a slicing motion with the sharp dagger in his hand while the group of people took a second or two to process the information. Zhang Liu almost instantly leaned forward and guarded his nether regions by instinct. The women took a step back, even the two main wives were taken aback by this revelation.

"Yes my two disciples it's better if you step back, you don't want to see this. Don't worry he is in a coma right now, so he won't feel any pain and I will heal his wounds right after. Be sure to not let anyone inside the room, even if you hear some strange noises..."

Everyone besides the two women left the room and the two were given instructions to spread their hubbies legs so that Zhang Dong could perform the operation.

"Is this the only way Patriarch..."

"Don't worry aunty, I'm quite handy with a blade it won't even leave a scar. Grandpa already has a wonderful family, this is a small setback in the grand schame of things."

He moved over to the bed that Zhang Jin was in while smirking to himself.

"Now please spread his legs and remove the cloth that is covering his orbs, we will perform this swiftly so that he can recover!"

The two women looked at each other and nodded. They knew that having a eunuch as a husband would probably mean that their charm wouldn't work on him anymore. Still, it was better than him remaining in a coma forever or dying. They also couldn't really refuse the request of their Patriarch so they complied by spreading the legs of their hubby.

Matt could see that Zhang Jin's whole body began sweating profusely. He even noticed that his eyebrows started twitching the moment those two women grabbed ahold of his legs.

"Now, remove the cloth and I'll perform the operation, one swift move is all it will take!"

The sharp dagger glowed with golden light and looked like it was now heated up and ready for the strike. The people in the room knew that the moment that weapon came in contact with Zhang Jin's junk it would sever it in a fraction of a second. The windup came, one of the women grabbed the cloth covering Jin's man bits and was ready to pull it to the side.

"NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOooooooo STOPPPPPPPPPPP..."

Before Zhang Dong could swing his dagger his patient jumped up into the air, his hands going towards his legs to protect his little feller that he was proud of.

"I'm sorry Dong'er... please show this old man mercy, I was in the wrong!"

Matt just rolled his eyes at the man that was clutching his groin, the two women in the room baffled to the quick revival of their husband that looked to be fine and dandy now.

Chapter 174

The people from the outside heard a loud scream and they instantly knew that it was the voice of their grand elder, Zhang Jin. The people that were standing right outside wanted to charge in to see what was going on. Before the women could make a move they were blocked by Zhang Xue and Liu that stood in front of the door.

"Halt, Master said that he didn't want to be disturbed!"

The young man shouted out while flexing his cultivation level slightly. This making everyone stop in their tracks. The women dropped their heads and moved back, they couldn't go against a direct order of the Patriarch nor his direct disciples.

Back inside the room, Zhang Jin was curled up in a fetal position his hands grasping for his family jewels. Sweat was covering his whole body after he almost became a eunuch. He turned to his wife and his mistress, they were looking at him funny. He then glanced at his grandson that was deadpanning at him, his eyes slightly squinting the dagger still in his hand.

"Oh...ohhhh... it's a miracle!"

He quickly straightened himself out and stood up from the bed. He started laughing while flexing slightly to show that he was fully recovered.

"Dong'er you sure are the greatest healer in our clan!"

He looked all cheery and fine, you wouldn't think that this man was on the death's door just a second ago. The two women knew that something was wrong, even taking their Patriarch's healing Dao into consideration the reaction was far too overblown. Before they could barrage their naughty hubby with questions they saw a large hand moving between them.

"Okay, this has continued long enough, let me have some time in private with my grandfather."

The two looked at Zhang Dong and couldn't do anything besides bowing as they left. The cogs in their heads were already turning though, they wouldn't just let Zhang Jin off like this, he had to be punished. The people outside saw the two leave and started asking questions, they rejoiced to the news of the grand elder's recovery but also had to wait as the Patriarch had ordered no one to come in.

"Okay you old fart, stop pretending we both know that you were already awake the moment I walked into this room. This isn't the time for this, tell me what the hell happened back in that city. Also, why did you lie to me?"

Matt crossed his hands over one another and glared at Zhang Jin. He was still mad that they didn't inform him about the dangers of going to the Dao festival. Though he also never told anyone that he was close to reaching the nascent soul level. The lack of communication between the leaders of the clan had caused this blunder and he was also at fault here.

"Yes, this Zhang Jin made a huge mistake..."

Zhang Jin went down to his knees or at least he tried, some kind of strange repelling force kept him from doing so. This was Matt who wasn't in the mood to watch a two-hundred-year-old grandpa kowtowing before him.

"This..."

Zhang Jin's eyes bulged as he stared, he could feel it, this was a nascent soul level of power. When did his grandson become this strong, was he hiding it from them?

"Yes, I've reached the nascent soul realm recently. This is also the reason why you are alive now."

Zhang Jin only regained his senses not too long ago. The people around him didn't say anything as they were more concerned about his health. He was also weakened, almost close to being in a crippled state. He had noticed that a huge number of his offsprings and concubines had shown up. These people were being kept off the main estate where he only had his main harem members.

The old man was keeping most of his side kids out of sight, not really wanting any infighting to break out between his huge family. But now they were all here and he wasn't sure how to handle this situation, he even heard his harem members fighting outside his room. He was in the middle of coming up with a plan of action, before his grandson walked in and now they were here.

"Did you think I'd cause some huge scene there?"

Matt rubbed his neck while thinking.

"Well, that might be true I'm not good at those formal gatherings... But still, you should have said something! I could have made some precautions, I could have been there sooner!"

Matt made sure to move his barrier around the whole room, not wanting all the other clan members to hear him shouting at the grand elder. He in response just stood there, just with some cloth covering his legs which made Matt's eyebrows twitch a bit. He gave out a sigh while looking at his grandpa that barely made it out alive.

"There is no time for this, get dressed we don't have much time. I might have bought us some time but the Dark Palm Sect will be at our doors soon enough, we must get ready."

"I'm sorry Don... no Patriarch, it won't happen again!"

The old man cupped his fist while doing a small bow, his expression resolute. He then felt his grandsons hand on his shoulder as he got closer.

"Well, uh... good to have you back old man, don't you go dying on me... but, please put some clothes on you old fart!"

Matt threw Zhang Jin a robe that was to the side, he had enough of seeing his grandpas bulge for a lifetime. The old man got dressed and Matt finally received the scoop on what happened during the Dao festival. Everything from the reason why Zhang Jin withheld information. The reason being that he was afraid that Zhang Dong's soft nature would cause some kind of offense against the sect. All the way to the fight with Yang Kai that was the cause of the whole predicament.

"So that's what happened..."

He rubbed his chin, he wasn't that angry at his grandfather. His reasoning wasn't so far fetched as him being there might have escalated things sooner, if that Yang Kai wasn't there in the first place nothing drastic would have happened. He also wasn't mad about his disciple stepping up to help his friend, even though that led to more things going astray in the process.

"I need to speak with Qiang and Liena..."

After getting the gist of what happened he decided to go through with his plan. He walked out first, his two disciples were still keeping guard. He nodded at the two siblings while walking through the door.

"The Grand Elder has recovered, you may enter the room at your own discretion. Xue, Liu let us depart."

Matt walked away without looking back, he could hear some women shouting. Unbeknownst to him a power struggle was happening on the Jin side of the family. The women were clamoring to treat their hubby and leave a good impression. This whole ordeal only reinforcing Matt's opinion about harems being too much of a hassle.

When he got outside the people were already kneeling with the path open. The reverence that these people were offering him was off the charts. He just increased his pace to get out of this uncomfortable situation, luckily his mental technique was keeping him relaxed. When he was about to leave the garden he could feel someone coming, someone in the great circle of core formation and they were being followed by others.

"Senior Brother!"

"Senior Dong!"

"Patriarch!"

"Honorable Leader, you have returned!"

Out of the frying pan into the fire, now he was faced with all the influential figures from his clan. Besides that there were also the Huo and Feng Clan people with them. Everyone was staring at him, he could tell by their piercing gazes that they were here for some answers.

"Um, let us move to a more quiet location first, then we will discuss the plan of action..."

Everyone nodded and they returned to the same place that they were previously in. Matt was surrounded by people from the elder generation from all sides. It just showed how much they were relying on him now, everyone even showed up to escort him to the meeting room and didn't just send their retainers for that task.

At the meeting room, he stood at center stage, all eyes were on him. If this happened two years ago, he would probably be a staggering mess but things were different now.

"Fellow Clan members, people from the Huo and Feng families, we face a big dilemma."

"Do we stay and fight, or do we leave and try to escape?"

"Before I make a decision, I would like to hear your thoughts on this."

He moved his hands behind his back, wondering what these native cultivators thought about the whole thing.

"Patriarch, do we have any other options than fleeing?"

"Yes, how can we oppose the Dark Palm sect..."

"Maybe we could seek refuge in one of the other large sect territories?"

"You fool, you think the other sects will just take us in and risk offending the Dark Palm sect?"

"Even if they allow us to stay, we will be nothing but slaves!"

"I say we fight!"

The conversation of the Zhang Clan members was mostly leaning towards escaping in some way. The only person that was for staying and fighting was Zhang Zhi. The other clans didn't have much to say, they didn't dare give input to someone that was at the nascent soul level even if they were given permission. The only ones that said something were the young Hou clan lord and the Feng Matriarch.

"I say that we stay and fight, it would be shameful to run."

Huo Qiang was down for a fight, as long as he had his senior brother to back him up he felt like they could do it.

"I trust that Senior Dong will make a just decision, the Feng Clan will stand with the Zhang Clan."

Feng Liena took a follower's stance, in her eyes the man called Zhang Dong would make the right decision and she would put her faith in him.

Matt nodded a couple of times, the opinions varied. It looked like the older people in the room were more inclined to flee or seek some kind of compromise, while the younger people like Zhang Zhi and Huo Qiang were all for fighting it out. Some of them like Feng Liena were unsure and left the decision to him.

Matt moved his hand up into the air, everyone in the meeting room quieted promptly.

"I have heard your opinions, now let us discuss something."

"Firstly, I have managed to dispatch two of the nascent soul elders from the Dark Palm sect, Wu Ming is dead and the man called Zhu has been crippled and won't be a problem anymore."

He gave a short recap of what he was doing for the past few days, mostly just giving information about the state of the sect they were going against.

"The problem lies in the lack of information, we don't know how many nascent soul cultivators the sect has. For now they might be busy with the Demon subduing sect, but there is no way of telling when they will knock on our doors."

The people in the room were quite happy to hear that their leader managed to take out two nascent soul elders from the Dark Palm sect. One was even in the middle stage which gave them much hope for the future. Though their morale plummeted after they heard that the enemy was able to send out five other nascent soul monsters from which their Patriarch had to flee.

"I think that there must be a limit to how many nascent soul elders the Dark Palm sect can realistically send out."

"That is true, they can't leave their main territory unprotected. If the other sects found it out, they would surely organize an invasion of their own."

"If we manage to hold out the initial attack, or even defeat some of those Grand Elders, we might not have to lift a finger afterward."

"Yes, but what if the other big sects decide to crush us along with the Dark Palm sect..."

Another discussion occurred, it wasn't a far stretch to think that if they managed to hold out for a while news to the other sects would spread. They might organize an attack to squash out a weakened enemy. Still, they could do nothing and just be at their enemy's mercy with no hope of winning.

"But Patriarch, how can we hope to last the brunt of their attack. Do you feel confident in battling five nascent soul cultivators, what if they bring more?"

All eyes were on him, it would be reassuring if their biggest fighter could just massacre their enemies but his chances of winning were slim in their eyes.

"I...I'm not sure... but I might not be the only one battling them..."

Zhang Dong glanced at Feng Liena and Huo Qiang, the two not sure what this was about.

"But first, we must create an official alliance with our allies... this isn't a battle of the Zhang Clan, we are all in this together. I wish for us to come together not as a coalition of clans, but as one sect... I wish to create a sect that will seek independence!"

Chapter 175

"You wish to create a sect?"

The people looked at Zhang Dong with question marks hovering above their heads. What was the point of creating a sect at this moment, that could even anger the other party even more?

"I know what you are thinking, but I assure you that it's something that must be done! I need everyone to swear an oath the sect so that we know who we can trust in the future."

'At least that's what says in my faction menu... I must change the name of the Zhang Clan to the sect first...'

Matt needed to change the faction to a sect and then let the other clan's join. He didn't think they would abandon their clans and join the Zhang clan, but if he made a sect then they could keep their old family names.

The people murmured with each other, creating a sect wasn't such an easy thing. The structure was different than a clan, for one thing, mostly anyone could join it without having to marry into the family. Most sects used some form of binding contracts to combat this, some didn't bother.

The people quieted down and started thinking, most of them were surprised, not sure what to think of this. Still, the proposal had some merit to it, it would be hard to trust the other clans if all of them weren't under the same banner. While the Zhang members were all on board as it was the proposal of their Patriarch, the others were skeptical, Huo Qiao was the one to speak up first.

"You want us to swear allegiance to you? But how can we do this without our Patriarch's approval? This isn't something that the people in here can decide upon."

In Huo Qiao's mind, there was still time to turn back. The people that were mostly involved in this fiasco was the Zhang and Feng Clan, their Clan might still have a way out of this if they just backed away. Their young master acted rashly, if they paid a fine then perhaps they would be left out of this.

"What can the Huo Clan even hope to achieve if we ally together against the Dark Palm sect, besides Senior no one can hope to contend with a Grand Elder from that sect."

The people started murmuring again, Huo Qiao was making sense. What could cultivators below the nascent soul level even hope to achieve here, they didn't even have any defensive or offensive formations nor treasures to aid them in the battle. The Zhang Patriarch was the only person that would be able to do anything. The rest would mostly just stare from the distance while being crushed under a nascent soul master's overwhelming aura.

"Qiao what are you even saying, If Senior brother wants to fight, we will fight!"

Huo Qiang looked at his bodyguard, Qiao in term frowned at his young master's words.

"You should be thankful that our Patriarch is giving you this offer!"

Zhang Zhi shouted out while staring at Huo Qiao with murder in his eyes.

"Calm down you youngsters."

Feng Maling stepped up to the stage.

"I can understand the young Huo lords eagerness, but you should think this through. Besides the Zhang Patriarch, none of us will be of much use. The sect war potential is far greater than ours, we wouldn't even be able to handle their core formation experts..."

The old woman looked at Zhang Dong, her showing deep concern.

"I ask you, can you defeat them all by yourself? Wouldn't it be more realistic to evade this battle and hide till the time is right?"

Matt rubbed his chin while listening, those were valid questions. The other didn't really add much to the plate, it would probably be better to hide everyone and run. Maybe he could sneak around and take out the nascent soul fogies one by one. The problem was that they were now at full alert and his disguise was infective against nascent soul cultivators. His other plan was patched together hastily and he would have probably chosen to run if he didn't manage to sack that spirit stone mine.

"Who said that I would be fighting alone?"

He looked at Huo Qiang and Feng Liena once more, it was time to reveal his plan to them.

"What if I told you, that I can help brother Qiang and sister Liena reach the nascent soul realm within the month, maybe even faster!"

The two people that were mentioned took a step back, their eyes blinked fast and their brows raised and curved.

"The nascent soul level within a month's time? This is no laughing matter, Zhang Patriarch! How can we believe such a thing to be possible!"

Feng Maling felt like her intelligence was being attacked, how could this young man claim to be able to heighten the cultivation level of their Matriarch within a month. How could reaching that realm be so easy?

"Senior Brother ... are you speaking the truth?"

"Senior Dong, how?"

Feng Liena and Hou Qiang looked at the white-haired man, their trust in him was the highest from the people gathered here so they were willing to believe in their claim.

"Everyone, please be silent for a moment."

Zhang Dong raised his hand up, as the people in the room became awfully chatty after his proclamation. He knew that he needed to present some evidence that would pull him over to his side and he had just the thing for that.

He asked for both Core formation experts from the Huo clan and Feng clan to come on over, Zhang Zhi was also invited. He then surrounded the group of five with his shield and blocked out anyone from peeking inside which raised a few eyebrows in the room. He pulled out a manual, it was golden from the outside and the calligraphy was at the highest level as he wrote everything down in it himself.

"Elder Maling, elder Qiao could you take a look at this and tell me what you think..."

He handed the book to the old woman, the bodyguard with the mutton chops walked over he was also curious about the whole ordeal, was this booklet the answer? The old woman started reading, while the elders in the room wondered what was happening behind that barrier. The old woman's hands started shaking, eyes bulged out in surprise, and her jaw-dropped in awe.

"T-this is... h-how... w-where did you get this..."

Huo Qiao snatched the book from the old elder ladies' hands, wondering what all the hubbub was about. He soon realized that what he was holding was something unfathomable. This here manual he was holding could cause a disaster to happen, as it was actually Zhang Dong's nascent soul cultivation manual, the same one that was in the immortal perfect grade.

"This... w-where did you find a legendary technique like this... is this really an immortal grade cultivation technique! This Dao is so deep..."

His eyes went bloodshot and he wanted to grab this manual and bolt it for the exit. It took some mental fortitude for him to calm down but his forehead was dripping with sweat.

"Yes, that is my cultivation technique and it's immortal ... perfect grade!"

The others gasped in surprise, an immortal grade was already a big deal, but this was even the highest level an immortal graded cultivation manual could reach, truly the stuff of legends.

"C-can I see it?..."

Feng Liena moved closer along with Huo Qiang, eager to take a look at the manual.

"If the other sects find out about it... the whole empire will be at war! This can never leak outside this room or we will all die a miserable death!"

The old Feng elder shouted out, everyone here knew that if any news got out this here place would be swarmed by any half-decent sect. Probably the Azure Emperor would be at their doorstep, they would all be dead by association. The small group of core formation experts started sweating, panic in their eyes.

"Please stay calm, as long as the word doesn't go out we will be safe. I showed you this to prove a point, I will procure similar cultivation manuals for both sister Liena and brother Qiang. You must understand there is a huge difference between a heaven grade cultivation manual and an immortal one..."

Matt started giving people the rundown. He explained that there was practically no danger in ascending to this higher realm if you had a fitting immortal grade manual. There would be no danger, they just needed time to advance.

"I will also supply them with the required spiritual energy to make the leap... they just need to study the manuals I will hand them and create their nascent soul..."

He moved his hands behind his back and nodded, the other people in the barrier looked to the Zhang Patriarch with vacant expressions in their eyes. No one knew where this man got this manual, but that explained how he had gotten to this level this fast. It was widely known that if the cultivation manual was of a higher grade then cultivation went smoothly. On the other hand, if it was of a lower quality, you could even end up with crippling yourself or shortening your life span.

"B-but h-how? You have more cultivation manuals like this one..."

He was half lying when he said that he had manuals for the two. He needed to use his system and combine some manuals to get something for his two friends first. He could exchange spirit points for crafting points, but first, he needed to know what the two were actually cultivating in, thanks to his analyzing technique that wouldn't really be a problem though.

"I don't, but my Master does... He allowed me to go through with this plan, but he imposed a condition of you joining the sect that I will create."

He had to somehow explain how he was able to acquire all those rare techniques, the easiest way would be to create a hidden master figure.

"Your Master?"

The Zhang Clan members had some reports of the Patriarch's 'Master's' sighting back in Moonlight city, but the man was mostly a mystery.

"Yes, my honorable Master, Wei Hung!"

Matt had to strain himself to not make his lips twitch or not to chuckle while saying that name. He went with this friendly doctor persona as he was already presumed to be his hidden Master by his own clan.

"With that, I want you all to swear an oath to join my sect! I have chosen Sister Liena and Brother Qiang to be the next Grand Elders of the new sect together with me! Time is of the essence, this chance is a once in a lifetime opportunity for your clans!

The people from the Feng and Huo clan's looked at each other. That manual was indeed unfathomable, if they were getting a similar one for free was there any reason to refuse? These people were quite simple, they weighted the pros and cons of each situation and then decided on the best path.

This was an immortal grade manual the Zhang Patriarch was speaking about, this was indeed a once in a lifetime chance for them to make it big. The Dark Palm Sect was a terrifying foe, but they knew how strong the Zhang Clan Patriarch was while only being at the early stage of the nascent soul. He was able to easily dispatch someone at the middle stage, they of course knew that that cultivation manual had something to do with it.

"Do you really need to ask? The Feng Clan will stand with the Zhang Clan and join the new sect as their eternal allies!"

Feng Liena was the first one to step forward, her head bowing before Zhang Dong as she accepted the offer. Huo Qiang followed suit, smacking his muscular chest with his hand while laughing.

"Haha, do you even need to ask, I and the Huo Clan will stand with you, if you get me into the nascent soul stage, that old fart won't be able to deny me anyway!"

Everyone agreed, one Zhang Patriarch wasn't enough to win this, but if they had three cultivators of this caliber their chances of winning skyrocketed.

"Well, if we all agree, then I would like to ask you for opinions about the sect's new name."

Matt took away the barrier that was blocking the view, the people outside were then promptly informed that their elders had decided to join with the Zhang Clan. They only needed to choose a name for their new sect.

Matt rubbed his chin as he wasn't sure what to name his new faction. He was criminally indecisive when it came to picking names and mostly went with silly sounding ones. This would be the name of his main faction from this point on, he couldn't just name it the broccoli sect for the laughs, he needed something official-sounding.

"Names, how about we name it after Senior's glorious name then?"

Feng Liena smiled as she gave her opinion, Huo Qiang was also for this.

"Yes, how about the Big Dong Sect? Sounds very fitting!"

If Matt was drinking something at this moment he would probably spit it all out after hearing that name.

"Hm, how about Grand Dong Alliance instead?"

"That also sounds very promising..."

The people in the room started proposing names, but for some reason, most of them had the word Dong in it, together with an adjective mostly to do with large and big things.

"Huge Dong Sect!"

"N-no please don't..."

Matt just facepalmed at all the names, the thought of changing his own name being a lot more enticing at this moment.

Chapter 177

Matt felt uncomfortable, those kids had those puppy dog eyes and were worshiping him like some kind of diety. He on the other hand didn't feel like he deserved this. If his communication skills were better then maybe this whole fiasco wouldn't have occurred and he would have years to cultivate himself and the whole clan into a great strong sect.

"That being the case, you need to alert your Master if you are facing odds like that!"

"I will give you two something with which you can contact me without the use of a communication jade..."

"Still, even though what you did was noble it was incredibly stupid, you endangered your whole clan and people close to you!"

Even though Matt agreed with the moral choice that he made. It was only that, the boy had no plan besides beating up that enemy in front of him. He didn't think about the master behind him, or that he was putting everyone there in danger by proxy.

"Y-yes Master, I did a great disservice to the clan..."

The young man that was all smiles after hearing the prise just a second ago went back to frowning.

"If it would be any other situation you would be punished severely, but we don't have time for such things now."

"Go see if you can help the other elders with the evacuation of the regular folk, you too Xue."

The clan for the past two years had been expanding, they created a large system of tunnels under the city for situations like this. They would have various traps along with being more or less a maze. This was to evacuate people and if someone decided to chase afterward they would find it hard to get through.

This was the time to use it, the low-level cultivators and non-combatants were useless and more or less dead weight in this situation. They needed to be evacuated so that the warriors in the city had less to worry about when the Dark Palm Sect finally arrived.

"Yes, Master!"

The two didn't stay for much longer, they agreed with everything their glorious master said. Matt started thinking that if he told them to jump off a cliff they would probably do it without even thinking.

"This devotion might be a double-edged sword..."

He shook his head, this wasn't the time to think about the consequences of being too devoted to one person. He needed to make those blasted skills! He activated his crafting abode and appeared withing the large area, various smelting devices all over the place along with some weapons that weren't quite finished.

"I need to get this over with quickly and then use the nascent soul weapon I got from Wu Ming to advance my cultivation!"

He headed to the spot where the skill combination device was. He already knew what kind of cultivation method the two used thanks to his analyzing skill, and it was something that they had taken from the secret ground. He had copies of those manuals right here along with his own that would be used. Before he started he quickly glanced at the two booklets as if checking if he really took the right thing with him.

The Sylph Empress Cyclone Manual [Heaven High Grade]
Flame Emperor Pure Yang Manual [Heaven High Grade]

"Okay, these are the ones... who comes up with these names..."

He arrived at the technique combining contraption that looked like a large desk with many small drawers in it. He placed the technique that Feng Liena used in first as the base, then his own Divine Golden Lightning Nascent Soul one was placed as the supplementary. This would produce a better version of her manual, but it depended on how compatible the two were with each other.

"Hope this works... what kind of name will this produce though..."

The Sylph Empress Cyclone Manual and Divine Golden Lightning Nascent Soul Manual are 69,420% compatible...

He looked at the compatibility percentage, it wasn't super high but it wasn't low either.

"Well, it's above 60%... almost 70% that's still good... guess I'll need to spend some points to improve it..."

Matt stared at the crafting screen, if he left it as it is the technique would end up an Immortal early graded one. But he didn't want it to just remain at the bare minimum. He started adjusting the sliders and clicking some options, the divine part of his own cultivation method wasn't very compatible with this, this was the first thing he dropped and focused on combining the lightning and wind components.

"I am using two types of Dao's with my own cultivation, so it shouldn't be a problem if she has that too... lightning and wind should be compatible..."

The options were clicked, he favored increasing the attack and speed of this technique dropping most of the defensive options in their favor.

"You don't need defense if you can dodge everything... but can't overdo it..."

The base manual was already focused on speed and long-ranged attack, he was just min-maxing a bit to give it even more power in that regard. In the end, after all the options were chosen and the technique was upgraded he remained with a manual in the immortal middle grade, but the advance grade for it was quite good at an A.

"Even with just this... I need to spend over 25 million points on this... will I have enough points to further their cultivation to the maximum so they can breakthrough?'

He started sweating, this was close to a quarter of his whole spirit point pool. He could exchange the points at a 1 to 1 ratio for crafting points so at least he didn't lose out in that regard.

"Here goes nothing..."

He activated the machine and saw it glowing. It took a minute for the rumbling to stop and the large drawer in the middle popped open with a green looking manual.

Ascended Storm Phoenix of the Thunder Winds Cultivation Manual. [ Immortal Middle Grade ] | This powerful immortal cultivation technique combines the Dao of lightning and wind to create powerful storms that consume anything in their path. The Soul-Beast fashioned from it will be a Storm Phoenix.

"Okay... that sounds nice...quite the long name there...let's move on to Qiangs..."

He pocketed the green manual and absorbed the knowledge from it into his system library. The next one in line was the Flame Emperor Pure Yang manual. He just replaced Feng Liena's old manual with Qiang's and looked at the options that were given.

Flame Emperor Pure Yang Manual and Divine Golden Lightning Nascent Soul Manual are 54,666% compatible...

"Worse but still not that bad... this is going to cost a lot more..."

He knew that Qiang was a close-range fighter that liked to use his large frame to overpower his opponents with large swings. So in contrast to Liena's speedy build, Qiang's came out quite tanky.

"Hm, does that make him the Tank of the party and Liena the backline caster? Guess I would be the all-around DPS or something?"

The cost of it all was even higher than what he had to spend on Liena's, costing him over 40 million in one go.

"Well, they are immortal techniques... I'm lucky that mine is in the perfect grade so it lowers the cost substantially."

He tried to see how much points he needed to upgrade a heaven graded technique to the immortal grade before. Without any good techniques to base it of, he would need to spend over 100 million points to just get it to the early grade. Though all things considered, that was still a low cost. The other sects would probably throw their spirit stone mines at him if he told them he could fashion them one for that price.

"Ah, the hard life of a rich person."

The new manual popped out in the middle, steam rising from it.

"Nice red color... these booklets have quite the cool designs..."

Plasma Ifrit Of The Perfect Yang Path Manual [Immortal Middle Grade] | This forbidden cultivation art combines the pure Dao of Yang with the chaotic lightning energies to produce a destructive force. The Soul-Beast fashioned from it will be an Ifrit composed of red plasma energy.

"Oh? Plasma! That one is neat... might be even cooler than mine..."

He imagined a large devil made from plasma energy fighting together with Qiang, next to it a wind Phoenix kicking up storms and in the back a golden dragon bringing in the pain.

"Yes... this could work..."

He had spent over half of his spirit point reserve but had managed to create two really good cultivation manuals. He absorbed the knowledge from this one to his library as well, later on, he could try using them as bases and fashion some nascent soul techniques for his two companions.

"I need to give them these two manuals and then cultivate on my own... I also need to remake the grand formation, it won't hold against those old nascent soul farts."

He remembered the large wall at the border, that thing could take some damage even though he was using attacks that weren't the strongest. They were still at the nascent soul level, he looked at this spirit point counter and would need to save some to upgrade the formation, and the biggest issue was the power source.

He exited his crafting abode and headed towards the clan's pocket dimension. He could hear people running around, the citizens were getting informed and evacuated even now. They all felt shocked that they had to leave, but they also felt reverence to the clan that was actually helping them evacuate in the face of danger.

Normally sects or clans didn't care about the general populace. When the Cheng Clan was fleeing from Moonlight city they took their core members and escaped. If the Zhang Clan turned out to be tyrants wasn't something they were concerned with. The citizens from Spirit Spring City would remember this, their trust into the clan and now sect was going through the roof while they all evacuated.

Matt appeared in the medallion space and saw Feng Liena and Huo Qiang. The problem was that the two were bickering again, he wasn't sure why but the two didn't get along too well. He wasn't sure what it was about, but he thought that it might have something to do with Qiang proposing to her once while having a hundred wives.

He was just in the time to behold Liena dancing around with the fans that he had gifted her, producing cyclone like winds that Qiang was finding hard to block.

"Hey you two, what are you doing!"

When the tanned girl saw Zhang Dong appear she stopped in her tracks, she was in the middle of her battle technique so she kind of fell on her butt afterward. This caused Huo Qiang to burst out in laughter.

"Hah, serves you right you violent woman!"

"Who you calling violent, you muscle brained pervert!"

The girl glared at the red-haired man, he in turn just smirked and shrugged. Matt quickly got between the two, his hand going down to help the gyaru up from the ground. This pocket dimension didn't look too great after he was done training, a lot of the ground was mostly destroyed and dusty from all the craters.

"You two... here Sister Liena let me help you."

He reached out his hand towards the lady, their eyes met. The moment they did Feng Liena's expression changed, she started fidgeting and her gaze focused on the hand that was presented to her. An uncomfortable silence followed where the lady just stared at the large manly mitt, only snapping out of it when Zhang Dong called out to her again in that deep manly voice.

"Is something wrong? Are you hurt anywhere?"

She finally snapped out of it and grabbed his hand, the moment she was pulled up to her feet Matt could have sworn that he could hear a sound akin to 'doki doki'

Matt might have been a dense person, but even he knew what this was. The woman was clearly interested in his and this wasn't anything getting acted out like at the secret ground. She was showing clear signs of a maiden in love, this revelation only causing Matt to stutter in response before his tranquil mind calmed him down.

"U-uh... right... I've got your cultivation manuals from my master... he said that he would help me out this once but he won't be helping us in the coming battle..."

'Hey, don't stare at me with those big blue eyes, this isn't the right time for this!'

Chapter 178

At a faraway location, you could see destroyed walls and chunks of rubble everywhere. It looked like a large battle took place, craters and cracks in the hard rocky ground were seen everywhere.

Up in the air, six people were floating on one side, they were looking in the distance where a group of five was staring at them from afar. Compared to the area around them these groups of people looked fine. They were glaring at each other but they were keeping their distance, both sides retreating.

"I propose a ceasefire... I think no one here wants to engage in an all-out war..."

The man speaking was Elder Wan, the strongest cultivator from the group that was previously chasing after Zhang Dong. After he attacked the border wall that belonged to the Demon Subduing Sect a fight broke out. The members from the Dark Palm Sect weren't here to fight their long-standing rival though, but after the misunderstanding, they had to stay to explain themselves before this got out of hand.

"You want us to believe that someone disguised themselves as Wu Ming to sew discord between our sects? Aren't you just afraid to attack!"

An elder man that was at a similar level as Elder Wan shouted out. He was holding onto a large saber and his face was full of scars. The Demon Subduing sect was a virtuous one and had a bad opinion of the Dark Palm faction. There were a lot of rumors that they were a demonic sect, but there wasn't any substantial proof. The two factions clashed here and there, but none were confident enough to go into all-out war.

"Don't try my patience Fan Ping, we from the Dark Palm Sect never turn our tails and run, but this was clearly a misunderstanding!"

The man named Wan shouted back at the other five people, his eyes going bloodshot after the others accused them of being scared.

"Please calm down, we will retreat to our side, there is no reason for this fight!"

The old woman cultivator from the Dark Palm side floated between the two shouting leaders. She gave Fan Ping a small bow and whispered some words into Elder Wan's ears.

"We can't fight the Demon Subduing sect while that cultivator is on the loose."

"He was strong enough to defeat Wu Ming, we must retreat!"

"We must alert the Sect Leader and the council!"

Elder Wan listened, his sect member was saying the truth. They couldn't let an unknown rogue cultivator run amok in their lands, he was the priority. They needed to go to their top bras and also examine the places that the enemy was seen before.

"My junior sister speaks the truth, we will reimburse you for the damages to your broken formation and wall."

Fan Ping stroked his beard while looking at the opposing faction. He knew that if they continued this fight deaths would be unavoidable. Taking some spirit stones for the destroyed walls and formation was a win in his mind. There was no reason for the two forces to clash here, everything did seem kind of fishy.

'They are probably telling the truth... but who was that man that caused this... we need more information...'

His eyes gleamed in a cold light while he looked down, this might have been something trivial but there was also a chance that it could lead to something.

"Fine...pay up and let's be done with this!"

The other side threw spatial pouch with spirit stones inside, there was enough to cover the costs. The two sides turned around and flew away, still they left more than one nascent soul elder on each side, just in case. The man named Fan Ping took out his communication jade afterward, he had to make some calls...

..................

Back in the Dimensional Regalia.

Huo Qiang had his mouth wide open, drool running down his chin, his hands trembling as he was staring at the red manual in his hands. Feng Liena was right next to him, her eyes were sparkling and she had a similar dumbfounded expression as her fellow cultivation brother next to her. The thing that snapped them back to reality was the cough from the white-haired man opposite them.

"I think you stared at them long enough... we should get on with it, time is of the essence!"

The two cultivators looked between their colorful manuals and then back to Zhang Dong. Their hands began shaking, the aura that was coming off these two booklets was unfathomable.

"S-senior B-brother are you sure we are allowed to read this?"

"Y-yes, t-this is just too much..."

Matt chuckled a bit, the two cultivators were acting like little kids. Their eyes were sparkling like a child that had received a toy for Christmas that they were waiting for long time.

"It's fine, you must cultivate this and quickly reach the nascent soul level, we don't have time!"

He moved over to Huo Qiang, his finger outstretched.

"For this reason, I will have to hasten the process... first, let me impart you the knowledge."

He had the Impartation of Knowledge skill, he had leveled it up to the pinnacle so he could force 100% of the techniques information into a given target. Though that what it was, information everyone was different and it would depend on them on how fast they could digest it. He placed his index finger on Huo Qiang's forehead and activated the skill, the red-haired man twitched as his mind was filled with the Plasma Ifrit Of The Perfect Yang Path knowledge. Matt also included knowledge about some of the Dao's that could be useful.

"W-what...?"

The man backed away and grasped his aching forehead, the pain subsided fast. He could then feel that somehow he knew the cultivation method now.

"S-senior Brother... this!"

"Yes, I can directly transfer the information of the techniques, it would take too long if you study it yourself. Keep the manual, for now, sometimes it helps to reread it yourself."

Huo Qiang quickly opened the booklet, he started reading and it was just as Zhang Dong said. He already knew everything that was written down here, but there still were some pictures that could come in handy if he got stuck. Qiang looked between the cultivation manual and Zhang Dong, his eyes going bloodshot.

"Huh?"

Before Matt could react he found himself in a bear hug. The man that was hugging him was larger and more muscular than him, plus he had a thing for not wearing much to cover his chest. He was now getting bearhugged by a buff dude that was wearing a tiny vest that was exposing his hairy chest.

"Hey, calm down, let me down!"

"You are my sworn brother for life, Uooohhhh!"

The man roared out while Matt pushed up against his face and slowly forced him away.

'God damn... use some deodorant dude...'

He pushed him back and due to him being in the nascent soul level, Huo Qiang was flung into the distance and tumbled a couple of times before coming to a stop. He was still laughing out loud while clutching the red cultivation manual like a starving man clutching some bread.

"S-senior Dong..."

Matt looked back, a Feng Liena with sparkles in her eyes was standing there. She fidgeted like a small child while hugging the manual against her large chest.

"Can I also receive your finger technique?"

"My finger technique?"

Matt looked down at his finger then back to the busty lady. She had closed her eyes and stuck her forehead out while looking up to him. He sweated slightly after misunderstanding what she meant and then placed his finger on her forehead. He imparted her knowledge for the Storm Phoenix cultivation technique. She gave out quite the cute low pitched sound during the process, then squatted down on the ground while holding on to her head.

"W-was it that bad?"

He was someone who got used to the headaches thanks to his system. He wasn't affected by it anymore but it seemed that other people like Liena weren't that resistant. He took the time that Liena was organizing her thoughts to peek at her status.

Name : | Feng Liena
Age : | 42
Faction: | United Sect of Elemental Dao
Cultivation : | Core Formation [Great Circle 3%]
Potential : | B+
Trust : | 78%

"Similar potential to my disciples, eh?"

"Only 3% progression this will cost a lot..."

He could see that she was under his new faction, the process could move forward now. He brought up his faction window, he had an option to search for people that were in it. He typed up her name and could see a similar status screen like the one he used for analyzing people. He selected her cultivation and was given the option for increasing her progress but this wasn't all.

This member has a high trust rating, it's possible to remove impurities in their cultivation, do you wish to start the process? Yes/No

Just like everyone else who used weak cultivation methods, people built-up impurities in their bodies. For instance, Zhang Jin that used a really low graded one had his progress halted at the early stage of core formation. It took a lot of resources to push him into the middle stage along with remaking his original cultivation manual.

'Nice... didn't know this option existed!'

Matt knew that the two were studying lower graded techniques, so even when they reached the next realm some of the impurities would remain. This would lower their power level in some way.

"Senior Dong?"

Feng Liena was already off the ground and had realized that she already knew what was written in the manual she was holding. She wanted to thank Zhang Dong that made it possible but found the man staring intensively in her direction while poking at the air.

"Ah... huh?"

Matt snapped out of it, the system window appeared directly in the line of sight of Feng Liena and made it look like he was staring at her with passion in his eyes.

"Ah sorry..."

"N-no it's fine..."

The awkwardness didn't last for long as Huo Qiang appeared from the side, his loud voice alerting the two to his presence.

"Ha, this cultivation technique is great... An Ifrit Soul-Beast, everyone will bow before my might, long live United Elements Sect!"

"Let us cultivate now, I can't wait!"

Qiang was ready to drop down into a lotus position and get to it, before he could go through with it Zhang Dong spoke out.

"We need to do something before that... if we do it normally this is going to take far too long, please take this first..."

Zhang Dong took out a round object, it looked like a marble that fit nicely into Feng Liena's hand. The woman looked at the item that was handed to her. It looked quite ordinary, a normal orb made from glass without any major features.

"Could you hold on to that and head behind that building..."

The woman looked at him for a moment but nodded. She believed that this item probably did something great and decided to follow the instructions. Though, why she was to go behind the building was a mystery.

"Are you in a safe spot Sister Liena?"

"Yes, Brother Dong."

"Okay, this might feel strange so please bare with it..."

Liena wanted to scratch her head, what was she supposed to bare with. Was this glass orb that she received some dangerous spiritual treasure.

"Something strangeeeeeeee?"

She screamed out, she started feeling pain all over her body. She could feel that something was happening, her whole body spasmed as she dropped down to her knees.

"Please bear with it, it should be over soon!"

She heard Zhang Dong's voice from the distance and followed the instructions. She clenched her teeth while the strange feeling took over her body. Besides the pain, she started feeling nauseous as if she was coming down with stomach flu. She couldn't hold it in as vomit shoot out of her mouth covering the ground with black like ooze.

The whole process took about five minutes and left a large puddle of black goop behind. Liena felt really weak but refreshed at the same time. The black stuff that came out of her body had a foul odor and she instantly knew what this was.

'Impurities! All of this...?'

She felt stronger her body was cleansed, her cultivation path reinforced by this strange glass bead that had shattered into pieces while she was going through the process. While she was trying to get a grip on the situation she heard Zhang Dong shout out.

"If you head back there is a hot spring you can use, you probably need a change of clothes after that."

She realized now why he told her to go behind the building. She had a foul odor to her and looked like a mess, she needed a change of clothes. She smiled a bit and then moved towards the area where the springs were. During this time Huo Qiang received the same treatment his loud shouts could be heard all around the floating island in the pocket dimension.

Chapter 179

Huo Qiang was on the ground in a pile of black goop, breathing hard. His muscular body twitched after the transformation and he was already feeling a lot stronger.

'Surprisingly his trust in me is even higher than Liena's...'

Qiang was but a simple cultivator, you gave him some treasures and cultivation manuals as gifts and he would treat you well. This wasn't over though, this was only the cleansing of impurities process he still needed to increase their cultivation level. He took out one more of those glass beads which were just regular glass. He was using them to hide how this process was working, hoping that the two would attribute their change to the balls of glass instead of his system.

"Ohhhh... Senior brother...t-this is!"

While Matt was looking at the status window and thinking about dumping spirit points into Qiang's cultivation the man in question started charging at him. He opened up his arms wide and his face was all smiles, he was clearly going for another hug. Problem being, that he was covered in black sludge that stunk like dung.

"Hey, get back, you stink!"

Huo Qiang came to an abrupt stop as he hit something akin to an invisible wall. His nose was squished and his hands spread almost in a T-pose.

"Brother, let me give you a hug, you have gifted me so much and I can't ever hope you ever repay you!"

He started squirming and pushing against the spiritual wall that Matt had formed with his Qi. He was so frantic that he even started biting it but wasn't able to make it budge even an inch.

"Calm down... the process isn't even over yet...let us just get on with it..."

He didn't think that he could reason with this man, his eyes were bloodshot and he was looking at him like he was a juicy piece of meat. He promptly clicked Qiang's cultivation option and started dumping points into his cultivation.

"W-what is happening?"

The man covered in black sludge backed away while looking at his own hands. He could feel his power rising, his muscles twitched and his core spun around as it exuded more and more power. Even when a cultivator entered the great circle of a realm, it wasn't the end. There was still space to improve, both of them could still boost their cultivation to the maximum and at 100% of it, they would reach a tipping point referred to as the half step point.

This was a moment at which the cultivator had the highest probability of reaching the nascent soul level. Most people couldn't push all the way through to that point though. If they tried to push onward they would mostly not be able to reach the higher realm and the only thing waiting for them was a backlash and cultivation regression.

Huo Qiang felt power rushing into his meridians. The Qi that was going into his body was incredibly pure and it caused him to tremble in excitement. The Flame core that he was using spun around and started expanding, it burned at an incredible rate even making the man's body exude steam. He looked like a ripe tomato which caused Matt to hesitate momentarily.

'Well... that looks peculiar... good that I tested it with him first... guess when I go over to Liena I'll insert the points slower...'

At the end of the procedure, Huo Qiang collapsed to his knees, his body was bulging and radiating strength. With time this subsided and the irritated muscles went back to their normal shape.

"I... This power..."

Huo Qiang roared out and bolted forward, he had his core formation cultivation pushed into 100% and had all of his impurities removed. He felt fantastic and he wanted to test out his newfound strength. This of course meant that he needed a target, which was Zhang Dong.

The same transparent shield appeared between the two, the red-haired man waiting for this moment. He gathered all of his fire Qi into his right fist that shone in a crimson light.

"Take this, Flame Emperor's Pure Yang Destruction Fist!"

The attack flew forward and there was a massive explosion that rattled the whole floating island. Feng Liena was washing up at the moment, the water in the spring splashed in her face and made her hair wet.

"W-what is happening, are they fighting?... why is Qiang this strong?"

Matt raised his eyebrow as he saw a bright red fist coming for him, he placed the same transparent Qi shield that had about the same defensive power as a regular nascent soul cultivator in the early stage. He watched as the fist continued to push against this barrier, the man that the fist belonged to shouted like a madman while inserting all of the Qi he could muster into the attack.

'...Crack...'

"Hoh?"

Matt raised his eyebrow as he felt the shield cracking slightly, but before it could give out Huo Qiang finally run out of steam. He suffered a small backlash from using too much Qi and his fist fractured in a couple of spots.

'Geez... why did he need to go that far...'

He fell back onto his back, his fist shattered but his spirit not broken. He looked up into the air, the hand that was fractured held up high into the air. He looked at the blood that was flowing a grin plastered all over his face.

"Ha Ha Ha! I heard it... it cracked! My attack reached you!"

Matt moved over to the laughing muscle head, he was apparently satisfied that he managed to cause a slight crack to the shield that was at a nascent soul level.

"You sure are an idiot... but that's not necessarily a bad thing."

Zhang Dong moved out his hand towards Huo Qiang who in response leaned forward and grabbed it. He helped his red-haired friend up to his feet and used this chance to insert his holy Qi into the fractured fist.

"You should really wash up, you smell like a Sludge Beast's asshole."

At that remark, Qiang moved up one of his armpits and gave it a whiff. He then looked back at Zhang Dong and gave him a shrug, not really seeing a problem there.

"This is the smell of a warrior Senior Brother, nothing to be ashamed of!"

"Yeah sure... could you and your 'warrior' smell go washup and then cultivate, we really don't know when the Dark Palm sect will be here."

At about this time Feng Liena appeared again, she was wearing a different robe and her hair was flowing behind her back while being slightly wet.

"Brother Dong, what was all this racket?"

She looked at Huo Qiang that was standing next to Zhang Dong, the foul odor that was coming of the buff cultivator could be smelled from even here. She came to a stop and realized that Huo Qiang had gone through the same process as she did, but he was also much stronger than before. She thought that Zhang Dong had to have done something to him besides the cleansing process, as she had gone through with it like him but her power level didn't go up this much.

"Ah, we were just finishing up here, I will help you advance your cultivation now as well."

Matt turned around to Feng Liena that was looking quite lovely with those loose hanging wet locks. His eyes wandered all over her body which probably didn't go unnoticed.

"Hah, you see this Liena! I could take you out with a pinky now!"

Qiang laughed while walking forward and towards the springs to wash up as well. The woman cultivator glared the man with no tact and just turned her head to the side while snorting. Matt just rubbed his head wondering why these two never got along with each other.

"You two... you will be the next Grand Elders of our sect..."

Qiang still laughed and Liena still snorted back, the two were clearly at bad terms which would be hard to fix. He felt like he would have to mediate things between these two in the future.

'Hope they don't start fighting at critical points...'

"Well then, let us get on with it Sister Liena..."

Feng Liena stood tight next to Zhang Dong, they were an arm's length away from each other. The foul odor was gone replaced by a perfume that smelled like cherries.

"I am ready Senior Brother!"

She looked resolute, she closed her small fist and jumped slightly forward. The problem was that when she did that, it caused her voluptuous mountain peaks to bounce. This delivered a critical hit to Matt's psyche as he suffered a massive mental attack.

"Tranquil Mind don't fail me now!"

He gulped and then coughed into his hand, he had a pair of sparkling blue eyes in front of him that belonged to quite the tanned beauty. He placed his hand on the girl's shoulder as if he was going to insert the Qi by hand. He was totally not taking advantage of the situation, he was far too much of a gentleman for such things. He only wanted to mask the fact, that he was doing it with the faction option of his system.

"Okay, I will begin the process now... this might feel strange..."

He started inserting spirit points into Feng Liena's cultivation. The percentages rose slowly as he didn't want the woman to suffer through the whole process just as Huo Qiang did. Her reaction was different that was for sure as instead of screams she started giving off some sensual moans.

"Oh...Senior Brother Dong...t-this f-feals s-strange...ahhhhh~"

Matt raised his brow and started sweating slightly. He looked down at the fidgeting woman that started panting. Her face was all red and she was giving out various lewd sounding sounds. He even wanted to pull his hand back for her to take a rest, but before he could do that she grasped his forearm while leaning forward.

"S-so much spiritual energy...uhhhh..."

She held his forearm with both her hands to support herself. Her legs were shaky and she felt like she would fall down if she didn't do this. This caused Matt's mind skill to go into overdrive as due to this lean, she could see quite a bit of tanned cleavage.

'Why do they wear those robes with so much space cut out...'

He gulped, even more, his heart racing as he tried to calm his little brother down. He was still a man and even though he had gone past his virgin phase, his dating experience was almost zero. The fling with the merchant daughter happened way to fast, which resulted in him not gaining much from the ordeal.

'I am but a rock in an empty field... nothing can phase me... I am one with the world...'

He chanted while closing his eyes, but he still needed to open up to click the blasted system window.

'Yes... everything is one... everything is...boobs...yes massive and bouncy...wait no '

The moment his eyelid rose he got a glimpse of more bountiful cleavage. His eyes opening wide while the woman leaned forward even further, so close that he could even smell her shampoo.

'Noo... I will get through this... I must... don't you get exited down there...'

He really didn't need excitement now, this would cause quite the loss to face, he would be able to face this woman down the road if she saw him pitching a tent. He decided to insert the rest of the points in one go even though they were only a bit over 50% done, this caused a drastic change to Liena's disposition.

She screamed out loud and just fell face-first into Zhang Dong's chest. She panted, even more, her hands and cheek resting on his broad chest, and those squishy lumps pressing into him as well.

'Noooooo! Not like this!'

In the end, Matt couldn't deny his carnal desires and something bloomed down low. His little brother expanded forward like a mighty sword that stood resolute, demanding a worthy battle. The only thing he could hope for is that the woman wouldn't notice it while being in that strange state of Qi absorption.

'My brother... why did you fail me in this time of need?'

Chapter 180

He stood there, motionless, his eyes shut and his fist clenched. He had a woman leaning up against his chest, her heart rate erratic, her pants echoing throughout the closed of space.

'I push away all negative distractions, allowing me to find clarity in my actions. To find peace of mind in this time of need..."

He chanted a mantra to calm himself down, but to no avail, his lower half had decided to stand up like a pillar pointing towards heaven. He couldn't just push Feng Liena away so he waited like a gentleman would, with his rear end pushed back in an awkward way.

"Oh, this feeling... Senior Brother, this is wonderful!"

She finally recovered and looked up, the coast looked to be clear as she didn't notice the trouble brewing down low.

"Ah yes Sister Liena, this increase in cultivation should help you reach the nascent soul level in no time! I think you should find yourself a peaceful spot here and cultivate, no one will bother you."

Feng Liena finally noticed that she had gotten really close to Zhang Dong. Her body was pressing against his which made her blush slightly, but then she noticed that something was off. Something was poking her, her thighs in particular. She moved her gaze down wanting to see what the large thing that was poking her was.

Zhang Dong sprung to action a glint in his eye. He could see her moving her gaze down for a peek, he quickly placed his hands on both her shoulders. This made Liena change the trajectory of her gaze and look up to meet Zhang Dong's eyes. By grasping her shoulders he picked her up from the ground, then she was spun around and placed down in one quick move.

"I think you should really start cultivating... I set the Dimensional Regalia to let you both out whenever you wish... so I'll be seeing you two later..."

He moved back and before Liena could turn around he was gone. She blinked a couple of times before heading out to find a spot where she could digest the new cultivation method.

Matt appeared outside, the treasure item next to him and the coast clear.

"Think she didn't notice anything..."

He glanced down, his little brother looked quite angry and ready for some action. For some reason, he wasn't calming down even though he was activating his tranquil mind technique.

'D-did I overuse that technique or something... why won't it go down...'

He leaned down as standing up straight was becoming a bother, luckily after some time passed he started calming down. He almost thought that he would have to give himself a punch as the last result. Maybe his little brother noticed his intentions and decided to give up this time around.

'Whew... okay enough of this I need to cultivate my physique and reinforce the formation!'

There was barely enough space for Qiang and Liena in the Dimensional Regalia so he decided to progress his body in his crafting abode which could block out his aura as well. He slipped inside and was greeted by a familiar sight of scattered ingots and smelters.

'I should clean this place up once in a while...'

He had obtained some weapons from the nascent soul elders that he fought so he didn't need to fashion his own this time around. He decided to keep Wu Ming's sword as his own had broken down during that fight. The other weapon that he had procured from that battle could be used though.

He took it out, it was a large black glaive. It was nice and long and had some strange patterns of the bent bladed part at the end. Matt spun it around above his head a little bit while having some fun.

'Hm, maybe I should have gotten some glaive related techniques... this one looks nice...'

He chuckled and places the weapon down while he himself sat in a lotus position. He had absorbed a vast amount of weaponry by this point but after the sacred ground event, he was rusty. The strange cube pushed his bodily cultivation to the apex of core formation at that time.

"It should be fine, let me get this over with..."

He placed his hand on the large sharp-bladed part of the glaive and activated the technique. His Qi resonated with the metals that the weapons was made of this making it glow with a reddish light. He could feel the particles and the Dao of what this item was made of slowly moving towards his digits. The sensation went further in going through his arm and then to his chest the feeling was slightly similar to goosebump.

"This is going to take a while..."

He had to spend an hour or two when he was absorbing core formation items, but this one was at the nascent soul level. He could feel the Dao getting absorbed by his physique but this was a whole new metamorphosis. He couldn't rush it, getting a cultivation backlash or regressing was not something that he could afford.

....

While Matt and the others were preparing for their next battle the news of what happened in Jade Grass City was spreading throughout the Dark Palm Sect area.

The main sect area wasn't located in a city, in particular. It was a removed area that was surrounded by ten large peaks. These were named the Harmonious Peaks and each one of them was owned by a Grand Elder of the sect. The Death of one of these elders caused a big scandal, this elder was Wu Ming.

Wu Ming wasn't the only elder that got hit though, Elder Zhu that was crippled also suffered bringing the number of peak masters down to eight. There were ten grand elders and ten Harmonious peaks, but now two of them were gone which brought the all-around battle prowess of this sect down a peg.

Four from the group of people that were chasing Zhang Dong had returned back to their own peaks by this point and awaited further instructions from the sect leader. This man was living in a huge building in the central part of the sect. The Harmonious mountain peaks stood all around this place acting as barriers.

"Lord Guanyu, this all information we have on the matter, the Grand elders have returned after failing to apprehend the mastermind."

A core formation master was reading something down from a large scroll while looking at another man that was sitting on a large throne-like chair. The man's name was Yang Guanyu and he was the Dark Palm Sects leader. Just as his son Yang Kai he had a gem embedded in his forehead. It was even larger than the one his son had, it was pulsating with a deep purple light.

"Call those idiots over!"

The man grumbled while leaning back. He was quite lanky, his whole face covered with wrinkles. He had a topknot of white hair coming out from behind his head, the front part shiny and bald. His hands were large, the digits long with sharp fingernails that looked like they could rip someone's throat clean off. Even though he looked like a skinny old man, the aura he was giving gave everyone the chills.

"So my stupid son is dead, his killer still alive..."

The man that was in the room was gone, Guanyu looked in a certain direction of this meeting room his eyebrows furrowing.

"Tell the council members that I will handle this myself, there is no need for them to act!"

The shadowy figure that was sticking close to the walls didn't reply, vanishing the moment the sect leader spoke out.

"Those old bastards, only whining when they feel threatened."

He leaned on his chair and supported his chin with his hand as he sighed. He was the sect leader, but there were other people close to his level in this sect. This was mostly called a sect 'reserve' a hidden group of old monsters that had been long forgotten by the world.

This was something that every sect did, when an old sect master or grand elder retired they would go into hiding. They would spend most of their life cultivating and trying to prolong their life, waiting for a time when they would be needed by the sect. They were old monsters all at the nascent soul level, but they were all running low on life energy.

People like this would never leave the main sect area of their given sects. They would be there acting as the last defense if any other powers decided to attack. This was also a big reason why fights between other powerful sects didn't lead to anything. It was hard to tell if those hidden elders were still alive which prevented takeovers from happening.

Yang Guanyu couldn't deny these elders, he had to resolve this situation before the body count increased. In the past years they have been suffering setbacks. First, the secret ground fiasco where they lost one of their grand elders. Now another one was dead, the second one crippled and useless. Even worse than the dead elder was someone that was at the middle stage of the nascent soul which was hard to reach.

"We greet the Sect Leader!"

The grand elder's starter arriving one by one, soon four of them were here as one of them remained back at the border region to keep watch. In total there were eight active grand elders, three of them were placed at strategic locations at the borders with three other powerful sects.

"Everyone listen, you all got the reports, the relation between this Zhang Clan and this mysterious cultivator is very probable."

"That clan's sin is high and it must be eradicated along with all of its allies. It is unlikely that the hidden master will come to aid this clan, but a small chance exists."

"The other large sects are watching our movements so we must be swift, as we speak a new teleportation formation is being created at Jade Grass City."

"It will take a weak before it is finished. Select two grand elders to bring that clan to justice."

The sect leader started talking, the grand elders just kept listening not seeing many holes in the plan. Thanks to the teleportation gate they would be able to return to the main sect if something happened while they were away.

"Sect leader."

One of the elders raised his hand as he asked for a question, only continuing after Yang Guanyu gave him a nod.

"What if that master appears at that Zhang clan location, he defeated Wu Ming on his own, two grand elders might not be enough to contend with him."

Guanyu just nodded and snorted.

"The other elders will wait by the teleportation gate, if that cultivator appears you will wait for me to arrive, I will take care of him personally..."

The man squinted with his eyes and looked at the four people that trembled slightly. They knew how powerful their master was, if he made a move then there was no reason to fear the enemy.

"The council will guard the main sect and activate the defensive array if something happens, it is highly unlikely that the other sects will react."

"But... keep an eye out for the Demonic Subduing Sect, their movements have been strange...this is all!"

The grand elders nodded at their leader and moved out. They would make preparations of their own in the wake of this battle. They knew that this Zhang Clan and its allies were good as dead and that strange master would probably not appear. It was something that needed to be done though, rumors were already spreading as the citizens of the city and even their sect members were left alive to tell the tale.

The most likely answer for Guanyu was that this nascent soul cultivator was long gone. Apparently he reacted only when his so-called disciple was being attacked, the following destruction was probably something he did in a fit of rage. He even tried to push the Demon Subduing sect into a fight with them. Probably to gain some time and cover his tracks, which worked out for him in the end. The sect couldn't find him anywhere and had to be warry of the other powers.

"After we finish eradicating those bugs we will find that man and show him why the Dark Palm Sect shouldn't be trifled with!"

Chapter 181

A white-haired man was sitting down, he was surrounded by various blades and weapons from all sides. His chest was exposed and it was glistering with sweat. His body was glowing in a golden hue radiating more and more power. This bright golden light soon filled the entire room, everything became bathed in its radiance.

"Ugh..."

His muscular frame expanded slightly and you could hear cracking sounds. The top layer of his skin was cracking and peeling away, what was underneath wanted to see the light of day. With a resounding explosion, all the items around him that weren't secured flew to the sides. The room was filled with even deeper golden light, his body crackling with awesome power.

True Golden Body [Nascent Soul Early Stage]

"True Golden Body huh? Thought I'd move into Platinium, or maybe Diamond?"

Matt slowly stood up, the whole place was ruined and he would need to spend some time on rearranging everything. After almost two days of absorbing he had finally pushed his body refining technique over the limit. He was now a true nascent soul body refiner, together with his Qi cultivation he was truly one of the best masters in the land.

"Wonder if I can tank early-stage hits now..."

He took out the other heaven grade weapon that he had earned from the sacking, this one belonged to the elder named Zhu. This was a green dao saber. He moved it over to his forearm and applied some pressure the moment he did he could feel the sharp edge scraping against his skin.

His skin was quite hard yet elastic at the same time, it was really good at resisting this heaven graded weapon. If he didn't add much of his cultivation, it didn't even leave a scratch behind, but he felt that if he tried whacking himself really good he would draw some blood.

"I should be able to resist some attacks, but I probably shouldn't get too cocky..."

He felt like he could brush off early nascent soul practitioners with this. But if they had some better weapons then it got tricky, he should be fine if they didn't get any good hits in.

"Done with this, on to the next one..."

He remained in his crafting abode and headed into the place where he kept the manuals he copied over. He had received some formation manuals from the secret ground. The grand defensive formation that was running through the city was also heaven graded, he would use that one as a base and level it up.

"The problem is the power source...luckily there were some treasures in those spatial rings, I think I should be able to make something akin to a Qi battery."

He focused on the grand defensive formation, he needed more time before his allies increased their power and had no idea when the Dark Palm sect would arrive. The process was similar to the previous one, though this time around the compatibility of his cultivation technique with the grand defensive formation was quite low.

"Figures... one is a formation manual, the other is a cultivation manual for people..."

The only thing he could do was to put some other heaven grade formation manuals and spend some points to achieve a formation at the high heaven grade.

"This will have to do... the more important thing is the power source... It requires many tower-like nodes to be spread throughout the city and they all need to be powered..."

He rubbed his chin, he could place the cultivators that weren't fighting as batteries around these spots. As long as the formation held up they wouldn't need to fight. He could then battle the enemies outside the barrier if it came to it.

"Uh... luckily the Qi gathering formations are spread through the city...but they can be improved upon..."

He had all of the formations in the city mapped out. They were all placed during the two years of peace and were of high quality all things considered. He didn't think they would stack up against the nascent soul monsters all too well though.

"Damn, if we have enough time to prepare... I could have made this into a giant fortress..."

He gave out a sigh and continued spending points while improving the formations with the help of his system. The millions of points were steadily decreasing.

"I need to get all the resources available in the clan, not sure I can make it cover the whole city..."

He left his crafting abode and raided the main Zhang Clan vault. The people guarding it after peeking inside couldn't find a single spirit stone or beast core left to be found. Zhang Dong also gave an order for his people to gather all of the spirit stones, spirit cores, and spirit herbs that were good at storing Qi.

What followed was a slight backlash from the order, no one wanted to give up their riches. They relented soon though, some due to fear of their Patriarch, some realizing that riches like these meant nothing if they were all dead, others just loyal and not caring about the monetary gains.

While the people were gathering the items Matt was busy, he returned to his crafting abode and decided to start crafting. There was one thing in particular that he could make. It was a spirit cube, it was strangely similar to the one that he saw back at the secret ground. He remembered that it had given him a major injection of spirit points and he had a crafting method for it.

"This might be the crafting method that the cube was based on, not sure if it's the same this one is mostly used for storing spiritual energy and information. I wonder if you could record movies on this..."

He recalled that that cube was made from some sturdy metal as at that time he couldn't leave a dent on it. He began the smelting process almost immediately, he chose the best spirit metal that he could use and even began melting down the weapons that were made from it. This cube had to be tempered multiple times, each time he hammered a part into place some of the impurities would be dispersed into the surroundings.

It took him half a day to make a simple cube that was ten centimeters in diameter. It was glowing with a bright blue light as he had infused it with spiritual energy from part of his leftover spirit stone stash. He had to melt them down into spirit essence and then direct it into the cube.

"Hmm...."

Spirit Repository Cube [Low Heaven Grade] [Fully Charged]

He had spent hammering and working on this thing for close to twelve hours. He was slightly proud as this was the first heaven grade item that he had produced. Even though it was just a plain cube, it was still a monument to his progress.

"Now to make five more..."

The defensive formation was in the shape of a hexagram. He needed to place these cubes at those locations to support his cultivators. These cubes had a function of absorbing spiritual energy from the surroundings and from people. They would be placed in six locations along with people that would supply them with more Qi to run on.

"I gave Kuo the plans for the improved formation arrays, hope they can make the changes in time. This formation has a size limit placing it around the whole city would require multiple hexagram formations. I hope we have enough time to cover everything."

Luckily he had all those books from the sacred ground. For the past two years, he had shared them with his whole clan. In those books were secrets of formation arrays and he had some of the able people learn the production process. He couldn't take care of everything himself, if he had the time he would come check up on them but for now, he needed to make even more of these.

"Time is of the essence, maybe I can reforge this black sword into something better if I have the time. Now time to make more squares."

He hammered away in his crafting abode while his clan members were running outside and frantically getting the defenses up in place. Most of the citizens that wanted to leave were already going through the long maze under the City. The path ahead of them was long but they would come to emerge at a safer location in a faraway forest. This forest had many places to hide, animals to feed on, and water to drink. They would be safe for months, they also had some food spatial pouches that they borrowed from the Zhang Clan.

This was also the time where other Zhang Clan members were arriving. Some more honorable ones had decided to lend their family a hand, while others took a more wait and see approach.

They weren't the only reinforcements that were arriving though, The Feng Clan was a close second. Their Matriarch was all in on this battle so they brought over all of their forces. Besides Feng Nuana and Feng Maling, there were various other core formation ladies. They were mostly in the early or middle stages but would come in handy in powering the new defensive formation that was being reinforced.

As always they were a head-turner, their quirky hairstyles and the overuse of bright cosmetics was something that these old fashioned cultivators weren't used too. Feng Maling gave everyone the orders, they were to support the Zhang and Huo clans. The women gave out a battle shout after hearing that they were preparing for a defensive war and that their Matriarch might be reaching a new level of power soon.

The last Clan to arrive was the Huo Clan, this clan also had the biggest force from the triforce alliance. The Zhang Clan was only in a higher position thanks to their Patriarch. The Huo Clan's fire lord had come as well, they all had to flee from their domain after hearing what was going on. The only hope was this Zhang Dong that was supposed to be a nascent soul master now.

"The Zhang Clan greets the Huo Clan's Patriarch."

A large man with a full beard and white hair walked down from one of the docked battleships. He was wearing a tight sleeveless red robe, this allowed everyone to see his thick tree trunk-like arms. His skin was quite dark making him look like he was a part of the gyaru clan.

"You're not Zhang Dong, I demand to see your Patriarch! This Huo Gang wants an explanation!"

Behind the Huo Patriarch stood a group of ten core formation elders. The one receiving them here was Zhang Ya, one of Zhang Dong's retainers. The lady just smiled while keeping a poker face, she knew that their leader moved to places that they could find him so she had no idea how to arrange a meeting. Zhang Dong at the time was busy hammering away on the battery cubes that were paramount to their survival.

"Let me guide you to the inner sanctum, your clan members like elder Qiao are there."

She tried moving the conversation in a different direction, maybe she could shove the responsibility on the elder from the Huo Clan instead.

"Qiao? What is that idiot advising my son? How did this all come to be?"

Huo Gang exploded in fury, his beard turned red and it looked like it was flaming. Zhang Ya had to back away, she was still someone only in the foundation establishment realm.

"Please my lord calm down, we are all allies."

She moved her head down not knowing what to do, infighting was something that she and the newly created sect wanted to avoid.

"Now now, please calm down... we are all in this together now."

Zhang Ya was finally able to relax as a strong counterforce pushed Huo Gang's killing intent away. Who appeared was another white-haired elder his name Zhang Jin. He was all smiles and was wearing a more robust looking battle robe. He did a complementary fist bow at the large angry looking man and then started talking.

"I'm sure we can talk everything through like civilized cultivators, isn't that right Lord Gang?"

Zhang Jin smiled but he was panicking inside. He knew that the man in front of his was more powerful than he could hope for, he also didn't have his black armor anymore as it was turned to scrap metal by Wu Ming. The two remained in place just staring at each other, no one saying a word.

Chapter 182

Zhang Jin moved in front of the woman and shielded her from the angry looking Huo Gang. The two exchanged glances for some time, Jin was smiling while Gang was frowning. The thing that broke the stare down was the appearance of Huo Qiao.

"Patriarch you have arrived!"

The man with the mutton chop beard moved forward and placed himself between the two elders. He was afraid that his leader might do something drastic. He was a loyal follower but he was more scared of Zhang Dong than Huo Gang at the moment. The white-haired cultivator could flatten their entire clan if he wished for.

"Qiao, where is that stupid son of mine? Bring him out, we are leaving!"

Huo Qiao started sweating bullets, not sure what to say to his boss. The young master was brought away by the order of the Zhang Patriarch and was in some secluded location. He was apparently training to reach the nascent soul level, but Qiao was still skeptical about the whole thing. The only thing keeping him here was the knowledge that the Zhang Clan possessed an immortal level cultivation technique.

"What are you waiting for? Where is he? We need to flee, we will head towards the west and seek shelter outside the Dark Palm Sect territory!"

"Your son is busy cultivating now, Senior Gang if you come with me I'll explain everything."

Zhang Jin moved in, trying to diffuse the situation.

"Cultivating? Why would he be cultivating at a time like this? Are you people sane?"

The man started furrowing his eyebrows and clenching his fist. His core formation aura at the great circle filled up the docking area where they were holding this conversation. The core formation masters behind him started moving forward while pulling out weapons. Huo Qiao was taken aback, his clan was turning hostile against a nascent soul cultivators sect.

"Please Patriarch calm down, we can't offend the Zhan... no, the United Elements Sect!"

The dark-skinned man stopped for a bit, not sure what his clan member was talking about.

"What nonsense is this, a Sect? Have you gone mad, if you don't tell me where Qiang is, I will consider this treason!"

Not a second later after finishing that sentence Huo Gang felt himself getting pushed into the ground. Some kind of pattern appeared at the spot he was standing on and it was sapping most of the energies from them. From the side, Zhang Kuo appeared, in his kind some kind of pilot looking treasure.

"You leave us no choice, the United Elements Sect will not negotiate with people like you!"

This was a defensive array and the item Kuo was holding was a remote control of sorts. This was a large defensive array that started affected all the core formation experts that were hostile. It siphoned the Qi out of their body rendering them defenseless but keeping enough for them not to die.

"You! ... Do you think something like this can hold me!"

The man's face went red and you could see the veins on his neck bulging all over. He started gathering all of the Qi that he could muster, his body covered with a red glow. But the moment he felt the pressure breaking Zhang Kuo turned the dial on the remote which made Huo Gang get pressed into the ground like a pancake.

"You won't get away with this! Are you working together with the Dark Palm Sect, what did you do to my son! Did you brainwash him like Qiao too!?"

The man started thrashing on the ground while bringing out some false accusations. He had quite the bright imagination as he tried pinning any type of scheme on the Zhang clan members. The array was keeping him in place, Qiao on the side wanted to go after Zhang Kuo that was controlling the whole thing. He stopped himself from doing that as he knew that this was a misunderstanding.

"Patriarch you are mistaken, Young Master is training to reach the nascent soul realm with the Zhang Patriarch that is already at that realm."

Huo Gang quieted down the moment he heard the nascent soul get mentioned. He heard about someone rescuing his son from Jade Grass City, but this information was hard to swallow. Why would a master of that level oppose the Dark Palm Sect and be from the Zhang Clan that has no power?

Huo Qiao knew that this old man was quite stubborn and would probably not believe any outlandish claims without enough evidence. The only thing they had to go off was from the call he had with his son. Huo Qiang after making a half-assed report decided to ignore all of his father's communication attempts.

It came to Qiao to try calming him down, but even when he described everything with detail. From the beginning till the end of the Dao festival, his Patriarch was skeptical. The only part he was convinced about was, that they had offended the main sect in the area and now had to flee.

While most of the Huo Clan elders were squirming on the ground, Zhang Jin stepped forward.

"Senior Gang we really mean you no harm, your sone is alive and well, if he was in danger your life indicating treasures would tell you this. Please appease your anger and we can talk this out like fellow Daoists."

The Fire clan leader looked up and was feeling humiliated. He realized that he wasn't the one with the upper hand here, the defensive measures this clan had in place were above the ones back home. He didn't like this, but for now, it looked like he had to abide by the other party's rules.

After a few moments, the large man nodded, in response, Zhang Jin gave Kuo the signal to lower the output on the defensive array. This was one of the measures put in place thanks to the secret ground rewards, this new suppressing formation warked similarly to how cultivators suppressed weaker opponents. It outputted enough spiritual pressure to incapacitate anyone below the nascent soul level. Its only downside was that it was only applicable to people in the main Zhang Clan compound.

"I hope we can start off again, Senior Gang."

Zhang Jin smiled while everyone from the fire clan breathed a sigh of relief. They all looked at Zhang Kuo that was holding the remote control to the defensive array. He just needed to use the dial while thinking about who to suppress and it would work. The fire clan relented and didn't try anything funny.

Most of their cultivators stayed in their ships while a small elite unit was escorted into the main sanctum. In there they were greeted by the fire clan juniors that were rescued from the Dao Festival, Huo Kong was one of them. He instantly spotted his grumpy looking grandpa in the distance and greeted him.

"Grandson greets his grandfather!"

He bowed respectfully, Huo Gang almost smiling as he saw that his grandson was fine.

"Little Kong, where is your father, is what Qiao speaking the truth?"

Huo Kong nodded and recounted what had happened from his perspective, most of it was the same but the youth's eyes began shining whenever he started talking about Zhang Dong's fight and appearance.

"And then Lord Dong took off with that Dark Palm elder called Ming, he returned not long ago, I've even seen him wondering these halls he truly reached the nascent soul level."

The grandson was set on convincing his grumpy grandpa on trusting this clan for one reason or another. His blossoming fondness towards Zhang Xue might have played a slight role in his decision-making process.

"Is that so..."

Gang was willing to believe his grandson, but there was also a probability of brainwashing. He still wanted to grab his family members and just bolt it for the hills. He still needed to find his strongest son, he was the future of the clan and already almost as strong as he himself.

Then suddenly people heard the sound of thunder, out of nowhere a cultivator in a pure white robe appeared. The man looked to be in a hurry as he run-up to the man that was holding on the defensive array remote control. Huo Gang was watching this happen, he noticed that the Zhang members were instantly bowing at the man that just came in.

He handed what looked to be a cube to the man along with a large scroll of paper. He wasn't hiding anything as even he could see that that scroll had some sort of array formation on it. He focused his ears to listen to the conversation, quite interested in what this Zhang Patriarch was all about.

"Yes Kuo, here is the improved array formation and here you have the first battery cube, you see these parts, you need to place them all there."

The man took out more large paper scrolls, there were various things drawn onto them showing some strange pointy tower-like structures.

"Here, give this to the formation masters, have them work on it."

He also handed the man a spatial ring, telling him that he would find most of the building materials in there.

"Supply the masters with more building materials if there happens to be something missing, now go we don't have any time to waste I still need to make five more of those!"

Zhang Dong had taken a small break, he needed to give the plans to his workers while he was crafting the items required to power the new array formation. When he was about to head back to his crafting abode a large burly man in a red robe stood in front of him, he looked like he wanted to say something.

"Grandfather t-this is the Zhang Patriarch..."

Huo Kong was to the side, bowing his head down and looked slightly scared. His grandfather wasn't showing enough face to someone that was at the nascent soul level as he didn't even bow. Zhang Dong looked to the red-haired youth and then to the muscular grandpa, the sight of those massive tree trunk-like arms was awe-inspiring.

"Ah, you must be from the Huo Clan, I'm glad that you have arrived to aid us in these troubled times, we will take all the help we can get!"

Before Gang could even say anything he felt the white-haired man's palm be placed on his shoulder.

"I welcome you to the United Sect of Elemental Dao, I don't have the time to take your oath right now, but after the preparations are done I'll be sure to arrange a pledge ceremony for everyone! Really glad to have you here!"

Huo Gang listened to the man talking and grasped Zhang Dong's hand by the wrist. He tried pulling it off his shoulder but it felt like he was trying to move a mountain. It just wouldn't budge, the man just continued talking like there was nothing wrong. His muscles bulged and he even pushed his Qi into it but still, not even a millimeter of that hand moved.

"Ah, I see that you have brought many ships with you, that's great! If you have any spirit stones and beast cores with you, it would be great if you handed them over, we can use them to power the new improved grand formation!"

Huo Gang just sweated, his attempt at resisting wasn't being taken seriously at all. The man just walked away after a moment after monologing for a while. The large old man knew just from that short encounter that this Zhang Patriarch was a true monster and he wasn't taking him the Huo Clan leader seriously at all.

"Hah..."

"Grandfather are you okay?"

"I'm fine Kong'er..."

The man had his fighting spirit sapped. First, there was this formation that could force them down to their knees and then there was this monster of a Zhang Patriarch running around. They had no way of forcing the Zhang Clan to do anything, the only thing they could do now is either stay or leave without Huo Qiang.

Chapter 183

Sometime later at Jade Grass City.

This city had gone through a lot lately, the streets were mostly deserted. The people with enough money to move out were long gone, the regular commoners on the other hand were waiting in their houses. The tensions were high and they knew that someone earned the wrath of the overlord sect. The people were just bunkering up, if the overbearing sect cultivators didn't see them, they might be left alone was their thought process.

The old sect base was in shambles but people were working. There were a bunch of cultivators wearing the Dark Palm sect robes gathered around a large portal gate. It looked similar to the one the junior cultivators used during the Dao festival final test but it was much larger. It was at least the size of a football field in diameter. There was a large ramp going up to it and some symbols on the sides were already glowing.

"The gate is stable... primary tests are all positive, we are ready to activate it."

A man shouted out from the side while standing next to some other cultivators. The people around the large teleportation gate nodded and started infusing the large contraption with their Qi. The large ring part of the gate started spinning while water like spirit energy appeared from the side and started flowing out into the center. The portal gate soon formed, the spiritual energy stabilized but was still bubbling slightly.

"That's enough spiritual energy, secure the gate, activate the balance locks!"

The ring that was spinning came to a halt, the rune-like symbols flickered around and shone brightly. Not long after that, you could see a person's foot coming through the water like the surface of the teleportation gate. The foot was followed by another one from the side as multiple cultivators emerged from the inside.

"Greeting's elders and grand elders, everything has been prepared for the invasion, we await your orders."

The ones that were stepping through this gate was Elder Wan and Elder Guo. These two were previously chasing Zhang Dong all the way up to the border, this time around they would be part of the scouting force. Elder Wan nodded at the fellow sect member before moving his had forward and speaking out.

"We will proceed with the plan, the strike force will head towards the Zhang Clan."

Everyone cupped their fists and was ready for some action. In the distance the people in the city heard some rumbling, some of them peeked through the cracks of their windows as the sound was coming from above. Their eyes bulged as they saw at least ten large flying ships going past them.

The vibrations that were coming of those huge vessels were causing the windows and glass to shake, the loud sound was hurting the people's ears. They knew that this was the sect making a move, their destination unknown but everyone knew that they would only leave death and destruction in their wake.

The two nascent soul grand elders took to the sky and flew by themselves. The ships were carrying a large force of the sect disciples, the people taking part in this organized raid were in the foundation establishment realm at the minimum. They were here to do the cleanup duty, the grand elders were far too high up the ladder. You couldn't expect them to do all the work, they were only there to clear out the nascent soul cultivator. If they were done with their assignment they would just remain there to keep watch only taking part if something out of the ordinary occurred.

This attack wouldn't get unnoticed by the other large sects, but it was up to debate if they would do anything. While everyone was going toward Spirit Spring City Elder Wan and Guo started talking.

"You think that person will appear, Senior Wan?"

"Don't think so, would you?"

Elder Wan replied while rubbing his chin, the answer seeming obvious to this man.

"I wouldn't, I would flee to a secluded location if I didn't have any backers."

"Yes, that is if he doesn't have anyone backing him, this could be some kind of elaborate scheme to split the clan up so be vigilant Junior Brother."

Elder Guo nodded, the two knew that they had to watch out. They had brought treasures to aid their escape, they were worried that they could be going into a trap. They got the short end of the stick, being ordered by their Sect leader to act as scouts.

"Can't these ships move any faster? It will take us half a day like this!"

The large scouting troop flew, hours passed as they were steadily moving towards their destination. While the Dark Palm sect was making its move word of it arrived at the Zhang Clan. They had planted various detection devices around their land that would alert them to such movement.

"A large fleet of ships is moving towards our location Elder...ten of them plus... this reading... there are two large energy signatures in that group they are..."

The person that was looking at a sonar-like device started sweating.

"What is it!"

The commanding elder asked.

"We lost the signal, the large energy signatures were probably nascent soul cultivators, Sir!"

"Inform the others, we are going into code orange, everyone remember your training, for the Zhang Clan!"

The elder man shouted the orders as the scouting party got discovered, their tracing apparatus was found out but that wasn't important anymore. It did what it was supposed to do and now they could prepare for the assault.

Sirens sounded out in the vicinity of Spirit Spring City. The streets were empty and all of the common people had left anyone that remained was either from the three clans, or someone patriotic enough to lend a hand. This was it, the battle would be beginning soon and everyone knew that.

Spirit Spring City was surrounded from all sides by a sturdy wall, upon this large wall there were many guard towers, spaced out about 200 meters from each other. The guard towers looked like your regular circular-shaped castle towers, but on top of them was something uncommon.

Each tower was equipped with a large canon. These cannons looked more similar to anti-aircraft weapons that you saw in the modern era. A single cultivator sat on a seat to the side, the length of the cannons was close to ten meters. These cannons didn't fire any projectiles, no they fired of condensed spiritual bullets and were powered by the city itself.

Out in the distance, the Dark Palm ships were flying forward, Spirit Spring City was still too far away for their own cannons to reach. The two nascent soul elders where a bit to the side, they were there mostly here to watch over the junior members and to defend against a nascent soul threat if it arrived. One of the elders was examining a strange metallic contraption that he found buried deep underground while they were flying here.

"This is a strange treasure, I'm sure it was giving off some kind of spiritual signal..."

"Why would someone bury something like this in the middle of nowhere?"

The nascent soul elder had found the miliary device that alerted the Zhang Clan of their arrival. They weren't sure what it was used for but reacted to the strange signals the treasure was giving out. They had spotted it with the help of their enhanced spiritual sense.

"Elder Guo, put it away, we will be reaching our destination soon, we must stay vigilant."

"Hm, what are you worried about Elder Wan, not like that person will risk being here to defend them. Even if he does, we just need to alert the Sect leader and he and the other grand elders will arrive within the hour."

The man nodded but still wanted to be careful, you never knew what would happen and he didn't get to this level by not being careful.

"Wait, something is coming!"

While they were talking they felt a disturbance in the spiritual energy around them. The two put up a large shield blocking the spirit rounds that were flying towards them from the distance. The whole sky lit up in a blue color as the bombardment started, the people at the guard towers continuously firing their cannons.

The two elders spread out their energies to encompass the ships, the cannon fire getting suppressed by the powerful masters.

"Hoh, those are some nice cannons they have there, they put ours to shame... they are at the earth grade level."

"Yes, surprising that a lower clan could build something like this and they have many, where were they hiding those?"

The two elders were surprised, core formation-level power was paramount for these lower clans. These people at Spirit Spring City had many of those cannons, which meant that no one from the other clans would be able to attack their main base.

"We should get the plans for those, maybe we can improve the design and place it in our sect."

The two Grand Elders chatted while the cannon fire continued, their ships remained untouched while the two swept the sky from the spirit bullets that couldn't puncture the barriers that they set up in place.

"Still, we will have to take care of those cannons before the ships can move forward."

"No need, we'll just squash them while slowly approaching!"

Replied Elder Guo, not really wanting to retreat with the ships while the two of them could protect them while moving forward.

"Hah, you sure don't like wasting any time Guo, fine let us just be done with... what?"

Elder Wan felt something, he was stronger than Elder Guo that wasn't paying attention and moved away to the side. He saw two golden beams of concentrated energy shooting out from the ground. One went for him while the other towards his ally. He was barely able to evade it while shielding himself with all his might and suffered minor Qi burns, his ally wasn't as lucky.

"H-how could this be? Elder Guo!"

The man watched on with shock, his ally was pierced by the finger wide beam, struct directly in the chest. He looked below, to the source of this attack and saw him. There was someone there and he was already flying forward. He didn't know who this man was, he was wearing a white robe and his hair was pure as snow. He had retreated to the side but Guo had suffered a direct hit, so he was a sitting duck for this cultivator that was certainly also at the nascent soul level.

"It must be him, quickly alert the Sect Leader, we need reinforcements!"

Zhang Dong didn't let this chance be wasted. The moment he got the report that several flying ships were going their way he decided to ambush the nascent soul elders leading them. He used the underground tunnels and some digging to place himself somewhere between himself and the city, waiting and biding his time.

He had improved some of his own techniques with the remaining spirit points, being able to hide his aura from even these two grand elders. While they were busy shielding their flying ships he took his chance and fired off two beams of concentrated energy from his fingers. He was quite far away from the two flying enemies, still, he managed to evade the notice of one of them, and now he was charging to finish the job.

Elder Guo vomited blood and activated various life-saving treasures. A barrier formed around him while he healed himself and started to flee. He was already injured, his speed dropping severely, Zhang Dong wouldn't let this opportunity slide. He pulled out a sword, it was black and belonged to Wu Ming, he didn't have enough time to reforge it within this short span of time.

"You're not getting away! Sever the Heavens, Nascent Soul version!"

Before he knew it radiant sword energy was moving towards him. He could only turn around and muster up all his power to attempt to block it. His defensive treasures trembled and split in half along with the man named Elder Guo, the sword strike traveled far and wide and slashed one of the galleon sized flying vessels in two. The ground trembled, the sky split apart as the cleanly cut body of the nascent soul cultivator exploded and signaled the beginning of the battle.

Chapter 184

Screams and shouts were heard everywhere, the flying ships were getting bombarded by the long-range anti-aircraft cannons of the Zhang Clan. Without the nascent soul elders protecting them, they were like sitting ducks. Before they could get into range to return fire they would be annihilated. Their defensive arrays were ineffective against the cannon barrage.

Their protective shields weren't strong enough to last. The leaders did the correct thing and signaled for a retreat. One of their ships was going up in flames while falling. Before it could crash it was bisected by an enemy cultivator. This was Zhang Dong and he was just delivering the ending blow to the Dark Palm Elder. His nascent divinity was badly injured and the chase wasn't long, he was first grand elder causality.

"That other guy sure ran away fast, he didn't even bother to help his own comrade..."

Elder Wan looked like a grain of rice in the distance, even with Zhang Dong's enhanced vision he was hard to spot. He looked to the sides and saw the retreating ships and some Dark Palm Cultivators fleeing the scene. Even while escaping they were getting bombarded by Qi bullets, the scene was quite gruesome to watch.

"So this is war..."

"This is long past the point of no return..."

Matt frowned while clenching his fist. His hand started glowing as golden lightning crackled, he remembered the time he mercilessly finished of a band of bandits two years ago. This would be something similar just on a larger scale. He threw the improved lightning spear into the air and watched it whizz past the clouds. A loud boom of thunder resounded throughout the area and a shower of golden lightning bolts rained down on everyone in the vicinity.

The Dark Palm sect cultivators found themselves getting attacked from the back as they tried to flee and from the sky. Matt looked at the gruesome scene of people getting blown up and exploding while screaming for mercy. Deep inside he knew that these people came to his city to do the exact thing that he was doing to them. Still, it didn't sit well with him.

"At least I'll give you a quick death..."

He wasn't in the mood to chase any straggler, all of the ships were going down after his lightning barrage. He propelled himself backward and headed back into the city, he expected more of those Dark Palm members to arrive as he didn't think that killing one Grand Elder would be enough.

"It would be nice if this was the end... but knowing these murder hobos they won't take something like this lying down."

While Zhang Dong was returning back to Spirit Spring City, Elder Wan was pushing his spiritual energy to the max just to get away from there. He was sweating bullets and using his spiritual sense to feel if he was being chased. He was vigilant as he barely noticed his opponent being there, only when the attack was fired off did he manage to react and dodge.

"Alert the Sect Leader, the enemy nascent soul master is in the city! Send the remaining Grand Elders to help!"

He shouted into his communication jade while flying without looking back. He thought that the man would give chase but Matt was worried that he would be lured into a trap, or that they might attack the city while he was busy fighting the grand elders. Back in the Dark Palm Sect main base, Yang Guanyu was getting his report.

"What... that fool Guo is already dead, just like that?"

He was sitting together with the rest of the grand elders that were waiting for further orders. After pulling back the grand elder that remained at the border they were down to four active ones and their sect leader. All of them would have to head out, they needed to protect the honor of their sect but they had already lost far too much in this battle.

"This... am I surrounded by fools? Can't you kill one whelp?"

The man's dastardly aura filled the whole room, the three grand elders that were with him went down to their knees under the pressure.

"Please grand elder, appease your anger."

The woman cultivator called out while Yang Guanyu was having a fit of rage. The old man looked at his sect elders and finally stood up from his throne-like chair. He placed his long hands behind his back and floated forward.

"I'll take care of him, you fools follow me, I will not stand for this!"

"This problem has to be kept a secret, the other sects can not find out about this, we might suffer further losses to our lands."

The group of elders floated towards one of the Harmonious mountain peaks. This peak in particular was responsible for the teleportation arrays and gates that went through the whole Dark Palm territory. The personnel was already waiting for them and the gate was activated.

"Mobilise the main troops, while I and the Grand Elders are taking care of the nascent soul threat, they will eradicate their crummy city, we will take no prisoners, no one will survive!"

He proclaimed in a calm voice, even though he wasn't shouting everyone at the sect could clearly hear this order. The proud sect members raised their weapons into the air and cheered out. With their Sect Leader leading them they had nothing more to fear. Everyone vanished through the large gate, even their large ships were able to fit through this thing that quite the wide diameter.

On the other side, they were greeted by part of the force that remained in the city. Everyone had their head lowered not daring to look at their sect leader. They knew that he had a no-nonsense policy and would strike them down in a heartbeat if they showed him any amount of disrespect.

"Where is Elder Wan?"

The sect leader asked while the rest of the army was going through the teleportation portal.

"Elder Wan has retreated, he is flying towards the city."

One of the people reported while not looking up, far too scared to meet the sect leaders' eyes.

"So he left his men? Hm..."

The sect elder just nodded, thinking to himself that it was probably the right thing to do when fighting an unknown enemy at their territory.

"We will depart and meet Elder Wan halfway."

"All the grand elders come with me, the rest of the sect will fly in the front."

The sect leader didn't put his trust into his sect warriors all too much but he still could use them as meat shields or a distraction. If the flying ships gathered around they could match the firepower of a nascent soul master. The only downside was that they were slow and their defenses were lacking. In a true battle, they would lose out but could act as a decoy or provide supportive fire from the back.

Finally, everyone moved and the citizens of Jade Grass City trembled once more. This time around the armada was much larger, the ships blocked out the sky as their shadows were cast on the ground below. There was at least a hundred of those ships coming in, the teleportation formation was working overtime.

"We must hurry and get done with this today, before the other sects find out."

In Yang Guanyu's mind, there was a low chance of the other sects getting here. Even they in their own territory needed a whole week to get their teleportation array going. Their opposition would need to do the same while being unnoticed by their Dark Palm sect faction. There was no movement at the borders and their nascent soul masters weren't reporting anything out of place either.

"I greet the Sect Leader!"

Elder Wan bowed while floating in the air. He had a solemn expression and was slightly sweating while looking at the thin man floating in front of him.

"So, Guo is dead?"

"Yes Sect Leader, the enemy cultivator had hidden his presence and managed to land a surprise attack..."

Elder Wan did a quick recap of the situation, he was the only person that returned alive from that encounter.

"He was young and with white hair?"

Elder Wan nodded, the enemy was known for changing his appearance.

"Yes, but I didn't feel that disguising technique on this man... it might have been his real appearance. From the way he looked, our intelligence faction has determined him to be someone named Zhang Dong."

The sect had their own intelligence-gathering force and procuring information about the clan heads was an easy thing to do. Going in deeper would require more time though.

"Do we have any information on this Zhang Dong you speak off?"

The sect leader and the grand elders were mid-flight while talking. None of them made any inquiries into the lives of the people from the Zhang Clan. They weren't treated as more than bugs in their eyes, there was no reason to do a throughout investigation.

"We don't know much, Patriarch... no one expected a small force like that to be protected by a strong cultivator like that."

The rest of the elders tried contacting their own retainers, but it would take time for any useful information to get back to them.

"It matters not, the only important thing now is that he and his clan gets eradicated. We must bring these people to justice for offending us."

Everyone agreed with the sect leader as they finally arrived close to the spot that Elder Guo was slain. Parts of the Dark Palm Sects ships were scattered throughout the area. There were multiple craters and holes, the nascent soul elders felt the place out worrying that there could be another ambush.

"Everyone is dead, I don't sense any survivors."

The Sect leader focused as well, his weaker sect elders weren't able to see through the enemy's hiding technique. He was the sect leader though, its most powerful official member. His spiritual sense reached far and wide, his eyes looking around as he searched for the enemy.

His eyes suddenly narrowed and he pointed a finger at a certain location. The gem on his forehead started glowing with a purple light. The energy traveled from this gem into his hand and collected in front of that digit in a matter of seconds.

"Do you think you can hide from this Yang Guanyu? Die!"

A massive surge of Qi flowed out from that finger. It looked like a purple mass of energy with wailing souls trapped inside, the scratches were horrifying and even the grand elders started backing off. The attack landed at a certain location among the ship debris a giant explosion echoing soon after.

The people from the Dark Palm Sect looked to that location, they felt proud at their sect leader who was able to sniff out the enemy master with just a glance. They started at that spot with eyebrows furrowed and their weapons drawn not sure if this was enough to slay this foe that had caused them so much trouble. After the dust had settled they saw someone emerge from the ground.

"Heh, didn't think the same tactic would work again, but I just had to try."

It was a cultivator in white robe-like armor. This robe seamed to be reinforced mostly by having pauldrons and armguards out of some kind of metal. The man that emerged was holding one of his hands, it was trembling and his palm was giving out smoke.

"That hurt... slightly..."

"So, you are the one that is going against my Dark Palm Sect, is this some kind of rouse from the other Sects?

Guanyu moved forward while looking down at the young man, his beady eyes scanning him over with his spiritual sense.

"Ah yeah, just lured you here so that the other sects can attack your base!"

The man said while smirking.

"You must be joking. Even if they did that it would at least take them a month to get past our defensive formation, you think such a blatant lie would work here?"

The man floated slightly backward while shrugging.

"Not really, but it was worth a try. You cultivation nuts like to overthinking simple things, so it wasn't that far fetched."

Yang Guanyu frowned at his opponent, the man was only in the early stage of the nascent soul, how was he able to slay so many of his men?

"Enough of this, you are clearly desperate to defend that little city behind you, there must be a reason for it."

"Hear my orders, surround the city along with the Grand Elders while I take care of this whelp, Dark Palm Sect, attack!"

Chapter 185

A week had passed and the enemy army had finally arrived. The defenses were patched up into place but the new formation array was only able to cover the Zhang Clan compound and not the whole city. The first encounter with the Dark Palm Sect was victorious and one of the nascent soul enemies was defeated. This boosted everyone's morale making them think that they could win this.

The exact same strategy was attempted a second time even due to the complaints of the other cultivators, and just as expected it had failed. At this exact time, Matt was looking at his hand, it was trembling after he had defended himself against the strange ghastly attack of this new opponent.

'This guy might be tricky...'

He clenched his fist while looking up at the enemies before him. He thought that his improved disguising technique would let him take out one more grand elder before the big battle. He underestimated their leader's detection skills, he was now looking at the man while frowning.

Yang Guanyu [ Nascent Soul Late Stage ]

'One in the late stage, one at the middle stage and three at the early stage...'

Handling the four of the people that chased him down previously was hard enough. Now he had to go against this slender man looking old fart, which lowered his chances of victory even more.

'Those two haven't come out of their seclusion and I have no idea how close they are...'

The dimensional regalia masked any inside auras so he wouldn't know if they were breaking through even if it was happening right now.

"You want to go to the city while I'm here? Do you think you can handle me alone? Are you sure about that?"

Matt clenched his fists and flew up into the air, he could see that army of over a hundred flying ships heading towards Spirit Spring City. Even without the protection of their nascent soul elders, it would be hard to shoot down all of these flying vessels.

Yang Guanyu snorted while moving his palm forward in a grasping motion. From his perspective this man was only in the early stage of the nascent soul, there wouldn't be a problem in just snuffing him out.

"Arrogant welp, die!"

A large purple hand of spiritual energy appeared out of nowhere. It was massive in size, each finger the size of a massive tree. The hand moved forward in a grasping motion as Guanyu attempted to crush his opponent with pure spiritual energy.

"Two can play this game, you anorexic Palpatine looking, bastard."

Zhang Dong mirrored the motion of the Dark Palm sect leader, he created his own massive hand that went against the purple one. It was crackling with lightning energies and was radiating golden-colored energy. The two huge energy hands of the two masters collided which caused even the grand elders in the area to stop in their tracks.

"W-what is this, he can match the leader's strength?"

"Nonsense, the Sect Leader is a late-stage Grandmaster!"

The two hands struggled against each other, Yang Guanyu raised an eyebrow and pushed more Qi into that hand which made it expand in size. The purple hand started wining out momentarily before the golden one expanded to match the other. After some back and forth both of the hands exploded into fine energy particles, the explosion causing hurricane-like winds that pushed some of the flying ships to the side.

Zhang Dong flew back, his opponent did the same while the explosion pushed everything away. Guanyu narrowed his eyes, this wasn't what he was expecting. His level of strength was enough to safeguard a large sect, there really weren't that many people above him at this level.

"Who are you... it's impossible that someone like you has remained hidden."

Zhang Dong just looked up and moved his hands over his chest, he struck a valiant pose before shouting out.

"You got me, in reality, I am the son of the Azure Emperor, if you harm me you'll all get eradicated."

The grand elders stopped and gasped, could this be true, if this youth was the actual son of the Empires ruler they would be all dead.

"Stop spewing nonsense, that is an obvious lie!"

Zhang Dong coughed into his hand while shifting his eyes to the side.

"You dare call the son of the Azure Emperor a liar! Hey, is that the Azure Emperor behind you?"

You could see a giant vein on the old Dark Palm Sect leader's forehead expanding. His pale face started getting red as he gritted his teeth.

"Kill them all!"

With this, the army of ships started to advance and it soon started getting bombarded by the city defense force that was set up on the walls. The four grand elders ignored the cultivator in white, leaving him to their sect leader. The man was confident and they wouldn't argue with him. Plus there had to be a reason that this man was trying to defend that structure, it would probably be best to find out why.

"Shit..."

Zhang Dong started glowing with a golden light that filled out the sky with a glaring glow. The light expanded to the sides, thunderous sounds echoed through the area. It looked like a miniature sun made from golden electricity and light was formed. It didn't take long for this effect to subside and be replaced by a large golden dragon that roared out into the sky.

The dragon burst upwards and towards one of the grand elders that were approaching Spirit Spring City. Matt's plan was to buy as much time as he could before his allies made some progress. The Dragon would help with protecting the city while he himself faced their strongest cultivator.

Yang Guanyu didn't just stat and look at Zhang Dong without doing anything. He unleashed his dastardly aura into the surroundings. Wails of spirits were heard and purple fog escaped from the gem stuck to the man's forehead. The mist expanded and expanded into the sky before forming into a shape.

The first thing Matt noticed about the mist was that it was taking a humanoid shape. The face looked like a skeleton, this skeleton was hovering in the sky while holding a large scythe. This was Yang Guanyu Soul-Beast, there were humanoid ones. This one looked like the grim reaper, it was dressed in a shadowy black robe and glowing purple energy was coming out of that hollowed skull.

Compared to the golden dragon the grim reaper looking soul-beast was a lot smaller, maybe just twice the size of its user. It just hovered behind the Dark Palm Sect elder, it's eye sockets burning with a spooky green glow. Yang Guanyu stood motionless in the air with his digits resting against each other in a triangle shape.

The skeletal figure behind him gazed at the man in the white robe, it rose its bony finger out while pointing at him.

"Ashes to ashes, dust to dust."

Matt felt that something was off the moment that man uttered those words. He raised his golden lightning barrier instantly before some strange dastardly fog surrounded him. It came out of nowhere and was highly corrosive, he could see it trying to eat away at his forcefield by the holy energies that were imbued into his defenses kept the demonic energy at bay.

"You... what is that awful Dao of the living..."

The man's beady eyes stared at Zhang Dong while he managed to protect himself from the strange energies. The grim reaper behind the man was still pointing out with his finger and probably resupplying this strange fog with more energy.

"Weak to the holy element?"

Zhang Dong smirked slightly and propelled himself forward while still keeping his shield up. He headed on a collision course with the Dark Palm Leader and his soul beast. The man in the late stage of the nascent soul level didn't move a muscle. He kept his long thin digits together while just staring.

The grim reaper behind him grew in size, its scythe moving out as it swung it against the incoming cultivator. The two energies collided with each other, the wails of many souls were heard as the reaper beast delivered a strong blow on the man surrounded by the circular barrier. The two energies fought with each other for a few moments before canceling each other out. Zhang Dong retreated a couple of steps and Yang Guanyu did the same, the man's complexion getting even paler after this exchange.

"Impossible! He was able to resist the Elder's Soul beast and secret arts!"

The grand elders were slightly busy with the golden dragon that appeared out of nowhere but they were able to see how their sect leader was faring. None of them would be able to survive one of Guanyu's demonic attacks, they knew that he was a demonic cultivator.No one cared about this fact as what mattered was the power and prestige that he brought to the sect.

He was mighty and not many could stand up to him due to the corrosive and poisonous nature of his attacks. He could even suck your soul from your body, leaving you nothing more than a skeleton. Somehow this man with white hair could protect himself from those attacks, they could feel that golden energy counteracting the venom that Yang Guanyu was producing.

One of the grand elders bit his lower lip and wanted to fly over to aid their leader. The golden dragon beast had other plans, it roared out while producing storm-filled clouds. The area began getting bombarded with golden lightning bolts that set any flying ship in the nearby area up in flames.

The whole place was a battlefield, the giant armada from the Dark Palm Sect continued on while getting barraged by the Zhang Clan defenses. Every able body was on those city walls, inserting all of their Qi into the long-range cannons. This was the only thing they could do to aid their leader in this battle, so they gave their all and some people were already passing out due to Qi depravation.

Everyone saw the moment the Patriarch's golden dragon appeared, this was overshadowed by the skeletal soul beast of the Dark Palm Sect leader. The strange aura from the creature was giving everyone the shivers it was as if it was sucking their Qi and Lifeforce away but just being there.

Things were different now, the clan might have had the upper hand against the small group of ships the first time around. They could submerge them in the cannon fire, they also had their Patriarch helping them. Now, on the other hand, they were against a hundred ship strong armada even with the golden dragon keeping the other nascent soul elders somewhat busy the enemies were advancing forward.

"Reporting Sir, the Patriarch has engaged in combat. He is facing off against what we presume to be the Dark Palm Sect Leader, he matches the descriptions."

The man getting the report was Zhang Jin. He was sitting in a room with some screens and looking at them. This place was the command center for the city defenses and the clan had managed to somehow copy it from the secret ground. This was far worse than the hologram console and looked more like a game of sink the battleship. The enemies were indicated as red dots, while the allies by green dots.

"Is there any word of the Feng Matriarch or the young Huo Clan lord?"

Zhang Jin asked.

"No sir, the secret treasure is inaccessible to us so we have no information."

Zhang Jin slammed his fist on the table and looked outside, he wanted to just fly out there on his sword and aid his grandson. He knew that it wouldn't change a thing and only might cause Zhang Dong's morale to plummet as he wouldn't last a second against any of those grand elders. He looked at the large gold dot that represented Zhang Dong and could only pray, pray for a miracle to happen.

Chapter 186

Zhang Dong and the Dark Palm Sect leader clashed a couple of times. A golden fist collided with a tip of a scythe that was being held up by a giant skeletal specter in a black robe. Each time the two masters connected with their blows a shockwave of mixed Qi energies were sent out into the surroundings.

It was a peculiar sight to behold. The energies that the younger cultivator was exuding, energized the soil, and made the grass and plants grow. On the other hand, the energy that the old man was giving out caused everything in the vicinity to die and rot away.

Somewhat further away there was another large battle taking place. There were four beasts attacking a larger one, the bigger one was a golden dragon that was shooting out lightning bolts from its maw. The four soul-beasts belonged to the four grand elders while the golden dragon was the one Zhang Dong was controlling.

The dragon beast was somehow holding its ground, but it was mostly on the defensive. The other beasts didn't give it much of an opportunity to counter-attack. The opponents varied by size and stature, one looked like a giant crane with a crimson red beak. Another one that was the closest to the golden dragon's size looked like a snapping turtle with an outer shell coated with huge green spikes. The third one was a giant cobra that spit copious amounts of venom, the last one was a giant ox with a fiery mane.

All of those colorful creatures were charging at Zhang Dong's soul beast. The dragon repelled the Ox with its tail only to be attacked by the giant spikes of the turtle that fired them off. One of the spikes connected with the beasts scaly hide and shattered into many tiny pieces unable to pierce it. Before the Dragon could counter-attack with its long-range breathing attacks the cobra spit venom and the crane kicked up blade-like winds. The golden beast could do nothing more than protect itself by curling up with its wings together and focusing its Qi on a protective barrier that deflected the attacks.

"That Soul beast is strong, how can it contend with the four of ours!"

Elder Wan shouted out while the other three elders tried pushing the golden monster back. In response, it roared and produced a storm cloud that started shooting out lightning bolts indiscriminately. The surrounding area was filled by golden thunderbolts that gave Zhang Dong's Soul beast some space but didn't deliver that much damage to its enemies that quickly retreated.

'My Dragon is having problems... I need to beat Skeletor here and go help him out.'

Matt thought while continuing his battle with Yang Guanyu. This old man looked like a walking corpse but was quite strong, he couldn't just blitz him like the other elders with his superior speed and power.

He threw a punch forward, it generated a surge of golden lightning energy that flew at his opponent. The reaper soul beast didn't move from behind the old man and just preformed a half-circle motion with the tip of its scythe. This motion produced some kind of illusion of a red moon that looked like it was soaked in blood. The moment the energy fist connected with the bloody moon, the moon rippled as if it was made from water. It was as if he hit a reflection of a moon from a pond, this ripple motion subsided after a moment as if it was never there in the first place.

"You have a lot of gall to try and fight me without your soul beast."

The old man showed an eerie smirk. He pointed out forward with his thin index finger, the reaper behind him swung forward and his scythe looked like it cut open the sky itself. Matt felt a shiver run down his spine the moment he saw that attack, he immediately propelled himself downward. The moment he performed his evasive maneuver, a large scythe appeared behind him aiming for his neck. He was quick enough to evade it but he lost an inch of his hair while at it.

'This guy is strong...'

Matt gulped, sweat running down his forehead as he almost got decapitated. He needed to step it up a notch if he was going to land a decisive blow but he was hesitating to go all out. One reason being the other four cultivators fighting his dragon, if he went all there was a big chance that he would lose against the elder quartet due to the draining nature of his techniques.

'Should I go for it... or should I buy more time for the others...'

He stared focused his spiritual sense behind him, the large armada of ships was heading for his city and the cannons weren't as effective as before. The flying ships had some sort of protective formation, the barrage of Qi bullets couldn't penetrate it effectively enough and they were advancing further and further. If this continued they would get into range and start returning fire.

Before he could make a decision he felt another of those dimensional scythe attacks coming his way. It wasn't one though as the grim reaper looking soul beast started swinging his scythe around at all sorts of angles. Matt finds himself dodging pointy black ghost blades left and right, his armor and clothes even ripping in various spots as he backed away.

"Getting distracted? You really have a death wish!"

Yang Guanyu shouted out while he started waving both of his hands around. The soul beast behind him increased in size slightly while the attacks continued, more ferocious and deadly than before.

"Don't get too cocky, you old fart!"

Zhang Dong's body started exuding a massive amount of Qi, he gave out a loud shout before charging forward. While flying forward he was continuously evading those dimensional blades. His body started transforming, golden lightning wrapped around his whole form and his muscles bulged out.

The scythe blades came from all directions, tiny rifts appeared around Zhang Dong's location. They shot out, going towards his body as they tried to impale him from multiple directions. The only thing they hit was his afterimage that exploded into thousands of tiny electrical sparks that caused some damage to the reaper soul beast.

Zhang Dong appeared right next to Guanyu while in his improved Embodiment of the Thunder God form. He was holding his right hand back and then threw it forward in a palm strike. Everything happened in a fraction of a second, the Dark Palm leader mustered up all of his power to block this attack.

An illusory figure appeared behind Zhang Dong as he was throwing his palm forward. It looked like a giant golden statue, similar to a buddha in appearance. This statue was sitting down in a lotus position and had multiple sets of arms. One of these arms was mirroring the attacking pattern of the Zhang Patriarch as he was pushing his palm forward.

Matt was lacking high-level techniques after ranking up into the nascent soul level. Luck was on his side though, he was able to get a nascent soul technique when he leveled up his body refining into the true golden body. This was an attacking technique that summoned a giant golden statue behind him. This statue looked like a cross between an Ashura and a Buddhist monk.

The shining palm went forward crashing into the defenses of the Dark Palm leader. The man formed a shadowy barrier in front of him, the reaper soul beast also used its scythe to defend against this attack. Guanyu found himself getting pushed back, slight cracking noises echoing as the attack connected fiercely.

The enemy cultivator flew backward and crashed into the ground, the golden statue faded away into nothingness after the attack finished. Zhang Dong remained floating in the air while panting slightly.

'Damn, this body refining attack uses up a lot of my stamina instead of Qi... can't use it that often.'

The Dark Palm cultivators on the side reacted in shock, their eyes going wide after witnessing the giant explosion that almost made their ears explode. The four grand elders even stopped attacking the golden dragon that was even getting injured by them at this point.

"T-the Sect Leader got pushed back?"

"I...is he able to fight?"

The four of them looked at the man hovering in the air, he was exuding massive amounts of radiant Qi. He was giving off an aura of someone that they shouldn't be messing with. They then turned to the spot that their leader was smacked away towards, hoping to see him uninjured.

Matt on the other hand was already pointing out with his finger, aiming at a spot behind all the smoke and dirt.

"You think I'll let you recover?"

A beam of light shot out of Zhang Dong's index finger, it impacted into the ground and caused another explosion to occur. Even though he wasn't able to see his enemy with his eyes he had other senses that allowed him to see through the smokescreen. He could clearly tell where the man was standing and didn't want to let him recover.

'I have to strike the iron while it is hot!'

He took off going for his target that was the tall and lanky Dark Palm sect Patriarch. The man had suffered a setback after receiving these two strikes and was retreating. He burst out of the ground while frowning, some blood coming out of his mouth. Before he could shout out some curses at his opponent he saw a fist coming his way. The only thing he could do was to turtle up and set up a ghastly barrier made from purple soul energy.

Lightning-fast attacks rained down on Yang Guanyu who couldn't get a hit in between the barrage. He found himself on the defensive while the opponent that was clad in a mantle of golden lightning continued to attack. Soon his barrier burst like a soap bubble and the familiar golden palm speed for his face once more. The palm descended once again with even more power behind it.

"I won't let you!"

Before the strike could be delivered Zhang Dong had to move his forearm upwards to cover his face. He felt a massive blow that caused his bones to strain and his muscles to twitch. He was sent flying to the side before his golden palm attack could land decisively on Yang Guanyu's face. He looked to the person that interrupted his assault and discovered that it was one of the grand elders. He was a slightly larger man with a large two-handed battle hammer, it was a miracle that he didn't have a broken bone.

'Damn... my whole forearm is numb...'

He glared at the Dark Palm grand elder that came to the rescue of their leader. Before he could say anything he had to propel himself backward as another Qi attack was thrown his way, this time by the old lady cultivator that was also a nascent soul grand elder.

"Sect Leader, let us help you take out this man, he is far too dangerous!"

Zhang Dong panted, he had used quite a bit of his spiritual energy to rush this old slender-man looking elder. He hoped to end the battle fast or at least injure him before the other elders came to help him, his strategy had failed. He could see Guanyu rising up and his wounds healing rapidly as he circulated that demonic energy around him. The plants around the area started whithering and anyone below the nascent soul level would also be sucked dry as this demonic cultivator healed himself.

"Yes, he needs to die!"

The old man replied in a strange voice, his body had gotten paler and even lost some mass after this exchange. He had finally realized that this man he was facing was far more dangerous than expected.

"Hear my order, all grand elders are to focus on this enemy cultivator, the rest of the sect will attack the city on their own!"

Guanyu was positive that he wouldn't beat Zhang Dong on his own. He was far too powerful to be left alive and was also someone that used the holy Dao that demonic cultivators like him were weak against. The city in the back had no value, this man had to go down and he needed to die fast before they continued.

Chapter 187

Matt looked at his new opponents, he had to back away while the enemies recovered. The four other elders were now hovering around their sect leader that was right in the middle. The soul beasts were recalled by the four grand elders that stood against him, his own golden dragon also retreated and was roaring at the enemies.

'Outnumbered five to one... '

This reminded him about the time when he protected his clan from the initial invasion of some other clans. He was also outnumbered at that time, but there were differences. For one, these people were all the top brass and from one sect while the old enemies that he faced were far lower on the totem pole and their teamwork wasn't that great.

"I see that the noble Dark Palm sect knows how to gang up on people, very honorable of you..."

Zhang Dong chuckled while rubbing his forearm that was still a bit jittery. The five cultivators stared daggers at him as they knew that he was making fun of them.

"Being noble has no worth in battle, the victorious ones are always just."

Yang Guanyu replied while moving forward. The five nascent soul elders moved in some kind of square formation with their leader in the middle. Their spiritual power had a serious spike in energy as they advanced. Zhang Dong moved his hand forward as he signaled his Dragon to attack.

The beast released a massive blast of golden energy from its maw at the approaching cultivators. Sparks flew as the massive beam of golden plasma hit some kind of barrier that it couldn't get through. The four soul beasts charged forward and Zhang Dong's dragon charged in to intercept as they returned to their own battle. This left Zhang Dong against the four grand elders and their sect leader with his reaper like beast in the back.

More explosions resounded throughout the Zhang Clan region, the large galleon ships flew through the air while suffering some casualties. They finally managed to get into range and returned fire at those anti-aircraft weapons in the city. The cannon fire was exchanged and the protective formation that was keeping the walls in place crackled and was close to shattering.

The people that were on the city walls knew that the outer protective formation wouldn't hold out for long. They continued to stay and return fire though, none of them was willing to give the enemy even an inch.

"Keep firing, don't let them get near the city!"

"The Patriarch is holding the sect masters at bay, we must aid him!"

"We need more spiritual energy!"

Various battle shouts filled the area but they were quickly drowned out by multiple cannon fire coming from both sides. From the hundred ships, about eighty remained and they were continuously falling from the sky while slowly approaching. The enemy's barriers were slowly giving out but they were right at Spirit Spring Cities doorstep. The outer barrier finally fell and the anti flying ship weaponry started receiving damage. Various explosions filled the city walls and towers as the advancing armada pushed further in.

"It is time brothers, let us destroy this clan we had suffered enough loss to our face!"

A Dark Palm Sect elder in the core formation realm charged out while shouting. His bravado didn't last for long as he received a stray hit from a Qi blast from one of the intact Zhang Clan cannons. He was the first of the core formation warriors to die, he wasn't the last one charging forward though.

The City defense force found themselves getting pushed back, soon enough the enemy cultivators reached the walls and started destroying the weaponry. Shouts and cries of the defenders were quickly drowned out as the Dark Palm sects blades fell onto their necks and turned everything crimson.

The enemy cultivators charged into the city premise only to find the place abandoned. All of the city population was evacuated and there was not a soul to be found here. Some of the defenders from the walls had escaped before the sect warriors could get to them. The pursuit continued as the sect cultivators wanted vengeance for their members that died under the cannon fire.

"Senior brother, we found some of the enemy cultivators in that building!"

One of the sect members shouted out while a group of others charged at the spot he was pointing at. They kicked down the door to discover two people inside. The person was an old man that was wearing a blue robe, one that showed that he was a regular member of the Zhang Clan. The other one was an older lady with a more brownish tint to her skin and wearing a Feng Clan robe. The two were huddled together and the old man was holding something in his hand.

"Heh, what do we have here, two old love birds?"

The Dark Palm cultivators walked forward while brandishing large sabers that were already red from blood. Before they could deliver a deceive blow the two cultivators from Spirit Spring City nodded to each other and shouted out.

"For the alliance, For the new Sect! May it live long and prosper!"

A clicking sound was heard afterward, followed by a bright light that came from the ground. Before the Dark Palm cultivators could react the whole place exploded. The city defenders had placed massive amounts of explosives and attacking formations around the premises. With the people that lived here gone, there would be no civilian casualties.

The shouts and cries of the invading forces were drowned out by the booming sounds of detonation. The ones that were on the ground looking for survivors suffered a quick death, some of the people that were hovering in the air and close to the blast radius suffered crippling injuries.

"Get back into the sky, those bastards are blowing up the city with themselves in it!"

The invading forces fled back into their ships or onto their flying swords, the less powerful ones suffered from the various traps that were placed around the city. This was long from over though as there was still a large force hovering in the air going towards the main Zhang Compound where most of the city cultivators were in.

"The city is on fire..."

The people inside looked in shock at the happenings outside. The city that housed millions of people was getting destroyed, the springs of water were erupting from all the heat and the buildings were crumbling the further the enemy army went in. The only thing keeping them out now was the new grand defensive formation.

"Everyone stay inside, the new grand defensive formation can defend against nascent soul threats, we will be safe inside."

Zhang Liu shouted out while trying to calm some people down, he and his sisters were helping out the soldiers that managed to return from the defensive walls. The two were also performing their duties but were forced by their elders to retreat faster than the other united elements sect members.

Zhang Xue was quite adept at the water Dao recovery arts. These were boosted by their Patriarch to a new level and could even regenerate severed limbs. The process was quite slow though and required an ample amount of spiritual energy. She wasn't the only one helping out though, her friends from the once established 9th Platoon were all here with her.

Her senior sister Zhang Ai that got relocated to Moonlight City with her snake faced senior brother were both here. She was actually tending to his wounds he was badly injured from one of the explosions that occurred, his fingers were blown off and she was frantically trying to help him regenerate.

Zhang Bao and Zhang Peng that looked even more muscular than two years ago were helping carry the injured people in. Both of them were in the mids of the evacuation and also helped during the bombardment. The only reason they were alive now, was that the older members from the triforce alliance decided to stay behind while the youngsters could evacuate. They were carrying them over to the twins Zhang Yuu and Mii for healing as the two were quite adept at it.

Zhang Tai was also there, he had Zhang Hong's large arm around his neck as this large junior brother had suffered the most. His body was riddled with holes and scratches as he had used his larger body as a shield to protect some of the junior members during the retreat. The war was now upon them at there were casualties on both sides.

The attackers were now slowly encircling their main base while bombarding it with various attacks. The barrier rippled and shone in bright light as it managed to repel all of the attacks. After the smoke cleared the Dark Palm sect cultivators were surprised that the barrier didn't suffer any damage.

Everyone inside gave out a sigh of relief. The enemies couldn't get to them but they were still trapped here and could only wait for the battle outside to go their way.

The enemy sect didn't just wait there while twiddling their thumbs. The flying ships that survived the offensive encircled the Zhang Clan compound. Their cannons were continuously blasting at the defensive formation as they tried testing its defensive features. Even a powerful battier like this would run out of spiritual energy eventually.

"The formation is holding out, someone give me a report!"

Back at the command base, the Zhang Jin shouted, a cultivator with a mustache that was sitting to the side quickly replied.

"The Patriarch has engaged the enemy nascent soul cultivators in battle, an hour has passed since then and there is no clear winner yet."

The man gave a recount of the situation, mostly mentioning that even after an hour Zhang Dong wasn't able to deliver a killing blow to any of the five enemy nascent soul cultivators.

"That Yang Guanyu is really powerful and also looks to be a demonic cultivator... how can the other sects allow him to roam free?"

Zhang Zhi asked while looking at the little dots on the screen. The large golden one was bouncing about on it, it indicated Zhang Dong. Five other red dots were circling around it, this indicated the battle that was taking place between their Patriarch and the Dark Palm sect masters.

"Alas, no one will make a move on someone of that caliber. They are afraid, afraid of the repercussions. They can't risk losing valuable masters in a drawn-out fight. They might be able to bring the demonic cultivator to justice but then they will find themselves at the mercy of the other big sects."

Zhang Zhi sat down after Zhang Jin did the explanation. He more or less knew why this was happening but it was a hard pill to swallow. There was no trust between the large factions and they cannibalized themselves constantly. Battles for resources and terrain occurred and if one side showed any sign of weakness they would get probed and then attacked. This was the type of world they were living in, if there was uncertainty the other large factions wouldn't act.

The people glued their eyes to the screen. The large golden dot was slowly decreasing in size, each time the smaller red ones moved closer to it, it would slightly waver.

"Can the Patriarch win alone... are we supposed to wait here for our deaths after he draws his last breath?"

The others in the room deliberated. Zhang Dong had ordered them to stay behind the fortified barrier and just wait for the battle to be over. This didn't sit well with the warriors here, they would rather fight to their deaths than just wait for their demise. Still, they knew that they wouldn't be much of help against that many core formation and nascent soul cultivators. They knew that they could at most be meat shields for their leader.

While they were contemplating a loud sound could be heard outside. The large defensive formation churned with power and shone brightly. The trapped people looked with astonishment as they saw all the large ships in formation around an even larger one. This larger one had a massive cannon at the bow. This cannon was blasting a condensed stream of spiritual Qi at the forcefield, slowly eating away at its defenses. Would the formation hold up, or would the beam of Qi cut through in time no one knew, the people inside were aghast as they could only watch as the barrier was slowly thinning.

Chapter 188

"Aw... fuck!"

Zhang Dong thrust his sword forward, following his motion some golden energy shot forward. The sword energy collided with a purple beam of light and the two forces canceled each other out. He then propelled himself backward with haste as another attack came for his head, a few strands of his hair got severed as he propelled himself to safety.

At least that was what he thought, the moment he reached his destination another enemy cultivator was waiting for him. This time around he wasn't lucky enough to just dodge it. He felt something hitting his side, his mouth opened up wide and some blood escaped as he groaned. He held his midsection for a moment before looking at the person that hit him, the man was the same one that had previously struck him with that large sledgehammer.

'Five on one ... I can't land a decisive hit on any of them...'

He felt like a ball getting kicked around by some rowdy kids. His enemies continuously attacked him from all sides, he wasn't able to evade everything and found himself getting hit constantly. He was worried about the thin elder in the late stage the most, so he was making sure to keep watch over him. Though due to this he was getting pummeled by his four cronies whenever he dodged his attacks.

His white robe was ripped up and some of the armor parts were also falling off. This robe wasn't made to resist nascent soul attacks. The only reason that he wasn't dead yet, was thanks to his body refining technique. It proved to be essential in protecting him from the strikes but it also had a limit and he was slowly getting riddled with injuries. His soul beast wasn't doing much better as it was also battling against the odds.

"Heh, is that all you've got? I can keep this up for months!"

He spat some blood to the side and wiped his mouth. His opponents glared at Zhang Dong, he was proving to be a tough opponent even for them. Yang Guanyu flew forward and pointed at Zhang Dong with his bony finger, the other four elders shifted their positions to move around him.

"Don't listen to him, he is bluffing!"

The other four nodded at each other while getting into a battle formation. Guanyu gave some kind of signal with his eyes while flying back, his hands started moving as he formed some strange symbols with them. The other four didn't wait for their leader and continued with their attacks.

The Dark Palm sect leader smirked to himself while looking at his sect members battling the white-haired cultivator. He started murmuring something under his breath and continued making some strange hand seals.

'Hehe, just you wait...'

His eyes glowed as he saw the enemy cultivator glowing brightly and dispersing some attacks while dodging.

"Don't think that you are the only crafty person around, you just activated my trap formation!"

The man grinned while pushing both of his hands forward the moment he saw Zhang Dong move to a certain location. A greenish glow shot up from the ground and surrounded the white-haired cultivator. He was busy blocking two attacks and wasn't expecting a trap, even less on his home turf.

"Argh... what is this?"

A thick green pillar of light shot up from the ground and went straight to the heavens. Matt was right in the middle and felt like vomiting. This beam of light appeared out of nowhere and it was draining him of his Qi. He tried pushing his cultivation to the maximum in an attempt to get out but before he could the four nascent soul cultivators reacted.

They placed themselves around the green pillar of light with their hands stretched out. The moment this happened the light flashed brighter and Matt felt his cultivation getting drained. He found himself unable to move from the spot, he could barely move his hands and legs as he inched forward sluggishly.

"Truly monstrous, even when faced with the devouring soul formation he is still able to stay conscious!"

Said the only female grand elder from the bunch. She was pushing all of her remaining Qi into this trap that they had set up. While Zhang Dong was getting distracted by the group of nascent soul cultivators they were placing special array forming treasures. They had hidden them away during the scuffle and then successfully lured the young cultivator into their trap.

"He is resisting, we can't hold him for long Sect leader!"

Proclaimed the third nascent soul elder that was in the early stage. The man was quite lanky and his eyes were really small.

"No need to worry, I only need a second to eradicate him!"

Matt didn't like the sound of that, not for one bit. He pushed his cultivation to the apex, his eyes started glowing and he could feel power returning to his limbs as he flew forward.

"Ugh..."

The four people that were keeping him in place gritted their teeth and activated various spiritual treasures. They felt a new burst of power entering their bodies and the trapping formation burst with even more power. The green energy pillar expanded in thickness and it looked like Zhang Dong was getting swallowed up by a swamp.

His advance stopped and he found himself getting bombarded by excruciating pain. It was as if a million tiny hooks were getting pressed into his body and then pulled on his skin and flesh from all sides. He could barely hold on thanks to his pure holy energies that were surrounding his body, but even he couldn't go against four nascent soul masters working together while getting backed by various high-quality heaven treasures.

The golden dragon in the back couldn't come to his aid either, the moment he got his by this strange trap formation he felt his connection to his soul beast getting muddled. The beast's power dropped and it was now getting pummeled by the four enemy soul-beasts, unable to aid its master.

"This is the end, you will die for offending my sect, your city and everyone in it will fall next!"

Yang Guanyu had taken out a weapon of his own. It was, of course, a large war scythe, its blade crimson, and laid out with strange black runes. A war scythe was different from a regular scythe that was associated with the grim reaper. It was similar to a spear with a curving single-edged blade with the cutting edge on the concave side of the blade.

The blade released a strange black fog that covered the crimson edge that shone bright red. The power coming of this high-grade heaven weapon was astronomical and would surely deliver a massive blow to Zhang Dong if he didn't manage to dodge it. His whole body trembled as he tried to move, the four elders around the pillar pushed even more Qi into the formation to keep him at bay.

'Shit... I can't move...'

He couldn't budge a muscle, he could feel that the enemy cultivators wouldn't be able to hold this soul-devouring formation up for long. They didn't have to though, their sect leader was already close to being done with charging up his attack. Matt tried activating his system window, his only hope was reaching the disciple window and teleporting away from here.

'Damn move!'

There was a problem though. He needed to manually move his finger over to the system window and perform a couple of clicks. He wasn't able to even move his fingers, even less his whole arm to go through all the popup windows.

'Goddammit, who designed this shitty system this way!'

Yang Guanyu raised the war scythe up into the air while looking in the direction of Zhang Dong. The whole blade was giving off a sinister aura and it seemed that he was ready to deliver the finishing blow.

"You have caused enough trouble you whelp, now die and become nourishment for my cultivation!"

The old man brought down the blade of his weapon downwards in a swipe. The moment the war scythe blade descended it produced a surge of dastardly weapon energy that looked like black blood. It descended on Zhang Dong that was trying to escape. He pushed himself to the brink, his whole body expanded and his muscles bulged.

He tried activating both his bodily cultivation along with his nascent soul that was kicked into overdrive. The four enemy cultivators that were holding him in place started bleeding from their noses as they did the same, not willing to let this enemy go.

'Can I take this hit? Will I die? Can the others flee in time?'

A myriad of thoughts filled his mind while he thrashed about, unwilling to die at this moment as many lived depended on him. Still, he was only one nascent soul cultivator going against many. He was still an inexperienced fighter that had entered this trap without knowing any better.

The bloody scythe energy descended and was about to deliver a massive blow to the Zhang Clan Patriarch but then something strange occurred. One of the grand elders vomited copious amounts of blood, it was the one with the lanky one with the small eyes. The trap array wavered and Zhang Dong managed to release more of his aura.

The killing move from Yang Guanyu finally hit the spot that Zhang Dong was in but due to one of the elders faltering he was able to push himself to the side. Everything exploded and the other three grand elders defended themselves while moving back.

"What!? Who dares!"

After the smoke had cleared they spotted the cultivator in white a hundred meters away from them. He was still alive and kicking, he wasn't uninjured, his left thigh was bleeding profusely as his leg was almost severed from that attack. The attack went right through his metal-like muscle and almost went through his thigh bone, he was lucky enough for it being such a hard bone to cut through. If the attack went for the neck as his enemy intended, he would have been dead.

The other three grand elders and their sect leader glared at the man that had wavered and allowed the trap formation to break. He was holding his mouth and still vomiting the others only noticed now why he was doing that. They turned around and saw a large red soul beast choking out the large cobra soul-beast with its hands.

The red monster beast looked like a devil. The upper part was humanoid and the beast had large black horns, its hair was on fire as well as the rest of its body that radiated red plasma energy. The legs of this creature looked to be goat-like, it had coal-black hooves that connected to muscular bright red legs. The soul beast that this creature was mangling belonged to the grand elder that was suffering a backlash and explained how this happened.

This wasn't the only problem, the old woman grand elder started feeling quite weak as well as her own soul-beast was suffering a life-threatening attack of its own. It was getting attacked by a bird soul-beast. This beast looked similar to a legendary phoenix but instead of having fiery red feathers it had green ones. It was spitting out wind Qi out of its beak together with lightning bolts that were causing her crane soul-beast to loudly wail from the pain.

"Who dares attack the Dark Palm Sect!"

Yang Guanyu shouted while turning around. He wasn't expecting this young nascent soul master to get any backup, from the way he operated it made it look like he didn't have any type of backing. He could see two figures approaching, they were coming from the city. One looked to be a large muscular man, his hair and fists were on fire, his body was radiating dense fire energy. To his side was a woman, she was surrounded by green energy and her eyes were glowing with the same color. Whenever the woman flew storm clouds gathered and produced lightning strikes that devastated the area.

"Why wouldn't we dare to protect our Sect Leader?"

Proclaimed Feng Liena as she flew forward.

"That's right! You think we from the United Element sect are easy to bully?"

The five Dark Palm Elders looked at each other with question marks above their heads. They had no idea what this sect that they were speaking off was but apparently, they were the enemy as they came to help the man that they were attacking.